Current Situations and Next Steps
Item ownership has been transferred.
Thirdrema
Developer of Shangri-La Frontier
Utopia Entertainment Software
Utopia  Head of PR Division
Sakai Tsukuyogi
Chinese Herbal
Digestive Medicine
Shangri-La Frontier
Executive Producer
Ritsu Amachi
Original Text Reference Room
Utopia Founder
World Creative Administrator
Tsukuyo Tsukuri
Glitch
= A move that exploits a bug in the game's design
Damage 1
Hizutome
Saiga
She means items left behind by the Ashura Kai
(Not actually presents)
Hizutome
Important business until
tomorrow morning
Stay out!
Bonus Unique Scenario
Vorpal Epic
Items Needed
Receiver Delta
Positioner Delta
Transmitter Delta
Iron Ruins of the Divinity
Thirdrema
Prismatic Forest Grotto
Diremarsh Waste
Secondale
The Rampant Forest
Evolved  Drill Piercer → Glowing Pierce
Evolved  Skate Foot → Drift Step
Evolved  Parry Protect → Split-Second React
Evolved  Best Step → Moon Jumper
Evolved  Hunger Wolf → Transient
Evolved  Five-Boat Leap → Six-Boat Leap
Evolved  Vorpal Blade Tech [Moon's Reflection]
→ Vorpal Blade Tech [Moon's Reflection] v3
Sharp Turn → Choice of skill
Ignition Lv. 1
Overheat Lv. 1
Great Climb
Duelism
Nitro Gain Lv. 1
Boundless Slash
Assassin Pierce Lv. MAX
Infight Lv. MAX
Use Items
Tome of Truth: The Tombguard
Clear Sky Skillbook
Inventoria Key
Tome of Truth: The Tombguard
Chapter 1: The Birth of Wethermon the Tombguard
Long, long ago, during the age called the Divinity, a trivial misunderstanding led Wethermon to tell a small lie in a moment of weakness that resulted in Setsuna's death. This is what caused Wethermon to pledge himself to eternal protection of her grave. Setsuna knew Wethermon all too well, and so in her moment of death, she made a wish: "As not even death will stop him from guarding my grave, I pray that someone will stop him."
Clear Sky Skillbook
A digital record of sword techniques
left by a Divinity-era swordsmaster.
Inventoria Key
Non-Standard Specialized Armor
Adebane
Non-Standard Armament: Wire
Keep-Out Wire
Non-Standard Armament: Blade
Harbinger
New Chapter
"Venturing Wolves, Be Ambitious."