SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
The Speedrunner's Visit
to the Hidden Flower Grave
Mini!
SLF Theater
They live for a moment,
then remain for eternity...
The flower's name reflects
that— "Setsunatowa."
Perfect for you and me, right?
Boy, but it wasn't easy to get these.
All my equipment got
confiscated when I respawned.
Sorry, but I'm in a hurry.
You mind taking me on the
secret route to Thirdrema?
So, where's my payment?
Hey, thanks!
I'll take it on loan, if you don't mind.
I'm in a hurry, so later!
Thank you for saving me.
Please take this, as an
expression of my gratitude.
I cleared the event and got the loot!
Hey!
I knew you would be gone.
But I wanted to make it here before dawn.
Just in case... you know?
Kind of a silly thing to hope for, I know.
Boy, am I sentimental or what?
Well, I'll be back.
Set-chan.