Hey!
Help yourself.
Thank you.
What do we do now?
Pencilgon was our smooth talker,
and now she's been vaporized.
That's your friend, right?
Do something already!
More like the person who anticipated my escape plan,
laid an ambush, then shoved a friend request in my face!
I'm still kinda walking on eggshells here!
Ah, well.
Time to show off the social skills of a pro gamer!
G'luck!
I d-do have a question for you... Sunraku.
Y-Yes?!
I... well...
Do you and... Pencilgon...
What exactly is your relationship?
Oh...
Gaming buddies?
O-Oh, is that it?
Buddies... buddies...
Friends.
The Friend Warp timer is expiring.
Well, seriously, thanks again for helping today.
I'll pay you back sometime!
In that case, if ever you're free,
I'd love to adventure togeth—
Maybe I should find a game that boosts my social skills.
Yeah. Wanna play Love Clock?
Nah, forget it.
Too much pizzeria apprenticeship trauma.
Huh?
That creepy sword's still there.
Probably looked too freaky to take.
Hate to just leave it lying here, though.
Ah, well.
It's pretty creepy, but I guess I'll hang onto it.
Boy, I haven't felt this dog-tired in a while.
I'm gonna sleep well tonight.
I'm thinking less "sleep" and more "coma."
Yeah.
Let's hit up Thirdrema, then log out.
You said it.
What are you doing, Emul?
I beat that baddie, no respawns needed!
S...
Sunraku!
You're so amazing!
I was so worried!
Excuse me?
Hey, I'm back now.
Oh, that's right.
Thanks for this, Emul.
I managed to beat Wethermon
the Tombguard because of you.
S-Sunraku...
I'm so glad!
Chief Tsukuyogi!
What's the situation?
Wethermon the Tombguard's been beaten.
The unexpected timing has the whole company in a panic.
I'll bet.
Ctarnidd was supposed to be the first to fall,
with Wethermon in the middle
or, perhaps, even endgame.
I thought I'd be able to enjoy my wife's
home cooking for the first time in two days,
but I'm getting dragged back to the office.
Is Tsukuri in the basement?
Yes, likely holed up as usual.
But I heard Miss Amachi was heading off in that direction...
So...
Okay, I get it.
This is part of the job.
It's empty?
D-Dammit...
I'm going in unarmed!
You don't happen to have some antacids, do you?
Huh? Oh... no, I don't.
I see.
Employee ID recognized.
Please input code.
Code recognized.
Please confirm fingerprints.
Fingerprints recognized.
Now undergoing retinal scan.
Please place your face near the sensor.
This is bullshit!
Freaking open up already!
Retina print recognized.
Hey.
Wethermon's been defeated.
Didn't you say with the rate things were going,
no one would beat him in ten years?
I said Ashura Kai couldn't do it.
I wasn't expecting them to bring the Reward Scales into it.
But they didn't use any glitches or cheats.
It's impossible to complain about the result.
Impossible to complain?
Don't give me that!
You're the one who nerfed Wethermon
in that utterly disgusting way!
Admit it was a mistake! Right now!
Oh?!
That's because no one could ever beat him
with the original stats you gave!
That's because Wethermon's supposed to be
really, really, really strong!
He's the greatest hero of the Divinity!
But your stupid worries about stupid game balance
are ruining my carefully designed story concepts!
You can't tie story progress flags to an unbeatable monster!
Are you nuts or something?!
How dare you?!
You're a parasite feeding on
the leftovers of my beautiful world!
What was that?!
You couldn't balance your precious little world,
which is why I had to step in and do it for you!
Dumbass!
Your dandruff is terrible!
So's yours!
I had a shower two days ago!
And I had one three days ago!
My stomach hurts.
But I can't let this scare me off.
That's enough, both of you!
How long are you going to fight like children?!
You shut up!
It... It hurts!
Utopia's crown jewel is the fully immersive
VR game, Shangri-La Frontier.
Tsukuri Tsukuyo designed the world,
and Amachi Ritsu balanced it
to where it could function as a game.
Who could've imagined the core development staff
fighting like preschoolers?
I already have so much to do
to prepare for what's coming up,
and yet these two, every single time...
Calm down.
I'm the only one who can pacify them.
Still...
To think SLF's story would have kicked off
in this extremely unexpected way...
H-Hey, you two! At least go take a shower!
Shut up, you Pomade-stinking four-eyes!
I took a big, big step today!
Hizutome asked me to come to him...
Come, stand by my side.
And he gave me all those presents...
For you.
W-We'll keep getting closer, and in time,
maybe we'll get closer... in the real world...
Squee!
All right...
Time to get going!
I still gotta tally up all my gains.
M-My dadd—
The boss wants to see you.
How long have you been crying?
Mind if I ask you a question, then?
How'd you like that stubborn old fool?
Well, Don Vash...
Wethermon was quite strong indeed.
That Woodmage thing couldn't even compare.
I'll bet.
If I didn't have experience playing trash games
where unreasonable attacks were the norm,
it'd have been over before it started.
Hey, Emul.
Where do you think you're blowing your nose?
Did he depart this world satisfied?
He said it was a job well done.
Ah, excellent.
Cultivate and open the way...
Perhaps the time has come.
For what?
Would you like to know the truth of this world, son?
I would be honored.
Then there's a little something I'd like you to do for me.
What's that?
Just bring me a few items.
Huh?
There's a process to these things, see?
Once you've done it, I'll tell you the truths of this world.
Oh, come on!
I was all hyped up about kicking off
my bonus unique scenario, Vorpal Epic,
and it's a freaking fetch quest?
Well, fine.
That's how these things usually start, anyway.
Let's see... Items needed...
Receiver Delta, Positioner Delta, Transmitter Delta...
I think I get the gist, but where do I even start
looking for these things?
Surely you're not going to send me out blind...
Right.
Check out a place called the Lightless Barrens.
Um...
Lightless Barrens?
I guess it's nowhere near Thirdrema, huh?
You won't find it on a chintzy map like that.
Guess I'll check Peatz's shop next.
Well, then, I guess I'll go wait patiently for your return.
B-But, Don! Can't you give me any more info?!
As long as you're not too great a fool...
you should find it soon enough.
Maybe it's in an area way ahead of where I am?
Unique scenarios do kinda seem like endgame content, so...
Guess it makes sense.
It seems it may be quite a long journey!
Sweet, naïve Emul...
You might be surprised.
Hell yeah!
My level freaking exploded from that Wethermon fight!
I got a flood of new skills and evolved skills, too!
Guess it'll be time for a new visit to the Skill Garden!
Well done, indeed!
A power boost like this'll have me
skating through the game for a while!
But wait, there's more!
Yes, don't forget...
The Wethermon battle loot!
The time has come!
They wouldn't put me through all that effort
for a totally lame payoff, right?!
Gimme the good stuff!
What the heck's this?
"Tome of Truth: The Tombguard."
Oh, it's just a detailed rundown of Wethermon's backstory.
I can read that stuff later.
C'mon, give me something I can use!
Let's see... "Clear Sky Skillbook"?
Clear Sky Skillbook.
"A digital record of sword techniques
left by a Divinity-era swordmaster."
"The strikes recorded within can cleave the heavens,
pierce the earth, and clear dark clouds."
"Divinity equipment is required
to decipher and master them."
Wait, isn't "Clear Sky" that array of skills Wethermon used?
What? What?!
What is it, Sunraku?
I can freaking learn Wethermon's skills?!
You kidding me?!
Which means... I might be able to learn "Sky Clear", too?!
This is too freaking good!
It says I need Divinity equipment, so it might be a while,
but this is gonna be great!
Right, Emul?
I thought you were gonna rub my cheeks off.
Hell yeah!
Let's keep up the pace!
And for my last piece of loot!
Hey, it's an accessory!
I'll bet it gives a pretty sweet stat boost!
Let's see...
"Inventoria Key."
"It is both the door and the key to a storage space."
"A special bracelet worn only by a select few,
even during the Divinity."
"Even if the wearer is player-killed,
neither the accessory nor the items inside
the storage space can be stolen."
Hey, pretty good!
"Provides portable access to an expandable space."
"Synchronizes with anatomical data
to fuse and become a part of the user."
"Acts as a warehouse with infinite storage"?
So it's like an item box you can stuff
anything smaller than 50 meters in?
I can also spend some MP to transport into
the storage space itself, huh?
Not as cool as I'd hoped, but let's give it a try.
H-He disappeared!
So this is my storage space... huh?
H-Hey...
I know I was asking for stuff I could use, but...
What... What the...
What the hell is this?!
I'm pretty much destitute now,
but I went hard on bartering and managed to get them.
I'll have something much nicer the next time I come by.
So I hope you can let this one slide.
These flowers stay in bloom for five minutes, then die.
But if you pick them before that happens
and put them in your inventory,
the flowers stay in bloom, they say.
They live for a moment, then remain for eternity...
It fits the flower's name, "Setsunatowa."
Perfect for you and me, right?
You called yourself a copy,
but as far as I'm concerned, you were the original.
The real deal.
If you wish to know of your roots,
of the truth of this world...
Seek out "Bahamut."
The truth of this world, eh?
Well, I'd originally meant to quit SLF
after I beat Wethermon the Tombguard...
But all right, Set.
Whatever this Bahamut thing is...
I'll get it to cough up all the secrets it holds.