This world is filled with too many games to count...
though the vast majority simply come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of them all
is the fully immersive VR game
boasting over 30 million players worldwide.
Shangri-La Frontier rightly earns
the status of "god-tier"!
One lover of trash games, Hizutome Rakurou,
is trying out this very Triple-A!
What adventures await him there?
Heading to the dojo?
Y-Yes!
Um, well...
I thought I'd see if you had
any good games before practice.
Just so you know, Hizutome's not here.
Um, I...
It's summer break, so he's probably
been playing this one the whole time.
So you still haven't found him?
Well, you said he always plays as "Sunraku,"
so I've been looking for him under that username.
But he seems to have skipped the first tutorial city entirely.
He's charting his own course, huh?
A typical thing for trash game fanatics.
He'll do things normal players won't do,
and run into all kinds of outrageous unique scenarios!
Before he even knows how to play the game?
Well... I guess it does seem plausible.
I'm sure you'll find him soon.
Don't give up, Rei!
Okay.
Then tell him how you feel.
I'm heading out!
Sure.
I've got work after, so I'll be out late!
"Unique scenarios recommended for beginners."
Trigger conditions for the "Tour of Rabituza".
This must be it.
"If you defeat a monster of a higher level than you
with Vorpal weapons equipped,
a special Vorpal Bunny will appear
in any town and invite you to Rabituza."
"The Vorpal Bunny will just keep running
without saying anything,
so make sure you don't lose sight of it."
"Once you arrive, if you defeat a monster
terrorizing their city called the Lagonian Python,
you'll learn the 'Enchant Vorpal' spell."
Yeah, that's nothing like
the unique scenario I played yesterday.
That sure wasn't a Python I encountered.
The yakuza-boss-looking bunny was intimidating,
but not as much as Lycagon.
Well?
Mind giving me a bit of your time?
I'm the boss here in Rabituza.
The name's Vysache.
You gave that pup quite a fight, didn't you?
That's a hell of a vorpal soul you've got.
What in the world is a "vorpal soul"?
What do you think?
I'd be happy to get you up to snuff, if you're up for it.
Get me up to snuff?
Oh, I get it now!
It's a training quest!
And if I complete it, I could get ridiculous buffs!
I have no reason to refuse!
I place myself in your hands...
Don.
What?
"Don"?
O-Oh, that was just a little joke...
Oh, crap!
Did I choose the wrong response?!
I like you.
Asking for my training does make you my underling!
Glad you know how these things work.
Feel free to call me Vash.
A privilege I reserve for people with potential.
S-Sure... Don Vash.
I-I'm so glad it was the right choice!
I thought he was gonna skin me alive!
Emul!
Yes?!
Dadd—I mean, Boss?!
I'm putting him in your care.
Yes! I'm going to work so hard!
So, so hard!
So, so, so hard!
All right, Sunraku!
Allow me to give you a tour of the palace!
H-Hang on a minute!
It's been a pretty long play session for me.
I was thinking of taking a break.
Oh, really? That's a shame.
And I'd like to look up more about
unique scenarios and monsters.
I'll show you to one of our inns, then!
Oh, really?
I can register my respawn point here?
Sounds great!
Leave every little thing to me!
Oh, right. I forgot about this.
Wh-What the heck?
A forced-equip item?
"Vorpal Soul Collar" has been acquired.
It halves the EXP I receive?!
Hang on!
It's no use.
You can't take that off unless I allow it.
Extreme hardship is necessary
for the weak to grow stronger.
Never forget the vorpal soul.
It suits you very well, Sunraku!
I...
I've been saddled with another restriction?!
A 2.5 multiplier on my stat points, huh?
Even if it does halve my EXP received,
that's a pretty big upside.
Kinda broken, to say the least.
No one on the forums seems
to know about Vysache or Emul,
let alone the Vorpal Soul Collar.
No one's found a unique scenario
where you enter the Rabituza Palace.
Which makes it a unique scenario only I know about!
That's pretty rad!
Whoops, time for my appointment.
Stupid Katzo.
Why'd we have to do this in BERP?
Been forever since I logged in.
Berserk Online Passion.
BOP for short.
Or, derisively, BERP.
BERP is a fighting game Rakurou once got addicted to.
So it is, naturally, a trash game.
Its playerbase has waned to less than 100 sign-ins per day,
leaving many to wonder why the service is still running.
Which means most of those who remain know each other, and share the same passion.
Trash game enthusiasts.
You've shown yourself at last, Sunraku.
Shall we get right to it?
Rules?
Ready? Fight!
You even need to ask?
Vale tudo!
"Anything goes"!
That's some creepy-ass glitching.
It's a new move I worked out
while you were focused on Failia!
Get a taste of my NSFW Tentacle Attack!
You developed a new glitch, huh?
How'd a madman like you get to be a pro gamer, huh, Modor Katzo?!
Quick-Draw Fist!
What?!
I'm using a delay, but he's still blocking them?!
You're the madman with the ridiculous reaction speed!
Quick-Draw Fist is the ultimate style!
Theoretically, as long as you've got 12 frames,
you can even counter boss insta-kill attacks unscathed!
I'll break through all your hits!
Hey, Modor Katzo's fighting!
Hold on! Isn't that Sunraku?!
Really?
Though this is considered a trash game,
That's a top-tier match-up!
the reason for its niche appeal is on display here.
Vale tudo, or rather "Bug tudo," is "any bug goes."
Heck yeah!
The afterimage fist textures were part of the hitbox?!
You lose!
Still, I've only been fighting NPCs lately.
Getting a PvP trashgamium recharge
really hit the spot, Katzo.
When you emailed me to say you were taking on SLF,
I figured it was a bad joke. So it's legit?
I'm not ashamed to say, it's got me pretty much hooked!
Guess I'll be seeing pigs fly tomorrow.
Hear me out.
I've been reading the forums.
SLF's got these crazy strong monsters
called the Seven Colossi.
The playerbase has only managed
to even get the names of four of them.
So?
No one's beaten a single one ever since the service started.
Aw, it's over already?
Darn! I missed it!
Hey, that's Sunraku!
It was awesome, man!
So I fought one of them...
And it wasted me.
So that's why you're so into it?
At least, I doubt I'll set it down until I beat that mutt.
Maybe I'll start playing, too.
For real?!
Hearing you talk it up piques my interest.
Besides, none of my IRL friends play BERP.
Oh, right!
You-know-who is playing SLF, too.
"You-know-who"?
I sent 'em an email that you were in the game, too.
Since it's such a big deal.
"Sunraku's picked up SLF"?
That trash game addict, doing a Triple-A title?
I always thought if he ever stopped the habit...
he'd die because of some withdrawal.
I'll have to oh-so-gently guide him through it.
Hey, we're really back!
It's called a teleport gate.
A trivial matter for me, of course!
Emul's a handy little thing.
And... maybe it comes from playing BERP for a while,
but these SLF avatars are hella easy to move in!
But the minute you woke up, you wanted to go elsewhere.
Why?
There's lots of fun places in the Rabituza Palace!
Like an arena, a training hall, and more!
Oh, I'm totally interested in the palace, too, and I really want a good tour of it.
But I'd really like to get to Thirdrema
before the crowds start pouring in.
Crowds?
There's been a big uptick in players
since summer break started, right?
The forums report that the starter town, Firstia, is packed to the gills with new players.
This city won't be far behind.
Ah, yes, indeed!
Which means we're gonna see logjams at facilities,
and fights over monsters and mining spots.
Ah, yes, indeed!
I hear Thirdrema is a pretty big city.
If I'm gonna whole-ass that unique scenario,
I'd like to do it in a big city with plenty of breathing room.
Ah, yes, indeed!
You really following?
I don't actually know what most of that means!
Okay, so you weren't.
But if you wish to reach the next city,
I'll gladly help you get there!
A party request?
I can have NPCs in my party?
Well, you can't reach Rabituza or the palace without me!
I get that, but I figured you'd just tag along.
She's mostly got better stats than me.
Speed's the only place where I've got a slight edge.
No problem. I'll catch up soon enough.
Right.
I'm pretty sure Lycagon's Mark
is the trigger for this unique scenario.
I wonder if Emul is the game's way of making up for it.
If so, it's good design.
Let's work together, Emul.
Okay!
At your service, Sunraku!
So cute!
Where'd you get that rabbit?!
Is that a Vorpal Bunny?
Can you tame them as pets?
And did I just see it talk?!
Wait, a bird?
Half-naked?! A pervert?!
That sure was a quick change in tune!
Yes! It talked!
Crap... we've been talking this whole time
so I stopped thinking about it,
Hey, hey! What's your name?
but Emul's an NPC attached to
an undiscovered unique scenario!
I'm Emul!
Emul!
Hey, Emul, how can I get you in my party?
Since I've got it to myself for now,
I'd like to keep it a secret until I can clear it...
Well, you can—
Zip that lip!
That was my ventriloquism act!
Heavens, I must be off!
Wait!
Aw, I wanted to know how he tamed them.
I got a screenshot! Let's ask on the forums!
Great.
There's no more other players nearby now, at least.
I'm terribly ill-suited to all this running around!
What kind of rabbit says a thing like that?
Besides, you've got about the same speed stat as I do.
Now, what would you have us do next?
Good question.
Actually, there's something I wanna confirm.
Confirm?
There's that line in my curse... the mark.
"Monsters of lower level than
the afflicted character will flee."
Sunraku, it fled away!
Like it spotted some kind of degenerate.
But this is perfect!
First, I chase after it at top speed!
I don't just pursue mindlessly,
but I'll make it run into an obstacle!
And then...
the moment it changes direction...
I throw!
Then, once it's stopped...
I strike with as much speed as I can muster!
An attack bonus from inertia.
It's a law of physics you take for granted in the real world,
but very few games actually try to replicate it.
Naturally, SLF models reality as close as it can!
That was spectacular, Sunraku!
I could hardly tell which one was the real monster!
Was that supposed to be a compliment?
Okay!
Even with the mark, I know I can take out
monsters that speed or slower.
I've verified what I needed to, so here's the plan!
Ignore the scrubs!
Straight to the area boss!
That is all!
That wasn't much of a plan!
Now, as befits us speedsters, gotta go fast!
Away we go! To the area boss, and Thirdrema beyond!
Yeah!
Um...
According to the map, the area boss is around here.
But it's swamp as far as the eye can see.
Oh, no!
This will simply ruin my clothing.
Yeah, no, I think I get it.
With what Emul said on the way here and all...
I was in such a hurry to get out of town,
I never got a chance to ask about the next boss.
You know anything about it, Emul?
Well, it's a monster named Mud Digger!
It rockets out of the ground to attack,
so it's crucial to find a way to hold it in place!
Mud Digger.
I gotta fight it in the swamp.
I might be in trouble here.
Sunraku, it's coming!
Hop on my shoulder!
Righty-o!
A characteristic of Shangri-La Frontier's "swamp" terrain...
is that it forces the player in "walking state."
One leg always remains trapped in the marsh
until the other foot reaches the bottom.
In other words...
This is my worst match-up possible!