This world is filled with
too many games to count,
though the vast majority simply
come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of all games
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide—
Shangri-La Frontier, which rightly
earns the title of "god-tier game"!
One lover of trash games, Rakuro Hizutome,
is trying out the god-tier
game, Shangri-La Frontier!
What adventures await him there?
Heading to the dojo?
Y-Yes!
Um, well...
I thought I'd see if you had any
good games before practice...
Hizutome-kun's not here, just so you know.
Um, I...
It's summer break, so he's probably
been immersed this whole time...
You still haven't found him?
Well, you said he always plays as "Sunraku,"
so I've been looking for
him under that name...
But he seems to have skipped the
first tutorial city entirely...
He's charting his own course, huh?
Typical trash game fanatic.
He'll do things normal players won't do,
and run into all kinds of
outrageous unique scenarios!
But as the first thing he does in the game?
Well... I guess it does seem plausible.
I'm sure you'll find him soon.
Keep going, Rei-chan!
Okay...
Then tell him how you feel.
I'm heading out!
Sure.
I've got work after, so I'll be out late!
"Unique scenarios recommended for beginners."
"Tour of Rabituza" trigger conditions...
That must be this.
"If you defeat a monster of higher level
than you with Vorpal weapons equipped,
a special Vorpal Bunny will appear in
any town and invite you to Rabituza."
"The Vorpal Bunny will just keep
running without saying anything,
so make sure you don't lose sight of it."
"Once you arrive, if you
defeat the Lagonian Python,
a monster terrorizing their city,
you'll learn the 'Enchant Vorpal' spell."
Yeah, that's nothing like the unique
scenario I played yesterday.
That sure wasn't a Python I encountered.
It was an intimidating—if not as much
as Lycagon—yakuza boss-looking bunny.
Well?
Mind giving me a bit of your time?
I'm the boss here in Rabituza.
The name's Vysache.
You gave that pup quite a fight, didn't you?
That's a hell of a vorpal soul you've got.
What in the world is a "vorpal soul"?
What do you think?
I'd be happy to get you up to
snuff, if you're up for it.
Get me up to snuff?
Oh, I get it now!
It's a training quest!
Unique scenario training could
yield unprecedented buffs!
I have no reason to refuse!
I place myself in your hands...
Aniki.
"Aniki"?
O-Oh, that was just a little joke...
Oh, crap!
Did I choose the wrong response?!
Hey, I like you.
Asking for my training does
make you my underling!
Glad you know how these things work.
Feel free to call me Vash.
That's a privilege I afford
to people with potential.
'K-'Kay... Aniki Vash.
I'm so glad it was the right choice!
I thought he was gonna skin me alive!
Emul!
Yes?!
Dadd— I mean, Boss?!
I'm putting him in your care.
Yes!
I'm going to work so hard!
So, so hard!
So, so, so hard!
All right, Sunraku-san!
Allow me to give you a tour of the palace!
H-Hang on a minute!
It's been a pretty long play session for me.
I was thinking of taking a break.
Oh, really? That's a shame...
And I'd like to look up more about
unique scenarios and unique monsters.
I'll show you to one of our inns, then!
Oh, really?
I can register my respawn point here?
Sounds great!
Leave every little thing to me!
Oh, right. I forgot about this.
Wh-What the heck?
A forced equip item?
"Vorpal Soul Collar" acquired.
It halves the EXP I receive?!
Hang on!
It's no use.
You can't take that off unless I allow it.
Extraordinary hardship is necessary
for the weak to grow stronger.
Never forget the vorpal soul.
It suits you very well, Sunraku-san!
I...
I've been saddled with another restriction?!
Two point five times stat points, huh?
Even if it does halve my EXP received,
that's a pretty big upside.
Kind of broken, to say the least.
No one on the forums seems to
know about Vysache or Emul,
let alone the Vorpal Soul Collar.
No one's found a unique scenario where
you enter the Palace of Rabituza.
A unique scenario only I know about!
That's pretty exciting!
Whoops, time for my appointment.
Stupid Katzo.
Why'd we have to do this in BERP?
I haven't logged into this game in forever.
Berserk Online Passion.
BOP for short.
Or, derisively, BERP.
BERP is a fighting game
Rakuro once got deeply into.
It is, naturally, a trash game.
Its playerbase has waned to less
than a hundred sign-ins per day,
leaving many to wonder why
the service is still running.
Which means most of those
who remain know each other,
and are of a single kind—
trash game enthusiasts.
You've shown yourself at last, Sunraku.
Shall we get right to it?
What are the rules?
Ready? Fight!
You know what they are...
Vale tudo!
"Anything goes"!
That's some creepy-ass glitching.
It's a new move I worked out
while you were focused on Failia!
NSFW Tentacle Attack!
You developed a new glitch, huh?
How'd a madman like you
get to be a pro gamer?
Modor Katzo...
Quick-Draw Fist!
What?!
I'm using a delay,
but he's still blocking them?!
You're the madman,
with reaction speed like that!
Quick-Draw Fist is the ultimate style!
Theoretically, as long as
you've got twelve frames,
you can even counter boss
insta-kill attacks unscathed!
I'll break through all your hits!
Huh?
Hey, Modor Katzo's fighting!
Hey! Isn't that Sunraku?!
Really?
Though this is considered a trash game,
That's a top-tier match-up!
the reason for its niche
appeal is on display here.
Vale tudo—Rather, "Bug tudo"—
"Any bug goes."
Heck yeah!
The afterimage fist textures
were part of the hitbox?!
You lose!
Still, I've only been fighting NPCs lately.
Getting a PvP trashgamium recharge
really hit the spot, Katzo.
When you emailed me to say
you were taking on SLF,
I figured it was a bad joke. So it was true?
I'm not ashamed to say,
I'm pretty darn into it!
I guess I'll see pigs flying tomorrow.
Hear me out.
I've been reading the forums.
SLF's got these crazy strong
monsters called the Seven Colossi.
The playerbase has only managed to
even get the names of four of them.
So?
No one's beaten a single one of
them since the service started.
Aw, it's over already?
Darn! I missed it!
Hey, that's Sunraku!
It was awesome, man!
A raging battle of bugs!
So I fought one of them...
And it wasted me.
So that's why you're so into it?
At least, I doubt I'll set it
down until I beat that mutt.
Maybe I'll start playing SLF, too.
For real?!
Hearing you talk it up piques my interest.
Besides, none of my IRL friends play BERP.
Oh, right!
You-know-who is playing SLF, too.
"You-know-who"?
I sent 'em an email that
you were playing, too.
Since it's such a big deal.
"Sunraku's Picked Up SLF"?
That trash game addict, playing SLF?
I always thought he had some condition
where he'd die if he ever
stopped playing trash games.
I'll have to oh-so-gently
guide him through it.
Hey, we're really back!
It's called a teleport gate.
A trivial matter for me, of course!
Emul's a handy little thing.
And... maybe it comes from
playing BERP for a while,
but these SLF avatars are
easy as hell to move in!
But the minute you woke up,
you wanted to go elsewhere.
Why?
There's lots of fun places
in the Palace of Rabituza!
An arena, a training hall, and more!
Oh, I'm totally interested in the palace, too,
and I really want a good tour of it.
But I'd really like to get to Thirdrema
before the crowds start pouring in.
Crowds?
There's been a big uptick in players
since summer break started, right?
The forums report that the
starter town, Firstia,
is packed to the gills with new players.
This city won't be far behind.
Ah, yes, indeed!
Which means we're gonna
see logjams at facilities,
and fights over monsters and mining spots.
Ah, yes, indeed!
I hear Thirdrema is a pretty big city.
If I'm gonna whole-ass that unique scenario,
I'd like to do it from a big city
with plenty of breathing room.
Ah, yes, indeed!
You're following all this?
I don't actually know
what most of that means!
Okay, so you weren't.
But if you wish to reach the next city,
I'll gladly help you get there!
A party request?
I can have NPCs in my party?
Well, you can't reach Rabituza
or the palace without me!
I get that, but I figured
you'd just tag along...
She's mostly got better stats than me.
Speed's the only place where
I've got a slight edge.
No problem. Just overtake her soon enough.
Right.
I'm pretty sure Lycagon's Mark is the
trigger for that unique scenario...
I wonder if Emul is the game's
way of making up for it.
If so, it's good design.
Let's work together, Emul.
Okay!
Let's work together, Sunraku-san!
So cute!
Where'd you get that rabbit?!
Is that a Vorpal Bunny?
Can you take them as pets?
And did I just see it talk?!
Wait, a bird?
Half-naked?! Pervert?!
You're a very excitable person!
Yes! It talked!
Crap... we've been talking this whole
time so I stopped thinking about it,
Hey, hey! What's your name?
but Emul's an NPC attached to a
never-before-seen unique scenario!
I'm Emul!
Emul-chan!
Hey, Emul-chan, how can
I get you in my party?
Since I've got it to myself for now,
I'd like to keep it a secret
until I can clear it...
Well, you can—
Zip that lip!
That was my ventriloquism act!
Heavens, I must be off!
Wait!
Aw, I wanted to know how you tame them!
I got a screenshot!
Let's ask on the forums!
Great.
There aren't any more players
nearby now, at least.
I'm terribly ill-suited to
all this running around!
What kind of rabbit says a thing like that?
Besides, you've got about
the same speed stat as I do.
Now, what would you have us do next?
Good question.
Actually, there's something I wanna confirm.
Confirm?
There's that line in my curse... the mark.
"Monsters of lower level than the
afflicted character will flee."
It fled from you, Sunraku-san!
Like it spotted some kind of degenerate.
Okay, perfect!
First, I chase at top speed!
I don't just pursue mindlessly,
but chase it into an obstacle!
And then...
the moment it changes direction,
I throw!
Then, once it's stopped,
I strike at the fastest speed I can muster!
An attack bonus from inertia...
It's a law of physics you take
for granted in the real world,
but very few games actually
try to replicate it.
Naturally, this game models
reality as close as it can!
That was spectacular, Sunraku-san!
I could hardly tell which
one was the monster!
Was that supposed to be a compliment?
Okay!
Even with the mark, I know I can take
out monsters that speed or slower.
I've verified what I needed to,
so here's the plan!
Ignore the scrubs!
Straight to the area boss!
That is all!
That wasn't much of a plan!
Now, as befits us speedsters,
let's get there speedily!
Away we go!
To the area boss, and Thirdrema beyond!
Yeah!
Um...
According to the map, the area
boss is around here, but...
It's swamp as far as the eye can see.
This will simply ruin my clothing...
Yeah, no, I think I get it.
With what Emul said on
the way here and all...
I was in such a hurry to get out of town,
I never got a chance to ask about the boss.
You know anything about it, Emul?
Well, it's a monster named Mud Digger!
It rockets out of the ground to attack,
so it's crucial to find a
way to hold it in place!
"Mud Digger"...
I gotta fight it in the swamp.
I might be in trouble here.
Sunraku-san, it's here!
Get on my shoulder!
Righty-o!
A characteristic of Shangri-La
Frontier's "swamp" terrain
is that it forces a "walking state."
One leg always remains trapped in the marsh
until the other foot reaches the bottom.
In other words...
This is my worst match-up possible!