A Trash Game Realignment of Elevated Tastes
Summer Break Promotion!!
Now Adding Servers!
Rumi Hizutome
Shangri-La Frontier Guide
Tour of Rabituza
* Respawn Point:
A location from which you can resume play.
Vorpal Soul Collar
acquired.
While equipped, user receives half EXP
but gains 2.5x stat points
(rounded down) when leveling.
BOP → BERP
Sunraku
Modor Katzo
* Vale tudo = "Anything goes" in Portuguese
The Seven Colossi
Sunraku's Picked Up SLF
From: Modor Katzo
to: Me
I hear Sunraku bought SLF.
He's pretty into it too.
Watch out for signs of hell freezing over.
TBF, I've been curious about it, too.
If he's playing it, it might be worth trying...
Arthur Pencilgon
Secondale - Back Alley
You've received a party request
from NPC "Magical Bunny Emul."
Accept?
No
Yes
You've received a party request
from NPC "Magical Bunny Emul."
Accept?
No
Yes
You've received a party request
from NPC "Magical Bunny Emul."
Accept?
No
Yes
NPC "Magical Bunny Emul"
has joined your party.
Emul
Sorcerer
Vorpal Bunny Traveler
Skill Points Remaining: 0
Cash on Hand:                                   0 Mahni
File Saved
Mud Digger
Area Boss
Rec. Party Size: 4