This world is filled with too many games to count...
though the vast majority simply come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of them all
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide.
It rightly earns the status of "god-tier", Shangri-La Frontier!
One lover of trash games, Hizutome Rakurou,
is trying out this very Triple-A!
What adventures await him there?
I've verified what I needed to, so here's the plan!
Ignore the scrubs!
Straight to the area boss!
That is all!
Hop on my shoulder!
Righty-o!
A characteristic of Shangri-La Frontier's "swamp" terrain...
is that it forces a player in a "walking state."
One leg always remains trapped in the marsh
until the other foot reaches the bottom.
In other words...
This is my worst match-up possible!
How am I gonna fight with the swamp
locking down my speed?
How does he dive into mud that shallow?
Well, I'll just chalk it up to game logic.
He's coming this way, Sunraku!
Oh, it's going to skin us alive!
What are you, the Hare of Inaba?
Hang on tight, Emul!
Righty-o!
Slide Move!
The EXP from my battle with Lycagon
evolved a bunch of my skills.
And if I'm gonna win this fight...
I'll figure out how to use them!
An evolution of Perfect Parry...
Repel Counter!
Truly impressive, Sunraku!
I just used some skills to get out of
a tight spot, but there's a problem.
Just seconds into the battle and I've already used
both the skills that seemed useful for damage evasion.
They'll be up again in 10.
I've got no way to avoid damage in the meantime.
What do I do?
Magic Edge!
Oh, I succeeded!
Hey, what was that? Magic?
Yes, indeed, it was!
Of course.
I'd been so focused on soloing this game,
I forgot I've got a partner.
Seems sorta iffy for a real gamer
to be relying on a stronger NPC.
But she gave me this opportunity, so I'm not gonna waste it!
Let's go, Emul!
We'll close the distance with Accel while it's still reeling!
Left! Right! Left! Right!
Almost! There!
But this freaking sucks!
And now...
The evolution of Screw Pierce...
Spiral Edge!
Let's keep going!
Edge Climb!
There!
Emul!
Yes?!
How about giving us a big boom?
I... I certainly shall!
Add Spell!
Hup! Hoi! Whoops!
I've played trash games with trickier platforming than this!
Go on and eat me if you can!
Too late. It's been ten seconds.
Repel Counter!
Here comes the big boom!
Power-Boost Magic Edge!
Hell yeah!
That was perfect, Emul!
Nice shot!
Oh, dear! My poor clothes!
That spell really packed a wallop.
It's gotta be—
Eh?
Wait, where'd he go?
What's with all the shaking?
It's like it's sucking my feet down. I can't move!
This is what I was telling you about!
It rockets out of the ground to attack,
so it's crucial to find a way to hold it in place!
Sunraku?!
It threw me into the air?!
I figured it'd be an insta-kill attack,
but it barely did any damage.
No, wait.
From this height...
The Mud Digger is a mole-like quadruped
with the head of a shark and the whiskers of a catfish.
Its most noteworthy trait is the special move set
that activates after its HP reaches a certain threshold.
It dives deep into the ground and vibrates
the swamp to hold players in place.
Then it randomly rams
one of them up in the air with its nose.
If a player challenges it alone,
not only will it hit them with this attack every time
as long as they remain in the swamp,
but it will almost inevitably shave down
all their HP through fall damage,
hence its nickname, The Solo Killer.
It's gonna kill me through fall damage?
And since the initial juggle attack didn't hurt much...
Whoever came up with this boss
has a real nasty personality!
Player skill isn't even a factor at this point!
What do I do?!
If Emul hit me from the side with her Magic Edge...
No, that'd just blow me up!
Magic, items... anything I can do?!
Nah, I'm done for.
I'm totally screwed.
I've never been able to get used
to falling deaths in VR games.
A feeling of electricity running through your body,
followed by a total loss of feeling...
The unnecessary pursuit of reality resulted
in some games being taken off the market.
Show your vorpal spirit!
There's an attack skill
that utilizes inertia called "Meteor Fall".
Sunraku had picked up a lot
of downward momentum from his free fall
at which point, Emul teleported him over the Mud Digger.
An attack that is normally deemed fatal to players,
was, in a slipshod way, recognized instead as a risky attack.
It was not a Meteor Fall,
but a Meteor Flub!
Did I seriously survive that?!
Splendidly done, Sunraku!
So many things happened all at once
that I'm having a hard time getting it all straight.
But either way, Emul...
You're simply splendid!
K-Kindly refrain from imitating my speech!
I had a pretty rough ride there,
just like my fight with Lycagon.
But this time, we survived!
Not even herbs'll get me back to max HP right away, huh?
You just shoved them down your throat!
It's the only way they reach my mouth.
Still, Emul was way stronger than I expected.
She ended up carrying me.
Feels pretty bad after how cocky I was...
Until I reach Emul's level,
I'll just put her to work as a mascot.
Might be the only way to stay motivated.
We'll arrive at Thirdrema soon!
And after we arrive,
you'll be staying in Rabituza full-time, yes?
I can hardly wait!
Yeah, but we've got a little problem.
How do I hide you once we get into town?
Drawing more attention like last time
might even get us jumped.
In that case...
Why, I haven't used it in so long!
Used what?
The secret treasure of the Vorpal Bunnies!
Sunraku, I must ask you to keep this between us!
Sure?
Metamorphose!
Surprised, are you?
This will allow us to inconspicuously enter the town!
Now, isn't that weird?
Here I thought I was playing Shangri-La Frontier...
with a tagline, "Explore the world, enjoy the world".
It was supposed to be Japan's premier Triple-A game.
Sunraku?
But this is...
This is starting to look like...
Sunraku!
Hey, hey!
Sunraku?
Sunraku!
...some kind of harem game with an anthro bunny girl!
Eh?
It's simply so exhausting.
I'll transform again once we near the town.
Four or five minutes is my limit in my current state.
Oh, I get it.
So once we're in town, you'll have
to undo it when no one's around.
But, Emil, you've severely miscalculated.
Yes, it's a truly fatal,
vorpal-class misunderstanding.
The minute you started hanging out
with a half-naked bird-man,
"inconspicuous" was thrown out the window.
Well, you'll just have to play
the hapless girl dragging along a streaker
with an animal's head for some reason.
Good luck!
My steps feel as heavy as if I were still in the marsh.
Oh, it's as large and lovely a town as I remember!
So that's Thirdrema, eh?
You seem curiously unimpressed, Sunraku!
Well, I'm not exactly a warrior guided by destiny,
but I've seen a few places in my time.
How truly spectacular!
You pioneers really are a well-traveled lot!
Okay, let's go, Emul!
Get ready to transform and make yourself inconspicuous!
Righty-o!
Hey, hang on a minute!
Why are you half-naked?
Were you beset by highwaymen?
Yep, knew it. All their attention's on me.
And what frightening marks you bear.
They're on his legs, too.
Wait just one moment now, Sir Guard!
This man has a past...
A past that would bring sorrow to all who hear it!
What?
Guided by destiny itself, he was reborn as a great warrior,
and challenged his destined rival
from his past and current life,
Lycagon, to a duel!
But by the narrowest of margins, by a mere hair's breadth,
by the smallest and simplest of fate's own whims,
he ended up inflicted by a curse instead!
Where'd you pull that story from?
But unable to escape his destiny,
he leaves himself to the currents of fate,
a solitary warrior on a wandering journey
to remove the curse that afflicts him!
That is he... Sunraku!
Hey, hang on!
You—
The tale of Super Warrior Sunraku
has only just entered its second season!
But—
Next episode is "Super Warrior Sunraku:
Where the Wind Blows, the Carrot Greens Waver"!
F-Fine, I get it.
It's unusual to see a half-naked pioneer,
but not completely unheard of.
You may pass.
Hey. That guy...
Yeah.
Did I just imagine it?
That wasn't the usual "what a weirdo" vibe.
Shall we, then, Sunraku?
S-Sure.
I recognize you.
You're Sunraku, right?
Um...
And who might you be again?
Wait!
Aw, I wanted to know how he tamed them!
I took a screenshot! Let's ask on the forums!
Great idea!
I bet the more advanced players know all about it!
Let's see...
"I have a question for our esteemed elders.
I was picking up equipment in Secondale
when I ran into this player.
He had the cutest talking bunny with him.
How can I befriend this monster?"
And post!
What's with this freak?
You could get arrested for a getup like that.
What does she mean, it talks?
Since when can monsters do that?
Wait one precious heart-stopping minute!
The game's only tame packs are buddy dogs and cats, right?
Is this a cheat?!
You didn't get permission for this screenshot, did you?
The guy sure doesn't look like he's consenting, at least.
P-Permission?
Is this not allowed?
I mean, it's a game...
Isn't everyone taking screenshots all the time?
Sunraku's his name, right?
I've got it.
And he's in Secondale?
I'm on my way now!
And what's with this tattoo skin?
I don't remember seeing a full-body pattern
like that in the character maker.
You mean to tell me this guy encountered Lycagon?
Lycagon's a random encounter,
so it's not unusual to hear of beginners running into it...
But how'd he end up with the curse?
Orcelott of Ashura Kai?
Ashura Kai?
That clan of player killers?
Is this Sunraku guy gonna be okay?
I'd love to meet and talk with him.
Mr. Sunraku, if you're reading this,
please speak to a player
wearing the wolf and sword emblem.
I'm sorry that so much of your info got leaked...
but we can help to protect you.
Lycagon's Mark, eh?
Psyger, huh?
And here come the achievement clans, joining in the fun.
Sunraku's got one hell of a spotlight on him.
He's being treated like an event boss himself.
Maybe I'll go look for him, too.
I just want an answer.
Tell me straight...
How do I tame a Vorpal Bunny?!
Please, don't play dumb with me.
I know you were with a talking Vorpal Bunny!
How'd that get out?
Was it when we were seen in Secondale?
What do I do?
Please!
No way am I spilling the beans on that unique scenario.
It's not like I know how I triggered it anyway.
I-I'm afraid I don't really...
It's not nice to keep things to yourself.
Everyone should share in the fun...
Revolutionary Knight Sunraku.
You've shown your face, Pencil Knight!
Hey, now.
That's no way to talk to a vixen...
like she's some kind of annoying monster.
Besides...
I don't have that username in SLF anymore.
Kindly call me Arthur Pencilgon.