This world is filled with
too many games to count,
though the vast majority simply
come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of all games
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide—
Shangri-La Frontier, which rightly
earns the title of "god-tier game"!
One lover of trash games, Rakuro Hizutome,
is trying out the god-tier
game, Shangri-La Frontier!
What adventures await him there?
I've verified what I needed to,
so here's the plan!
Ignore the scrubs!
Straight to the area boss!
That is all!
Get on my shoulder!
Righty-o!
A characteristic of Shangri-La
Frontier's "swamp" terrain
is that it forces a "walking state."
One leg always remains trapped in the marsh
until the other foot reaches the bottom.
In other words...
This is my worst match-up possible!
How am I gonna fight with the
swamp locking down my speed?
How does he dive into mud that shallow?
Well, I guess that's game logic for you...
He's on the way, Sunraku-san!
Oh, it's going to skin us alive!
What are you, the Hare of Inaba?
Hang on tight, Emul!
Righty-o!
Slide Move!
The EXP from the Lycagon battle
evolved a bunch of my skills.
Figuring out how to use them
will be the key to this battle!
An evolution of Perfect Parry...
Repel Counter!
Truly impressive, Sunraku-san!
I just used some skills to
get out of a tight spot.
I still haven't addressed the real challenge.
Just seconds into the battle and
I've already used both the skills that
seemed useful for damage evasion.
The recast time is ten seconds.
I've got no way to avoid
damage in the meantime.
What do I do?
Magic Edge!
Oh, I succeeded!
Hey, what was that? Magic?
Yes, indeed, it was!
Of course.
I'd been so focused on soloing this game,
I forgot I've got a partner.
Seems sorta iffy for a real gamer to
be relying on a stronger NPC, but...
She gave me this chance,
so I'm not gonna waste it!
Let's go, Emul!
Let's close the distance with
Accel while it's still reeling!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes! Yes!
This freaking sucks!
And now...
The evolution of Screw Pierce...
Spiral Edge!
Now, keeping up the pressure!
Edge Climb!
There!
Emul!
Yes?!
How about giving us a big boom?
I...
I certainly shall!
Add Spell!
Hup! Hoi! Whoops!
I've played trash games with
trickier platforming than this!
Go on and eat me if you can!
Too late. It's been ten seconds.
Repel Counter!
Here comes the big boom!
Power-Boost Magic Edge!
Hell yeah!
That was perfect, Emul!
Nice shot!
Oh, dear! My poor clothing!
That spell really packed a wallop.
It's gotta be—
Eh?
Where'd he get off to?
What's with all the shaking?
It's like it's sucking my
feet down. I can't move!
Sunraku-san, this is...
It rockets out of the ground to attack,
so it's crucial to find a
way to hold it in place!
Sunraku-san?!
It threw me into the air?!
I figured that'd be an insta-kill attack,
but it barely did any damage?
No, wait.
From this height...
The Mud Digger is a mole-like
quadruped with the
head of a shark and the
whiskers of a catfish.
Its most noteworthy trait is the special
move set that activates after its HP
reach a certain threshold.
It dives deep into the ground and vibrates
the swamp to hold players in place.
Then it randomly rams one of them
up in the air with its nose.
If a player challenges it alone,
not only will it hit them
with this attack every time
as long as they remain in the swamp,
but it will almost inevitably shave down
all their HP through fall damage,
hence its sobriquet—the "solo killer."
It's gonna kill me through falling damage?
And since the initial juggle
attack not doing much damage...
Whoever came up with this boss
has a real nasty personality!
Player skill's not even
a factor at this point!
What do I do?!
If Emul hit me from the
side with her Magic Edge...
No, that'd just blow me up!
Magic, items... anything I can do?!
Nah, I'm done for.
I'm totally screwed.
I've never been able to get used
to falling deaths in VR games.
A feeling of electricity
running through your body,
followed by a total loss of feeling...
The unnecessary pursuit of reality resulted
in some games to be taken off the market.
Show your vorpal spirit!
There's an attack skill called
"Meteor Fall" that utilizes downward energy.
Sunraku, had picked up a lot of
downward momentum from his free fall
at which point, Emul teleported
him over the Mud Digger.
An attack that might normally be deemed
a fall and result in player death,
was, in a slipshod way,
recognized instead as a risky attack.
It was not Meteor Fall,
but Mistake Meteor Fall!
Did I seriously survive that?!
Splendidly done, Sunraku-san!
So many things happened all at once,
I'm having a hard time
getting it all straight...
But either way, Emul...
You're simply splendid!
K-Kindly do not imitate my speech!
Just like with Lycagon,
I had a pretty rough ride there...
But we were the survivors this time!
Not even herbs'll get me back
to max HP right away, huh?
You shoved them down your throat!
That's the only way they reach my mouth.
Still, Emul was way stronger than I expected.
She ended up carrying me.
Feels pretty bad after how cocky I was...
Until I reach Emul's level,
I'll just put her to work as a mascot.
Might be the only way to stay motivated.
We'll arrive at Thirdrema soon!
And after we arrive, you'll be
staying in Rabituza full-time, yes?
I can hardly wait!
Yeah, but there's still a question.
How do I hide you once we get into town?
Drawing more attention like last
time might even get us jumped.
In that case...
Why, I haven't used it in so long!
Used what?
The secret treasure of the Vorpal Bunnies!
Sunraku-san, I must ask you
to keep this between us!
Sure?
Metamorphose!
Surprised, are you?
This will allow us to
inconspicuously enter the town!
Now, isn't that weird?
Here I thought I was playing
Japan's flagship god-tier game—
catchphrase, "Explore the
world, enjoy the world"—
Shangri-La Frontier.
Sunraku-san?
But this is...
This is starting to look like...
Sunraku-san!
Hey, hey!
Sunraku-san?
Sunraku-san!
...some kind of harem game
with an anthro bunny girl!
Eh?
It's simply so exhausting.
I'll transform again once we near the town.
Four or five minutes is my
limit in my current state.
Oh, I get it.
So once we're in town you'll have
to undo it once we're in private.
But, Emil, you have committed a fatal...
Yes, one truly fatal,
vorpal-class failure of understanding.
The minute you started hanging
out with a half-naked bird-man,
you maxed out your "conspicuous" stat.
Well, you'll just have to play
the hapless girl dragging along a
half-naked bird-man for some reason.
Good luck!
My steps feel as heavy as if
I were still in the marsh.
Oh, it's as large and lovely
a town as I remember!
So that's Thirdrema, eh?
You seem curiously unimpressed, Sunraku-san!
Well, I'm not exactly a
warrior guided by destiny,
but I've seen a few places in my time.
How truly spectacular!
You pioneers really are a well traveled lot!
Okay, let's go, Emul!
Get ready to transform and
make yourself inconspicuous!
Righty-o!
Hang on a minute!
Why are you half-naked?
Were you beset by highwaymen?
Yep, knew it.
I'm still the conspicuous one.
And what frightening marks you bear...
They're on his legs, too.
Wait just one moment now, Mr. Guard!
This man has a past...
A past that would bring
sorrow to all who hear it!
Guided by destiny itself,
he was reborn as a super warrior,
and challenged his destined rival
from his past life and this one,
Lycagon, to a duel!
But by the narrowest of margins,
by a mere hair's breadth,
by the smallest and simplest
of fate's own whims,
he ended up inflicted by a curse instead!
Where'd you pull that story from?
But unable to escape his destiny,
he leaves himself to the currents of fate,
a solitary warrior on a wandering journey
to remove the curse that afflicts him!
That is he... Sunraku-san!
Hey, hang on!
You—
The tale of Super Warrior Sunraku has
only just entered its second season!
But—
Next episode is "Super Warrior Sunraku—
Where the Wind Blows, Where
the Carrot Greens Waver"!
F-Fine, I get it.
It's unusual to see a half-naked pioneer,
but not completely unheard of.
You may pass.
Hey. That guy...
Yeah.
Did I just imagine it?
That wasn't the usual "what a weirdo" vibe...
Shall we, then, Sunraku-san?
S-Sure.
I recognize you.
You're Sunraku, right?
Um...
And who might you be again?
Wait!
Aw, I wanted to know how you tame them!
I got a screenshot!
Let's ask on the forums!
Great idea!
I bet the more advanced
players know all about it!
Let's see...
"I have a question for our esteemed elders.
I was picking up equipment in Secondale
when I ran into this player.
He had the cutest talking bunny with him.
How can I befriend this monster?"
And send!
What's with this freak?
You could get arrested for a getup like that.
What does she mean, it talks?
Since when do monsters talk?
"Wait one precious heart-stopping minute!
The game's only tame packs are
buddy dogs and buddy cats, right?
Is this a cheat?!"
You didn't get permission for
this screenshot, did you?
The guy sure doesn't look like
he's consenting, at least.
P-Permission?
Is this not allowed?
I mean, it's a game...
Isn't everyone taking
screenshots all the time?
Sunraku's his name, right?
I've got it.
Secondale, right?
I'm on my way now!
And what's with this tattoo skin?
I don't remember seeing a full-body
design like that in the character maker.
You mean to tell me
this guy encountered Lycagon?
Lycagon's a random encounter
so it's not unusual to hear of
beginners running into it...
But how'd he end up with the curse?
Orcelott of Ashura Kai?
Ashura Kai?
That clan of player killers?
Is this Sunraku guy gonna be okay?
I'd love to meet and talk with him.
Mr. Sunraku, if you're reading this,
please speak to a player wearing
the emblem of a wolf and a sword.
I'm sorry that so much of
your information got leaked,
but we can help to protect you.
Lycagon's Mark, eh?
Psyger, huh?
And here come the achievement clans.
Sunraku's got a hell of a spotlight on him.
He's being treated like
an event boss himself.
Maybe I'll go look for him, too.
I just want an answer.
Tell me straight...
How do I tame a Vorpal Bunny?!
Please, don't play dumb with me.
I know you were with a talking Vorpal Bunny!
How'd that get out?
Was it when we were seen in Secondale?
What do I do?
Please!
No way am I spilling the beans
on that unique scenario.
It's not like I know how
I triggered it anyway...
I-I'm afraid I don't really...
It's not nice to keep things to yourself.
Everyone should share in the fun...
Revolutionary Knight Sunraku-kun.
You've shown your face, Pencil Knight!
Hey, now.
Don't talk to a supreme beauty like me
like she's some annoying monster.
Besides...
in SLF, I'm not Pencil Knight.
Kindly call me Arthur Pencilgon.