Mud Digger
Area Boss
Rec. Party Size: 4
Lo, Thou Art Assailed on All Sides
Slide Move
Evades an attack with a gliding motion.
Repel Counter
Parries one incoming attack
and unleashes a counterattack.
Repel Counter
Slide Move
Accel
Grants a temporary bonus to
attack power and agility.
Spiral
Edge
Edge Climb
Stick a bladed weapon into
a vertical service to climb.
Add Spell
Repel Counter
Power-Boost Magic Edge
Sunraku
Fall Damage -8
Magic Scroll
Teleport
Energy
Meteor Fall
Mistake
Sunraku
Area Boss
Mud Digger
Dispatch Complete
Sunraku
Herbs used.
Mysterious Vorpal Bracelet
Thirdrema
Several Hours Earlier - Secondale
File Saved
[The Saint] Advanced Players Teach Beginners the Ropes  #81 [Cute]
74: Add (Advanced)
Seriously, to unlock the elite jobs you've got to at least make it to Sixburg.
How many times do I have to tell people this?
Maybe we should put it on the FAQ.
75: Alinoiyu (Beginner)
I have a question for our esteemed elders. I was picking up equipment
in Secondale when I ran into this player. He had the cutest talking bunny
with him. How can I befriend this monster?
76: Curry Jones (Advanced)
Is this a 'shop or something?
I mean I've never seen a talking Vorpal Bunny before
77: Exceed (Beginner)
What's with this dude lol half-naked with a mask,
call the cops plz lololol
Basashi Musashi (Advanced)
Our clan's leader ran into Siegwurm.
That one talks, apparently
Thundernut (Advanced)
I could see a unique monster talking, but a Vorpal Bunny...?
81: Animalia (Advanced)
Wait one precious heart-stopping minute!
The game's only tame packs are buddy dogs and
buddy cats for now, right? is this a cheat?!
82: Add (Advanced)
Yep, here come the furries. As I'd expect of the
leader of the animal-loving SF-Zoo clan. FYI this
game's admin cracks down hard on cheating
so it's unlikely to be that.
85: Thundernut (Advanced)
How would you feel if someone posted your face
up there without your knowledge or permission?
You've even got his name in the pic.
86: Super Alloy Tofu (Advanced)
Get some online etiquette already. This is reportable.
87: Alinoiyu (Beginner)
I really didn't know. I'm sorry...
89: Thundernut (Advanced)
The zookeeper moves fast! lol
You obsessives always find new ways of scaring me.
91: Add (Advanced)
I was trying to think of where I've seen this and
I just remembered. It's a curse. It prevents you
from equipping stuff onto the affected body parts
plus a bunch of other pros and cons.
It's proof that you're "acknowledged by the Night Emperor"...
at least, that's what some NPC said.
92: Basashi Musashi (Advanced)
The Night Emperor
Colossus
Lycagon the Nightslayer
94: Thundernut (Advanced)
The pupper's been sighted near Secondale, right?
95: Thundernut (Advanced)
Lycagon's a random encounter so it's not unusual
to hear of beginners running into it...
But how'd he end up with the curse?
96: Orcelott (Advanced)
I could spawn kill him until he tells us
97: Add (Advanced)
Oh? Well if it isn't Orcelott, esteemed leader
of Ashura Kai lol sup lol
I heard you got a bounty on your head and
even more NPCs are coming after you.
You got that all sorted? rofl
99: Add (Advanced)
If you PK too much and you get killed
by a player or an NPC all your items are lost,
including stored ones. Plus the bounty gets paid
from the PK's own cash. It's a pretty brutal system.
The Ashura Kai guys PK so much they can't go back.
They're a huge joke as far as I've seen.
100: Psyger-100 (Advanced)
I'd love to meet and talk with him. Mr. Sunraku, if you're reading this, please speak to a player wearing the emblem of a wolf and a sword.
I'm sorry that so much of your information got leaked, but we can help to protect you.
100: Psyger-100 (Advanced)
I'd love to meet and talk with him. Mr. Sunraku, if you're reading this, please speak to a player wearing the emblem of a wolf and a sword.
I'm sorry that so much of your information got leaked,
but we can help to protect you.
102: Basashi Musashi (Advanced)
Looks like this Sunraku guy's in a pretty unique situation.
And he might not even realize it himself...
Arthur Pencilgon