SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
Fifteenth Night in SLF
Mini!
SLF Theater
Why's it so tense?
Dadd—Boss.
Thank you for all you've done for me.
It appears this time has come at last.
I'll show you with everything I have!
The intensity of my vorpal soul!
Emul's on fire?
What's she going to do?
Go, go, go, go!
My vorpal soul is passionately raging!
You're pounding mochi for the
Fifteenth Night Festival?!
Simply scrumptious!
I'd like some kinako or soy sauce.
SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
Emul's Talks With Frogs
Mini!
SLF Theater
Ribbit.
Oh, I truly do empathize!
I have so many siblings myself,
both older and younger!
If I don't eat quickly, I'll find
my food snatched off my very plate!
It's simply a matter of perseverance!
Ribbit.
Yes, that's quite a challenge, isn't it?
One's personality is simply something
one picks up as life goes on.
That's what my brother, Aydward, tells me.
Even if now you're just one of many,
some day you'll find the special
place where only you can shine.
The key is to work patiently
on self-improvement.
That's what my daddy says.
Ribbit.
You believe you'll never amount to anything?
None of that, now!
You mustn't give up on your future.
It's not as if you were born in
your current form, after all.
At least, I assume...
That's right! Everyone is capable of change!
Don't give up, and you can
be whatever you wish to be!
That's what my daddy says!
What happens after you die?
That's a very difficult question indeed!
She couldn't follow a
word of what I told her,
but she goes on and on with the frogs...
And, I'm sorry, but a Mud Frog's a Mud
Frog no matter how it improves itself.
Or, wait... maybe they do evolve?