Crescent Vorpal
Sky Clear
The World Progresses, the Heroes Are Revealed
Sky clear = Clear as the sky
Unique Scenario EX
From the Living World, With Love
in progress
Setsuna's remnant has kept
the promise of bygone days.
Wethermon the Tombguard
has found eternal rest.
Unique Scenario EX
From the Living World, With Love
cleared
Progress: 11%
World Story
Progress:
Progress: 12%
World Story
Shangri-La Frontier
has progressed.
Clan: "The Library"
SLF game lore specialist clan
Schwarz Vulf Leader
Psyger-100
75: Alinoiyu (Beginner)
I have a question for our esteemed elders. I was picking up equipment
in Secondale when I ran into this player. He had the cutest talking bunny
with him. How can I befriend this monster?
Friend Warp
50 Seconds Later
Receiving Items
Highest Potion
Highest Magi-Potion
Highest Mixing Potion
Saint's Holy Water
Sticky Honey Ointment
Rebirth Tearjewel
Pirate's Wishjewel
Assassin's Black Hood
Assassin's Black Cloak
Assassin's Black Gauntlets
Assassin's Black Belt
Assassin's Black Trousers
Vital Piercing Blade
Demon Sword Vordigol
Demon Sword of the Butcher
Darkness-Shrouded Armor
Darkness-Shrouded Gauntlets
Emperor of Evil
Satan
Antinomy
God and Devil Greatsword
Karmic Embrace
Lightning Grace
Catastrophe
Highest Strength
Enchant Vermillion
Serial Killer
Silhouette's Sneer
Enchant Vorpal
Massacre Bite