SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
News: It's Morning, Indeed!
Mini!
Well, good morning, all!
I'm the peerless vorpal
bunny of Rabituza, Emul!
I'm going to tell you about all
the news I've seen and heard!
Horror! Undulating White Cloth Ghost!!
A ghost story so early in the morning?!
The Thirdrema urban legend,
the White Cloth Ghost, has been sighted!
It was seen jumping about on the
rooftops, its body undulating all over!
What a terrifying story!
It's so awful that we don't
know what it could be!
But there was a vorpal bunny who
spotted the White Cloth Ghost!
I got his story!
Horror! Undulating White Cloth Ghost!!
Oh, that was the thing I sold to that bird-man.
So I guess it had to be that bird-man...
Which means you had to be
there with him, right, Sis?
Oh? Well, I'd bet the bubbling
part would've been because
the bird-man was jumping and you
were under the cloth panicking—
There's no need to tell them all that!
We are experiencing technical difficulties
Hey! Sis, you hit me in the head!
Besides, I wasn't panicking!
Sunraku-san just said "It would be
faster to run along the rooftops"
and then he did a somersault, so I
was just trying to get my balance!
So it was you, Sis!
Vorpal Sister Punch! Indeed!
We had a little bit of white noise there.
The rabbit we spoke to is
no longer fit to be shown.
How come?!
Now, our next news item!
The Rabituza famed Vorpal Carrot Bumper Crop
Th-This is incredible!
We have a vorpal carrot bumper crop!
This is absolutely fabulous!
We have Sunraku-san on the scene right now!
We'll put you right through to him!
Sunraku-san! Sunraku-san!
How are things going over there?
Are the carrots looking wonderful?!
This is Sunraku on the scene.
Wh-What's going on over there?!
What? What was that?
What's going on over there?!
Well, as it happens, this Giga Armored
Death Carrot-Eater showed up...
Giga Armored Death Carrot-Eater?!
A Giga Armored Death Carrot-Eater
is attacking the carrot patch!
M-My carrots!
What's happening to my carrots?!
What's that?!
My carrots!
I don't give a crap!
I'm fighting the damn Giga Armored
Death Carrot-Eater right now!
Sounds like a Mongolian Death Worm to me!
I'll split you down the back
and make braised eel outta you!
I-I must take action!
My carrots...
I mean, the vorpal carrots must be
protected for the sake of all Rabituzans!
I must rush to the scene at once!
That's all for today!
Let us even meet again tomorrow!
What even is a Giga Armored
Death Carrot-Eater?!