Either on the Clear Sky Conquest action
or your oath to guard that
grave forever and ever!
On behalf of Vash, I'm putting you down!
Sky Clear!
Crescent Vorpal!
Go to sleep already...
Wethermon the Tombguard!
You were really strong...
But I've seen enough of your
attacks for a lifetime...
And your blade won't reach me ever again.
The ultimate strike has been solved.
Brilliant.
You have broken through my ultimate strike.
As "Clear Sky" transformed into
my ultimate, "Sky Clear"...
So, again, do the words transform...
to describe your talent.
"It is as clear as a cloudless sky."
Wait, was that a stupid pun?
Er, that just slipped out.
Setsuna said that to me often, as well.
I say it again. Your talent is clear.
Well done, descendant of the first pioneers.
I thought he was totally insensate,
but he actually reacted to me...
What, it's not over yet?!
No.
Into the gap between moments
spills a single wish
He's reached his limit.
Distant days, so blurred
by tears they can't be seen
I carry the light of your love in my heart
My body... fails.
I will sleep.
I'll remember it for eternity
Setsuna...
I'll be with you soon.
Hear me, my love, so far away
I-Is it over?
Looks like we haven't met
the clear conditions yet.
The cherry tree's dying?
The area's going back to normal, I guess?
Set-chan?
Arthur.
Sunraku.
Oikatzo.
You've done it, haven't you?
I can't thank you enough.
My wish...
No, the wish of the Setsuna
of the long-distant past
has been granted at long last.
That's a weird way of putting it...
You're making it sound like
you're not really Setsuna.
Set-chan?
You are Setsuna, aren't you?
Well, Arthur...
It's true that I am Setsuna.
But I'm not quite the
Setsuna who died that day.
Setsuna's wish...
"If my dearest love becomes
tied down by my death,
find a way to stop him."
I'm a remnant of her,
produced by those feelings.
Like a manuscript, perfectly replicated,
right down to the handwriting.
A remnant of the past, embodying the
real Setsuna's wish from long ago?
Like a copy-paste of herself or something?
That explains the whole "Setsuna
of Bygone Days," I guess...
I am a remnant of Setsuna.
I'm meant to disappear
once my role is fulfilled.
Wait! Set-chan!
Don't be sad, Arthur.
This was always going to happen,
once the world granted her wish.
You are pioneers,
the descendants of the Second Plan.
You exist to throw open this world.
If you wish to know of your roots...
of the truth of this world...
Seek out "Bahamut."
Bahamut?
Never heard of it, Katzo?
It's basically a big fish that
people treat like a dragon.
Yeah, I know what a freaking Bahamut is!
But what's it mean in the
context of this game?
There's no monster in SLF called
Bahamut, that I know of.
Set-chan, could you explain—
You should find that answer on your own.
That's what it means to throw
open the future, after all.
Arthur.
Let me speak to you now, not as Setsuna,
but as myself.
Thank you for always coming to see me.
I love you, Arthur.
Hey, likewise!
Pencilgon...
I'm not crying.
I didn't say anything yet.
Still, never knew you had a
"tears" function built in...
What is this feeling? Is this... a soul?
That's the second time you've made that joke!
Okay, I'm seriously gonna murder you two!
You can't PK me after all I've been through!
Take this one for the team, Sunraku!
Knock it off!
Just walk on up and take it!
Get off of me, loser!
Go on, get 'im!
Knock it off!
No! Go! You go!
We really managed to finish it.
Thanks for indulging me on this, you guys.
Hey, we just did it 'cause we wanted to.
Right?
The first dispatch of a unique monster
since Shangri-La Frontier started...
I can't wait to see what kind
of loot we've got waiting for us!
Yeah, yeah!
Okay, let's treat ourselves to a loot review!
This is an announcement to all
players of Shangri-La Frontier.
We have just confirmed
that the unique monster,
Wethermon the Tombguard, has been dispatched.
The players responsible for dispatching it
are Sunraku,
Oikatzo,
and Arthur Pencilgon.
Furthermore, with the dispatch
of this unique monster,
the world story of Shangri-La Frontier
has progressed.
World... story?
Royal Library, 2nd Collection
Hey! Big news!
Anyone got the professor's IRL contact info?
I'm pretty sure his wife is in Schwarz Vulf.
Ask her to fetch him!
You know the professor.
The minute he hears a unique
monster's been beaten,
he'll be here on the double.
I just hope his wife's logged in.
But what's the "world story" they
mentioned in the GM announcement?
Yeah, never heard that term before...
It's safe to assume it's different
from the regular story, right?
If the regular story usually involves
working with NPCs to explore the world,
the "world story" must mean the world
itself proceeding to a new stage, right?
If that's the case, we could
have some big changes in store!
You think we should ask
Schwarz Vulf to sniff around for us?
I think we should look into
Wethermon the Tombguard first.
I'm for that!
That's a unique monster that's been
totally unsubstantiated until now!
Siegwurm, Lycagon, Ctarnidd,
the Orchestra, and now Wethermon...
To think we'd get to fill in an unknown
Colossus after all this time...
That leaves just two unknowns left.
Okay, let's get in contact with the players
who took out Wethermon the Tombguard...
Hey, the professor's wife says she'll
wake him up and get him logged on!
Yes!
I feel bad that he had to be woken up...
Sunraku. Oikatzo. Arthur Pencilgon.
Good grief.
To think another set of players would
beat a unique monster before us...
And we call ourselves a top clan?
Arthur Pencilgon of the Ashura Kai, huh?
I thought it was odd that we
didn't see her during the raid.
I never dreamed she'd be off
slaying a unique monster.
Disgusting.
She funneled info on Ashura Kai
to us through a mediator
while she went after the unique monster...
She completely used us!
She might be even more troublesome
than Orcelott, who got away.
The other two aren't part
of Ashura Kai, are they?
I've never heard of this "Oikatzo" person,
but this player, Sunraku...
I believe he's the one
who tangled with Lycagon.
Pencilgon-san and Hizutome-kun...
are they close?
What should we do, Chief?
We've still got the journey
to the new land coming up...
We'll still be heading to the new land.
But I and a few others will remain here.
A beginner last seen in Thirdrema
did the unthinkable and
beat a unique monster?
I'm very interested in you
all of a sudden, Sunraku-kun!
I've gotta find a way to get
in contact with these guys!
Maybe we can even do some
laundering negotiations!
The chief seems to be enjoying this.
I was so sure she'd be upset.
Huh? Psyger-0's missing.
What happened there?
Said something about helping
a friend in trouble.
A friend?
Oh...
I do remember her saying she
managed to friend a guy she liked...
Well, I should probably support that.
Thought we'd run into you here.
Oh, is this the guy?
Y-Y-You people...
What was the name again?
Orcelott the Failhard?
Wow, what a wussy title.
Who's he think he is, Wethermon?
Oh, please! My loser little bro doesn't
need a fancy nickname like that.
He has no concept of the noble art of PKing.
He's an absolute hack with
delusions of grandeur.
I knew it...
You're the one who leaked
the location of our base!
Well, you reap what you sow.
You'd turned chicken, all fat and
comfortable and afraid of losing it all...
So I gave you a punch to the gut
to make you cough up the goods.
That's all.
Whoa!
The PK-talking lady is scary!
You think you know it all, huh?!
I bet you're tired out from
that Wethermon fight, huh?!
We're gonna murder you and
take all the loot you scored!
See? This is your big problem.
I'm always telling you to
focus on the big picture,
but you can't take your
eyes off immediate gains.
An anti-PK measure: the distress signal.
When attacked by a PKer, you can
send a call for aid to your friends.
Orcelott-san!
That's—
And if one of those friends
has the "Friend Warp" skill...
You can summon them right to the spot!
You again, Psyger-0?!
Sorry to be a big ol' bother, Psyger-0-san.
It's nothing.
Thank you so much for calling me!
The remnants of the Ashura Kai...
If you intend to run away, as
you've done once already...
I'll gladly let you go.
Will you accept?
You guys had better start
showing me respect...
You stupid pieces of shit!
D-Damn it...
Everything I built...
destroyed by you people...
You can't expect an MMO to
always go the way you want.
You'd be better off sticking
to offline single-player.
Personally, I recommend
Faeria Chronicle Online!
Jeez! What kind of monster are you?!
Hey, look at all these rare items
the Ashura Kai was packing!
Like they were trying to
skip town with the goods.
I didn't think you'd show up so quickly!
Thanks so much, Psyger-0-san!
R-Really, i-it was... nothing.
More importantly...
Congratulations... on dispatching
that unique monster!
Hey, thanks.
That's right. I guess that announcement
got the word out everywhere...
It's gonna be even harder
to walk around in public.
But what now?
After I called her out like this, I can't
just say, "Thanks a bunch, you can go now."
Wh-What's going on?
He's staring at me so intently...
Squee!
Hey, right, Psyger-0-chan.
You mind if I ask...
While you're here, would you mind killing me?
In exchange, how about
all the items I've got,
including two Rebirth Tearjewels
and all the rare items the
Ashura Kai was packing?
Hey, you sure about this?
Pretty sure the PKK penalty is
having all your items confiscated
and a big fine you gotta pay in
proportion to your crimes, right?
Knowing Pencilgon,
that'll probably be a pretty hefty fee.
I'd be an even bigger chicken than my
little bro if I never took any risks.
I'm pretty sick of PKing, anyway,
and this seemed like a good
time to wipe my slate clean.
Although... for now,
I'm still a player killer.
I'm not about to offer my
head up on a silver platter.
Psyger-0-chan...
Rather, Attack Master,
holder of unparalleled firepower...
I've always wanted to go all-out against you!
Very well. I'll take you on.
Satanael, reversal...
Satan!
The oft-spoken-of unique
weapon of the Attack Master,
Antinomy.
And you're even showing off the reversal...
How generous of you.
My siste—
Our chief told me about you.
You'll run at the drop of a hat,
so the moment I see you,
I should slay you swiftly,
with one decisive hit.
That's how people talk about cockroaches.
Huh?!
You guys are dead for sure.
I didn't even say anything yet!
If I'm fighting the Giant Killer,
I'm giving it everything I have!
In this corner, Psyger-0 just stacked
a bunch of scary-looking buffs
I don't know anything about!
Total demon king vibes.
Sup upon blood, tear away flesh.
Sink your teeth into death and reject life...
Thou art the butcher.
Let your song ring out from
atop a mountain of corpses!
And in this corner,
things are looking pretty grody!
Sheesh, her weapon's creeping me out.
Now, shall we begin?
Yes, let us...
Battle!
And they're off! It's a clash
between serious buff stacks!
How can you have so much
energy after that huge fight?
Massacre Bite!
Got you now!
My sword is stuck?!
Holy crap! Was that a direct hit?!
That was a close one...
I almost got myself cleaved in half.
After all that with Set-chan...
I've gotta put my whole heart into this!
In that case, just for you...
Light and darkness,
opposites in constant conflict
deny their mutual rejection
and weave together a severed destiny...
My body is bathed in light
and cloaked in darkness.
Let disorder devour this world!
Chaos Void!