The Walking Air Purifier
Ancient Craftsman
Legacy Weapon
Magic Operations Unit
Non-Standard Armament: Blade
Harbinger
Non-Standard Armament: Wire
Keep-Out Wire
Non-Standard Armament: Blade
Harbinger
Prismatic Forest Grotto
Fourfolkshire
Canyon of Ancient Souls
Eighthold
Eleventar
Ruins of Past Glories
The Lightless Barrens
Bonus Unique Scenario
Vorpal Epic
Items Needed
Receiver Delta
Positioner Delta
Transmitter Delta
Respawn point registered
Prismatic Forest Grotto
Fourfolkshire
Fourth City
Item Shop
Hexed
Reduces max HP and stats by a certain percentage
Fourfolkshire
Canyon of Ancient Souls
Wyvern Zombie
Rare Enemy
Dullahan General
Empire Bee Twinblades
equipped.
Vorpal Blade Tech
[Moon's Reflection] V3
Megaton Swing
Moon Jumper
Six-Boat Leap
Ignition
Hand of Fortune
Rabbit Gun
Titan Blast
Dropped Item
Dullahan General's Decapitator
Emul
Bilac
Bilac Lv: 98
Master Craftsman Sub: Archaeologist
Vorpal Bunny Master Smith
Skill Points Remaining: 0