This world is filled with
too many games to count,
though the vast majority simply
come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of all games
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide—
Shangri-La Frontier, which rightly
earns the title of "god-tier game"!
One lover of trash games, Rakuro Hizutome,
is trying out the god-tier
game, Shangri-La Frontier!
What adventures await him there?
Raising?
Growth?
That's it!
I just need to do some raising!
If there's no Ancient Craftsman around,
I just need to turn Bilac
into an Ancient Craftsman!
Me, an Ancient Craftsman?
You got it, bird-man.
I'll play along.
I'm gonna become an Ancient Craftsman!
Yay, Big Sis Bee!
Hell yeah!
Let's start the plan to cultivate Bilac!
Yes, indeed!
Y-Yeah!
So...
What exactly is the plan
to cultivate Big Sis Bee?
Huh? No clue.
Dumbass.
Well, what do you expect?
Listen up.
To be an Ancient Craftsman,
you gotta get two things.
And what are those?
The first is a remnant from
the Divinity, a Legacy Weapon.
A weapons craftsman can't forge crap
with just speculation and theory.
And the other, according to Pops...
is a marjik oppleration zoonit.
A "marjik oppleration zoonit"?
Are you trying to say
"magic operations unit"?
Yeah, maybe that's one way to say it.
Pretty sure that's the only way to say it!
Point is!
If I'm gonna be an Ancient Craftsman,
I gotta have a working Legacy Weapon
and a marjik oppleration zoonit!
Get it?!
Neither is gonna be easy to find!
A Legacy Weapon, huh?
That'd be a weapon from
the Divinity era, right?
Sunraku-san?
'Scuse me a minute.
Sunraku-san?!
Where'd that guy get off to?
Here we go.
A "Legacy Weapon" would be
something like this, right?
H-How'd you get your hands on this thing?!
Just a little something I
got for beating Wethermon.
That's a Legacy Weapon, all right...
But you need a working one, right?
I'm betting it won't gain "working" status
until I fix this Ether Reactor thing.
The reason I need a working Legacy Weapon
to make myself an Ancient Craftsman,
is so I can learn techniques
from the Divinity.
I just need something in good enough
shape for me to figure out how it works.
One in this good o' shape
oughta do me just fine!
Oh, great!
Okay, then...
Time to strip it down!
Hey, wait a second!
What now? I'm all ready to go, here!
Sorry...
I can't let you break it down without
consent from a few other people.
Yeah?
Yeah... this Legacy Weapon
came from the Inventoria.
Katzo and Pencilgon made it sound like the
weapons and armaments in the Inventoria
are shared between the three of us.
Which means we all share possession of it.
Fine.
Then I guess you better find the other thing
I need, the marjik oppleration zoonit.
Let's see...
Pops says you can find one
in the Ruins of Past Glories.
Hey, that's a pretty detailed map!
Lemme see!
Hey.
Okay... I'm departing out of Thirdrema, so...
I'll pass through the Prismatic Forest
Grotto to the fourth city, Fourfolkshire.
Then I'll pass through the Canyon of Ancient
Souls to the eighth city, Eighthold.
From there, halfway to
the 11th city, Eleventar,
is our destination,
the Ruins of Past Glories.
Looks like there's a lot of
path splits after Thirdrema.
It'll be a pretty straightforward
route, but it'll be a long way.
Wait, just past Eleventar...
The Lightless Barrens?!
Let's see... Items needed...
Receiver Delta, Positioner Delta,
Transmitter Delta...
I think I get the gist, but where do
I even start looking for these things?
Surely you're not going
to send me out blind...
Right.
Check out a place called
the Lightless Barrens.
That's the place Aniki Vash said
would have the items I need
for my bonus unique scenario!
Is this fate conspiring
to send me right to it?!
Hell yeah!
I'm super hype for this now!
Let's get moving!
Hang on a sec.
I gotta pack for the trip.
Oh, cool! Bilac's coming, too?
Though that does raise the question...
How do I get out of the city,
carting two rabbits around?
I can sort of hide Emul by wearing
her around my neck, but...
Maybe Bilac's gonna have to chug MP
recovery items to maintain a human form?
Oh, I can't transform into a human.
What, really? What do we do, then?
Well, I can't become a human, but...
Let's do this, Emul!
Righty-o!
Behold our powers of camouflage!
Yes, indeed!
You got yourself a perfect fur coat...
...and fashionable scarf.
Okay, whatever.
Okay! Let's head through Fourfolkshire
and on to the Canyon of Ancient Souls!
Get moving, bird-man!
Could you at least learn my name?
Yes, let us away!
First, though...
Gotta set my respawn point
in the Palace of Rabituza...
Respawn point registered.
Okay, let's move!
The Canyon of Ancient Souls.
The site of the last battle
in a war that occurred
before humanity was as advanced as it is now.
Ironically, the fighting had to be called
off due to the arrival of monsters,
but the large number of dead it produced
caused miasma to cover the land,
turning it into a nesting ground for
undead creatures who despise the living.
Even now, it remains a
grave danger to pioneers,
infested with undead and
curses... so they say.
Don't tell me what they say!
I told you to keep talk
to a bare minimum in town.
You'll be in it deep, without a cleric
or holy items to fend off that miasma.
Yeah, I know.
If you spend too much time in miasma
you end up with "Hexed" status, right?
That's why we ducked into this item shop.
I'm gonna get the items I
need, then blow this town.
Holy Water's pricey!
Although...
I might only need to buy anti-miasma
stuff for you two guys.
Okay, got it. So this is the
Canyon of Ancient Souls...
Just like you described it...
The air quality looks awful.
Hang on a sec.
How'd you get that aura
of clean air around you?
Noticed, did you?
It's the effect of the
mark Lycagon put on me!
Any spell or curse from a source weaker
than that dog gets canceled out!
It can even nullify miasma?!
That said...
That said...?
Sunraku-san! It's a Wyvern Zombie!
Dang, looks stinky.
D-Did that happen because of the mark, too?
Yep.
Anything lower level than me just runs away.
Too bad. I've got plenty of new
skills I'd love to test out...
Hey, Emul.
I think that major level-up
Wethermon handed me
might have left me a tad overpowered.
It does appear that way!
"Keep your hands off the
Night Emperor's prey," huh?
They're a buncha cowards, if you ask me.
Those Wyvern Zombies are so damn scared,
they even forgot they could fly.
Guess this might just be a
short stroll to the area boss.
Impressive as ever, Sunraku-san!
Still, it's kinda too bad.
I was hoping for a chance
to flex my skills, here.
Y'know, I forgot to check
out your stats, Bilac.
Are you even any good in a fight?
What'd you say?!
You saying I'm no good? Huh?!
I was kidding, I swear.
It didn't run from Sunraku-san on sight!
It must be a powerful foe!
That could be the case...
Or maybe he just can't see me.
He's got no head, see?
H-He's letting us attack first!
Maybe we can talk things out with the guy!
Yeah, right! A dullahan
don't even got a mouth!
Yeah, fair point.
He's readied his sword!
Okay...
Let's hunt a dullahan!
Sounds good to me.
Time to show off what I got!
Yeah! Looking forward to it, Bilac!
Yeah, Big Sis Bee!
I'm greatly looking forward to it!
Mimicking me!
Y-You just said what I
was going to, that's all!
Quit messing around. We've got incoming!
Here it comes!
Got it!
Ignition!
Time to try out my new skills!
You better handle your own
miasma countermeasures!
No worries there!
I-It isn't safe!
Keep your ears tucked, Emul!
If Lycagon's Mark didn't chase it off,
it must be a powerful opponent
with a higher level than me.
But somehow, I don't feel threatened at all.
Maybe it's because I already fought
the ultimate mounted warrior.
First, let's get you off that horse!
Okay, now!
Vorpal Blade Tech!
Moon's Reflection!
Version 3!
Watch yourself, buddy!
If you try to turn around
when you're off-balance...
A dead body's bound to be light.
Bet I can send you flying...
So get going, pal!
Megaton Swing!
Hey, nice hang time!
Impressive as ever, Big Sis Bee!
Don't let her show you up, Emul!
We need a follow-up! Get a spell ready!
I'll have Add Spell ready to go!
Moon Jumper...
Into...
Six-Boat Leap!
You wanna handle it yourself, eh?
Playing second fiddle to an NPC...
Any trash gamer needs to know when to do it.
Sounds good to me!
It's been thirty seconds.
Ignition oughta be warmed up by now.
Time to turn on the gas!
Ignition!
And with my luck in the
triple digits at last...
I'll pull out my luck-based attack skill...
Hand of Fortune!
And then...
I equip Emul to my arm!
I call this...
The Rabbit Gun!
Th-This is hardly appropriate treatment!
Fire, Emul!
Magic Edge!
Right on target!
Pretty weird way to fight,
but you put him right where I want him!
Hold your horses there, buddy!
I'm gonna return your master to ya.
Gotcha!
Titan Blast!
Now that was a big boom!
Big Sis Bee! You're so awesome!
Heck yeah!
Yeah, that's about right.
"Dullahan General's Decapitator," huh?
Let's see...
"Attacks to the head deal bonus damage."
"A longsword that likely once held
great power, now rusted badly.
It can only cleave flesh
through brute force alone."
Aw, it's all rusty.
The edge looks lousy, too.
"The corpse which had already
lost its memories, its pride,
and its love, even lost its head."
"This is why the remaining
torso targets the heads
of not just the living, but also the dead."
An "If I can't have my head,
neither can any of you" sort of deal?
Misery really does love company, I guess...
Guess I'll sell it off.
Mind if I take a look at it?
Oh, sure.
This sword's still got some life in it.
I'll restore it to its former glory later.
Hey, right. You're a blacksmith and all.
I forgot for a second there.
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?!
Level... 98?
Pretty strong...
And right after I finally outlevel Emul...
That's experience I earned from smithing.
You've got more experience fighting, for sure.
If you socked me in the face,
you'd probably break my neck.
Hey! Just what's that supposed to mean?!
Silence is golden, as they say.
As they say.
Emul.
You're starting to take after bird-man here.
Okay, let's go!
We gotta get to that boss, lickety-split!
We'll need that magic operations unit to
make you an Ancient Craftsman, right, Bilac?
Though I gotta say, the map here
seems way more simple than the
other areas I've been to...
Nevertheless, we need only to
proceed in a straight line!
Yeah, it's easy-peasy!