We live in a world filled with countless games...
though the vast majority simply come and go in obscurity.
What's considered the best of the best
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide.
It rightly earns the status of "god-tier," Shangri-La Frontier!
One lover of trash games, Hizutome Rakurou,
is trying out this very Triple-A!
What adventures await him there?
Raising?
Growth?
That's it!
I just need to do some "raising"!
If there's no Ancient Craftsman around,
I just need to turn Bilac into one!
Me, an Ancient Craftsman?
You got it, bird-man.
I'll play along.
I'm gonna become an Ancient Craftsman!
Yay, that's my big sis!
Hell yeah!
Let's start the plan to level up Bilac!
Yes, indeed!
Y-Yeah!
So...
what exactly is the plan to help Big Sis Bee level up?
Huh? No clue.
Dumbass.
Well, what do you expect?
Listen up.
To be an Ancient Craftsman, you gotta get two things.
And those are?
The first is a remnant from the Divinity, a Legacy Weapon.
A weapons craftsman can't forge crap
with just speculation and theory.
And the other, according to Pops...
is a marjik oppleration zoonit.
A "marjik oppleration zoonit"?
Are you trying to say a "magic operations unit"?
Yeah, maybe that's one way to say it.
Pretty sure it's the only way to say it!
Point is!
If I'm gonna be an Ancient Craftsman,
I gotta have a working Legacy Weapon
and a marjik oppleration zoonit!
Get it now?!
Neither one's gonna be easy to find!
A Legacy Weapon, huh?
That'd be from the Divinity era, right?
Sunraku?
'Scuse me a minute.
Sunraku?!
Where'd the guy go?
Here we go.
A "Legacy Weapon" would be something like this, right?
H-How'd you get your hands on this thing?!
Just a little something I got for beating Wethermon.
That's a Legacy Weapon, all right.
But didn't you say you needed a working one?
I'm betting it won't gain "working" status...
until I fix this Ether Reactor thing.
The reason I need a working Legacy Weapon
to make myself an Ancient Craftsman...
is so I can learn Divinity-era techniques.
I just need something in good enough shape
for me to figure out how it works.
And this one right here oughta do me just fine!
Oh, great!
Okay, then...
Time to strip it down!
Hey, wait a second!
What now? I'm all ready to go, here!
Sorry...
I can't let you break it down
without consent from a few other people.
Yeah?
Yeah... this Legacy Weapon came from the Inventoria.
Katzo and Pencilgon made it sound like
all the weapons and armaments I saw
were shared between the three of us.
Which means we all own it.
Fine.
Then I guess you better find the other thing I need,
the marjik oppleration zoonit.
Let's see...
Pops says you can find one in the Ruins of Past Glories.
Hey, that's a pretty detailed map!
Lemme see!
Hey.
Okay... I'm starting from Thirdrema, so...
I'll pass through the Prismatic Forest Grotto
to the fourth city, Fourfolkshire.
Then I'll pass through the Canyon of Ancient Souls
to the eighth city, Eighthold.
From there, halfway to the eleventh city, Eleventar,
is our destination, the Ruins of Past Glories.
Looks like there's a lot of split paths after Thirdrema.
It'll be a pretty straightforward route, but it'll be a long way.
Wait, just past Eleventar...
The Lightless Barrens?!
Let's see... Items needed...
Receiver Delta, Positioner Delta, Transmitter Delta...
I think I get the gist, but where do I even start
looking for these things?
Surely you're not going to send me out blind...
Right.
Check out a place called the Lightless Barrens.
That's the place Don Vash said would have the items
I need for my bonus unique scenario!
Is this fate conspiring to send me right to it?!
Hell yeah!
I'm super hype for this now!
Let's get moving!
Hang on a sec.
I gotta pack for the trip.
Oh, cool! Bilac's coming, too?
Though that does raise the question...
How do I get out of the city, carting two rabbits around?
I can sort of hide Emul by wearing her around my neck.
Maybe Bilac's gonna have to chug
MP recovery items to maintain human form?
Oh, I can't do any of that.
What, really? What do we do, then?
Well, I can't turn into human, but...
Let's do this, Emul!
Righty-o!
Behold our powers of camouflage!
Yes, indeed!
You got yourself a perfect fur coat...
...and a fashionable scarf.
Fine, whatever.
Okay! Let's head through Fourfolkshire
and on to the Canyon of Ancient Souls!
Get moving, bird-man!
You do know I have a name, right?
Yes, let us away!
First, though...
Gotta set my respawn point in the Rabituza Palace.
Respawn point has been registered.
Okay, let's move!
The Canyon of Ancient Souls.
The site of the last battle in a war that occurred
before humanity was as advanced as it is now.
Ironically, the fighting had to be called off
due to the arrival of monsters,
but the large number of dead it produced
caused miasma to cover the land,
turning it into a nesting ground
for undead creatures who despise the living.
Even now, it remains a grave danger to pioneers,
infested with undead and curses... so they say.
I never asked for the lore!
I told you to keep talk
to a bare minimum while we're in town.
You'll be in it deep without a cleric
or holy items to fend off that miasma.
Yeah, I know.
If you spend too much time in that stuff,
you end up with a "Hexed" status, right?
That's why we ducked into this item shop.
I'm gonna get the things I need, then blow this town.
Holy Water's pricey!
Although, I might only need to buy
anti-miasma stuff for the two of you.
You can really tell, this is the Canyon of Ancient Souls.
Just like how you described it,
the air quality looks awful.
Hang on a sec.
How'd you get that aura of clean air around you?
Noticed, did you?
It's the effect of the mark Lycagon put on me!
Any spell or curse from a source weaker than
that dog gets canceled out!
It can even nullify miasma?!
That said...
What?
Sunraku! It's a Wyvern Zombie!
Dang, looks stinky.
D-Did that happen because of the mark, too?
Yep. Anything lower level than me just runs away.
Too bad. I've got plenty of new skills I'd love to test out.
Hey, Emul.
I think that major level-up after the Wethermon fight
might have left me a tad overpowered.
It does appear that way!
"Keep your hands off the Night Emperor's prey," huh?
They're a buncha cowards, if you ask me.
Those Wyvern Zombies are so damn scared,
they even forgot they could fly.
Guess this might just be a short stroll to the area boss.
Impressive as ever, Sunraku!
Still, it's kinda too bad.
I was hoping for a chance to flex my skills, here.
Y'know, I forgot to check out your stats, Bilac.
Are you even any good in a fight?
What'd you say?!
You saying I'm no good? Huh?!
I was kidding, I swear.
It didn't run from Sunraku on sight!
It must be a powerful foe!
That could be the case,
or maybe he just can't see me.
Since his head's gone.
H-He's letting us attack first.
Maybe we can talk things out with the guy!
Yeah, right! A dullahan don't even got a mouth!
Yeah, fair point.
He's readied his sword!
Okay...
Let's hunt a dullahan!
Sounds good to me.
Time to show off what I got!
Yeah! Looking forward to it, Bilac!
Yeah, Big Sis Bee!
I'm greatly looking forward to it!
Mimicking me now?
Y-You just said what I was going to, that's all!
Quit messing around. We've got incoming!
Here it comes!
Got it!
Ignition!
Time to try out my new skills!
You better handle your own miasma countermeasures!
No worries there!
I-It isn't safe!
Keep your ears tucked, Emul!
If Lycagon's Mark didn't chase it off,
it must be a powerful opponent with a higher level than me.
But somehow, I don't feel threatened at all.
Maybe it's because I already fought
the ultimate mounted warrior.
First, let's get you off that horse!
Okay, now!
Vorpal Blade Tech!
Moon's Reflection, Version 3!
Watch yourself, buddy!
If you try to turn around when you're off-balance...
A dead body's bound to be light.
Bet I can send you flying...
so get going, pal!
Megaton Swing!
Hey, nice hang time!
Impressive as ever, Big Sis Bee!
Don't let her show you up, Emul!
We need a follow-up! Get a spell ready!
I'll have Add Spell ready to go!
Moon Jumper...
into...
Six-Boat Leap!
You wanna handle it yourself, eh?
Playing second fiddle to an NPC...
Any trash gamer needs to know when to do it.
Sounds good to me!
It's been thirty seconds.
Ignition oughta be primed and ready.
Time to turn on the gas!
Ignition!
And with my luck in the triple digits at last...
I'll pull out my luck-based attack skill...
Hand of Fortune!
And then...
I equip Emul to my arm!
I call this...
The Rabbit Gun!
Th-This is hardly appropriate treatment!
Fire, Emul!
Magic Edge!
Right on target!
Pretty weird way to fight...
but you put him right where I want him!
Hold your horses there, buddy!
I'm gonna give your master back to ya.
Gotcha!
Titan Blast!
Now that was a big boom!
Big Sis Bee! You're so awesome!
Heck yeah!
Yeah, that's about right.
"Dullahan General's Decapitator," huh?
Let's see...
"Attacks to the head deal bonus damage."
"A longsword that likely once held
great power, now rusted badly.
It can only cleave flesh through brute force alone."
Aw, it's all rusty. The edge looks lousy, too.
"The corpse which had already lost its memories,
its pride, and its love, even lost its head."
"This is why the remaining torso targets the heads
of not just the living, but also the dead."
An "If I can't have my head,
neither can any of you" sort of deal?
Misery really does love company, I guess.
I'll probably sell it off.
Mind if I take a look at it?
Oh, sure.
This sword's still got some life in it.
I'll restore it to its former glory later.
Hey, right. You're a blacksmith and all.
I forgot for a second there.
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?!
Level... 98?
Pretty strong...
And right after I finally outleveled Emul...
That's experience I earned from smithing.
You've got more from fighting, for sure.
If you socked me in the face, you'd probably break my neck.
Hey! Just what's that supposed to mean?!
Silence is golden, as they say.
As they say.
Emul.
You're starting to take after bird-man here.
Okay, let's go!
We gotta get to that boss, lickety-split!
We'll need that magic operations unit to make you
an Ancient Craftsman, right, Bilac?
Though I gotta say, the map here seems
way more simple than the other areas I've been to.
Nevertheless, we need only to proceed in a straight line!
Yeah, it's easy-peasy!