SLF Theater!
SLF Mini
I Reincarnated Into a Trash Game?!
Mini!
Sunraku!
Open your eyes!
Sunraku, you have been
reincarnated in another world.
Um?
The trash game world!
You must defeat the Demon King!
Aren't you gonna move at all, Goddess?!
And thus, my brutal isekai
reincarnation began.
The enemies' levels were
too high from the start.
What the hell? Huh? Huh?!
I slipped halfway through the wall!
I was constantly getting trapped
in the game's geometry.
Sunraku, leave this to me! Go on ahead!
Go on ahe— ea— ea— ea—
Okay, that's freaky!
Your head, man! Your head!
My allies couldn't maintain
a fully human form.
Wait. This is an isekai, right?
Is it, really?
But I overcame all challenges and
at last arrived at the Demon King!
Okay, dude!
I've been through hell and back!
I'm gonna murder your ass!
Congratulations on making
it this far, great hero!
But I am the Demon—
Lag isn't a game issue,
it's a user connection issue!
And that's when I woke up.
Nothing like remembering how reality works
to wake you up from a dream, right?
I don't even know what to say to all of that.