This world is filled with
too many games to count,
though the vast majority simply
come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of all games
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide—
Shangri-La Frontier, which rightly
earns the title of "god-tier game"!
One lover of trash games, Rakuro Hizutome,
is trying out the god-tier
game, Shangri-La Frontier!
What adventures await him there?
Hey, Sunraku's back.
Who's that he's fighting?
Never seen him before.
No way it's a new player, right?
Hard to believe, but I think it might be!
I'll take at least one round!
Quickdraw Fist!
You lose!
Wh-Why can't I take a
single round against you?!
The Quickdraw Fist style
is basically unbeatable.
One more match! This'll be the last one!
Best of three!
If you insist.
But this'll be the last one.
Thank you so much!
And the rules are, of course...
Bug tudo!
Yes!
Battle start!
Round 1!
Fight!
Same approach again?
Hey!
You learned to time the Yo-Yo
to your opponent's attacks?
Yes! I think I'm getting the hang of it!
Still, I meant to come train
myself for the Wethermon fight,
but I basically ended up
training some newbie...
I really wish I could've landed
some stronger competition...
Flying Smash!
He closed in with the retraction
of his elongated leg,
and attacked simultaneously!
That's some seriously impressive improvement.
But...
your choice of Flying Smash,
which isn't a bug technique,
shows just how little you
understand about BERP.
Flying Smash may be a powerful move,
but it leaves you with a wicked recovery time.
Makes it hard to deal out a
follow-up, even when you land it.
The correct move is...
Pile Bunker!
H-He's so fast!
If I can't get away, then...
Still charging in headlong?!
I'll just counter with a Quickdraw Fist!
What's he doing?!
Flying Smash!
He triggered two Flying Smashes at once?!
I've never seen that happen!
A Quickdraw Fist could
probably counter it, but...
I think I'll let it hit me!
You win!
I did it!
I took my first round!
What just happened?
Did he stack Flying Smashes?
Yeah. I've never seen that happen before.
Well, what do you guys think?
Both of 'em had hitboxes for sure.
Fundamentally, it's a Pile Bunker...
But that shouldn't let you stack gauge moves.
It must be a form of the
Doppelganger bug, right?
That's never let you form a double
in the same coordinates, though.
That much has been verified.
And you can't use a Chimera
from a Doppelganger.
Which means...
Yeah.
If the test team can
reproduce it, it's a lock.
Dragonfly-san.
Y-Yes?
Congratulations.
It's not quite official yet,
but you're probably the discoverer
of a new bugged-out move!
Congratulations!
Wonderful!
Bravo!
Congrats!
H-Hey, thanks!
The discoverer of the bug
move usually gets to name it.
So, what you got?
O-Oh, this is all too sudden...
Um... a name for the move?
Let's see...
You don't have to choose right away.
Take some time and think about it.
Besides, we've still got
rounds to play, right?
In exchange for showing me a
new bug, I'll show you one, too.
You mean it?!
It's a pretty crazy bug
that can only be activated
the instant the round starts, though.
Battle start!
Round two!
Fight!
Doppelganger achieved.
Sunraku-san split in two?!
I waffled on what to name this one
when I first discovered it, too.
Shadow Clones? Swampman?
Amazing, right?
You think you've got it all figured out,
but there's always new things
to learn in this game!
That's why, no matter
how deserted it becomes,
I've always gotta drop in from time to time.
That's the joy of BERP...
Berserk Online Passion!
You okay?
Two quick losses in a row...
Having one clone hold me in place while
the other one attacks isn't fair!
Yeah, it's not fair how the clone ends
up controlled by the AI if you let it.
Thank you so much for giving up
your time to a new player like me!
No prob.
I've learned so much today.
I'm going to think up a cool
name for my own bug move, too!
Oh...
Speaking of, there's one really
creepy bug a friend of mine found.
Not sure if I can pull it off,
but you wanna find out?
Yes, please!
Okay!
Meanwhile...
This "friend" of his was...
Damn it! Why do I gotta stay
behind here by myself?!
What, you're still just Level 47?
Instead of tuna, you should
put "minnow" in your name!
Sunraku, get back here already!
You small fry!
And, boom!
Hell yeah!
Time for another dedicated day of SLF!
Oh, do wait for me!
We're gonna try out that skill combo
stuff Katzo told us about, Emul!
R-Righty-o!
So, this the right way?
You went off running without even
knowing where the Skill Garden is?!
Still, Sunraku-san,
you appear quite motivated today!
Last night at bedtime,
you seemed so exhausted!
It had me so worried!
I really was tired, yeah.
But discovering new things
can't help but get me excited!
Especially when it's something
I can get really into!
W-Wait, please!
The Skill Garden is this way!
Turn left down this passage!
Still, there's one of these Skill Garden
places in the Palace of Rabituza, too?
But of course!
And the Skill Garden in the
Palace of Rabituza contains
a far greater selection
than the ones in the towns!
We'll just keep that between us!
A secret advantage? I like it.
Oh, welcome!
Gracious me! If it isn't Emul
and her bird-man friend.
I'm never escaping this "bird-man" rap, am I?
This is my big sister, Elke.
We're actually two of a set of triplets!
Such a pleasure!
A pleasure.
Well, she's got the lop ears.
I guess I see the resemblance.
And if they're triplets,
that means there's a third.
Well? How may I help you?
I heard you can combine skills here, so...
Oh, I certainly can!
As it happens, I'm very
good at that sort of thing,
so Father put me in charge of
it... and that's why I'm here.
Did he, now?
He's picked up my sister's speech pattern!
Well, then, if you'd be so kind,
I'd be ever-so-happy if you'd
help me combine my skills...
Oh, but of course!
I jumped levels pretty quick,
so they've really piled up.
A bunch of 'em have changed, too.
Just so you know,
combining high-level skills with each other
does tend to produce superior
skills in the end...
Oh, yeah?
When you put it that way, it kinda
makes me wanna max them out first...
But I'm also trying to clean house a bit...
So, let's get combining.
Oh, yes, let's!
There we go!
Is that all the skills I
can combine for now, then?
And this is the recipe you want?
Six combinations will cost you 6000 mahni.
Sure thing.
Six thousand...
You sit tight, now. I'll have it right out!
Oh, if you please!
Stop mimicking me!
I'll take a minute to
double-check my stats, then.
Though I'm Level 51 now,
I had to stat up to equip my Moonblades,
so I never got to increase my VIT...
My defenses are still paper-thin.
No... make that tissue-paper-thin.
Well, here you are!
Wow, that really was fast!
It's all ready for you!
It's six combinations at once,
so the amount is quite copious...
but the moment you drink it all down,
you'll learn the combined skills instantly.
I've gotta chug this whole foul brew?
There's a freaking branch in it!
Go on! All at once, now!
I'd never do this if it weren't a game.
Go on, all at once!
Go on!
Wow, I learned 'em all at once!
That's six new skills from the ones I linked!
Plus nine I learned or that
changed while I leveled up...
I hope at least some of 'em are powerful.
Congratulations to you!
Isn't it lovely?
Oh, that's right. If you'd like...
There are Skill Grimoires you can
acquire only here in Rabituza.
Would you like to buy one?
Skill Grimoires?
And as my sister is so very fond of you...
I'll give you a discount.
You mean it? Awesome!
Do be cautious, Sunraku-san!
Despite appearances, Big Sister
Elke is quite a moneygru—
Wow, I can tell you're related!
Your sister's fast, too.
Don't sweat it, Emul.
When it comes to merch you can only
buy in special areas like this,
I'm always prepared to pay some high prices.
What a wise bird-man you are!
If I might ask, how much
do you have to spend?
I've been having a fire
sale on materials lately,
so I've got about 80,000 mahni on-hand.
Gracious me!
You could easily afford these, then.
They're so expensive!
And this is with the discount?
Are you sure you got this right?
Hang on... are you ripping me off?
Well, what do you say?
Surely you're not such a fool as to
let this special offer go, are you?
Th-Then...
I'll take the Vorpal Blade Tech...
Moon's Reflection... if you please.
Why, thank you!
That'll be 80,000 mahni!
Thank you so much for your business!
I just couldn't say no.
Sunraku-san, are you all right?
I thought she was gonna tear
the feathers off my head.
Why, Big Sister Elke would never...
Actually, she might.
I wanted to buy that waist
armor in Thirdrema, too...
I'll have to make some more money
before the Wethermon fight.
Hey, what time is it?
Whoa, just in time!
Who knows what they'd do to me
if I was late to another meeting?
Emul, open a gate!
Righty-o!
A fine evening to you.
Oh, Sunraku-kun.
You're actually on time for once.
You have a good day or something?
I wouldn't say that, exactly...
But I've made up my mind.
About what?
Regarding our fight against Wethermon
the Tombguard in two weeks...
There's just one problem.
Problem?
What is it? We're both over level 50 now.
Currently, the only ones who know
the conditions to meet Wethermon
are my clan, the Ashura Kai.
They've been using the
unique monster system—
the fact that you get experience
just for encountering them—
to level up and build their PVP skills.
Ashura Kai?
Those guys, huh?
Unlike Lycagon, you can always meet
him in a given time and place.
Must be pretty ideal for grinding, huh?
So the issue is...
On the night of the new moon,
when we fight Wethermon,
we'll end up at odds with the
members of the Ashura Kai
who've already accepted the
unique scenario. Right?
Yes.
But aren't you part of their clan?
Can't you work together or something?
Like... ask them to stand down this month?
Not a chance.
They're actively opposed
to defeating Wethermon.
I'm not sure I see where
you're going with this.
What exactly is it you've
"made up your mind" about?
The Ashura Kai...
are universally hated for
their player-killing habits.
I'll bet, yeah.
And there was recently an
update that gives players
who've done PKing a special sort of status.
A special status?
If a player kills a PKer,
in addition to a bounty,
they earn the right to any items and
equipment the PKer was carrying.
All of it—including stuff
they've got in storage.
Oh?
High-level PKers like the Ashura Kai tend
to end up with some pretty rare items.
Which makes PKers like us basically
walking treasure chests.
It's created a new class
of player—the PK Killer.
Of course, we've found loopholes
in the system to reduce the
damage they can do to us,
but someone could get around all
of that by attacking our hideout.
Your hideout?
Hang on. So the thing you
made up your mind about...
You mean...
That's right.
Naturally, I know just where that hideout is.
And that gang of cowards is just
a thorn in my side at this point.
So...
I was thinking we'd go squash the Ashura Kai.
The fully immersive VR game,
Shangri-La Frontier...
Its major summer update has finally arrived.
Yes. And on the night of this major update,
Sunraku and his party will take
on Wethermon the Tombguard.