SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
Various New Years
Mini!
SLF Theater
A most blessed New Year to you.
I am indebted for all your
help in the previous year.
I hope to continue our amicable relationship.
I hope for amicable relations,
as well. Yes, indeed!
Pony up, Sunraku-kun.
Pony up?
My New Year's gift.
Like hell!
Stingy.
You, then?
That's not happening.
But you have a job!
You have a job, too, don't you?!
Don't play dumb!
Sunraku-san! Sunraku-san!
What might a "New Year's gift" be?
Oh, it's kinda like...
This.
A New Year's gift!
It's better than I could have dreamed!
So easy to please.
I couldn't muster up the courage to
send Hizutome-kun a New Year's card!
Happy New Year to you!