We live in a world filled with countless games...
though the vast majority simply come and go in obscurity.
What's considered the best of the best
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide.
It rightly earns the status of "god-tier," Shangri-La Frontier!
One lover of trash games, Hizutome Rakurou,
is trying out this very Triple-A!
What adventures await him there?
Hey, Sunraku's back.
Who's that he's fighting?
Never seen him before.
No way it's a new player, right?
Hard to believe, but I think it might be!
I'll take at least one round!
Quickdraw Fist!
You lose!
Wh-Why can't I win just one round against you?!
The Quickdraw Fist style is basically unbeatable.
One more match! This'll be the last one!
Best out of three!
If you insist, but this is it.
Thank you so much!
And the rules are, of course...
Bug tudo!
Yes!
Battle start!
Round 1!
Fight!
The same tactic, huh?
Hey!
You learned to time the Yo-Yo to your opponent's attacks?
Yes! I think I'm getting the hang of it!
Still, I meant to come train myself for the Wethermon fight,
but I basically ended up training some newbie...
I really wish I could've landed some stronger competition.
Flying Smash!
He closed in with the retraction of his elongated leg,
and attacked simultaneously!
That's some seriously impressive improvement.
But...
your choice of Flying Smash, which isn't a bug technique,
shows just how little you understand BERP.
That skill may be a powerful move,
but it leaves you with a wicked recovery time.
Makes it hard to deal out a follow-up,
even when you land it.
The correct move is...
Pile Bunker!
H-He's so fast!
If I can't get away, then...
Still charging in headlong?!
I'll just counter with a Quickdraw Fist!
What's he doing?!
Flying Smash!
He triggered two Flying Smashes at once?!
That's a first!
A Quickdraw Fist could probably counter it, but...
I think I'll let it hit me!
You win!
I did it!
I won my first round!
What just happened?
Did he stack Flying Smashes?
Yeah. I've never seen that happen before.
Well, what do you guys think?
Both of 'em had hitboxes for sure.
Fundamentally, it's a Pile Bunker.
But that shouldn't let you stack gauge moves.
It must be a form of the Doppelganger bug, right?
That's never let you form a double
in the same coordinates, though.
That much has been verified.
And you can't use a Chimera from a Doppelganger.
Which means...
Yeah.
If the test team can reproduce it, it's a lock.
Dragonfly.
Y-Yes?
Congratulations.
It's not quite official yet,
but you've probably discovered a new bugged-out move!
Congratulations!
Wonderful!
Bravo!
Congrats!
H-Hey, thanks!
The discoverer of the move usually gets to name it.
So, what you got?
O-Oh, this is all too sudden...
Um... a name for the move?
Let's see...
You don't have to choose right away.
Take some time and think about it.
Besides, we've still got rounds to play, right?
In exchange for showing me a new bug,
I'll show you one, too.
You mean it?!
It's a pretty crazy bug that can only be activated
the instant the round starts, though.
Battle start!
Round two!
Fight!
Doppelganger achieved.
Sunraku split in two?!
I waffled on what to name this one
when I first discovered it, too.
Should I call it Shadow Clone? Swampman?
Amazing, right?
You think you've got it all figured out,
but there's always new things to learn in this game!
That's why, no matter how deserted it becomes,
I've always gotta drop in from time to time.
That's the joy of BERP.
Berserk Online Passion!
You okay?
Two back-to-back losses...
Having one clone hold me in place
while the other kept pummeling me isn't fair!
Yeah, it's not fair how the clone
ends up controlled by the AI if you let it.
Thank you so much for giving up
your time to a new player like me!
No prob.
I've learned so much today.
I'm going to think up a cool name
for my own bug move, too!
Oh...
Speaking of, there's one really creepy bug
a friend of mine found.
Not sure if I can pull it off, but you wanna find out?
Yes, please!
Okay!
Meanwhile...
This "friend" of his was...
Dammit! Why do I gotta stay behind here by myself?!
What, you're still just Level 47?
You should put "minnow" in your name instead of tuna!
Sunraku, get back here already!
You small fry!
And, boom!
Hell yeah!
Time for another dedicated day of SLF!
Oh, do wait for me!
We're gonna try out that skill combo stuff
Katzo told us about, Emul!
R-Righty-o!
So, is this the right way?
You went off running without even knowing
where the Skill Garden is?!
Still, Sunraku, you appear quite motivated today!
Last night at bedtime, you seemed so exhausted!
It had me so worried!
I really was tired, yeah.
But discovering new things can't help but get me excited!
Especially when it's something I can get really into!
W-Wait, please!
The Skill Garden is this way!
Turn left down this passage!
Still, there's one of these Skill Garden places
in the Rabituza Palace, too?
But of course!
And our Skill Garden contains
a far greater selection than the ones in the towns!
We'll just keep that between us!
A secret advantage? I like it.
Oh, welcome!
Gracious me! If it isn't Emul and her bird-man friend.
I'm never escaping this "bird-man" rap, am I?
This is my big sister, Elke.
We're actually two of a set of triplets!
Such a pleasure!
A pleasure.
Well, she's got the lop ears.
I guess I see the resemblance.
And if they're triplets, that means there's a third.
Well? How may I help you?
I heard you can combine skills here, so...
Oh, I certainly can!
As it happens, I'm very good at that sort of thing,
so Father put me in charge of it... and that's why I'm here.
Did he, now?
He's picked up my sister's speech pattern!
Well, then, if you'd be so kind,
I'd be ever-so-happy if you'd help me combine my skills.
Oh, but of course!
I jumped levels pretty quick, so they've really piled up.
A bunch of 'em have changed, too.
Just so you know,
combining high-level skills with each other
does tend to produce superior skills in the end.
Oh, yeah?
When you put it that way,
it kinda makes me wanna max them out first.
But I'm also trying to clean house a bit.
So, let's get combining.
Oh, yes, let's!
There we go!
Is that all the skills I can combine for now, then?
And this is the recipe you want?
Six combinations will cost you 6000 mahni.
Sure thing.
Six thousand...
You sit tight, now. I'll have it right out!
Oh, if you please!
Yes, if you please!
Stop mimicking me!
I'll take a minute to double-check my stats, then.
Though I'm Level 51 now,
I had to stat up to equip my Moonblades,
so I never got to increase my vitality.
My defenses are still paper-thin.
No... make that tissue-paper-thin.
Well, here you are!
Wow, that really was fast!
It's all ready for you!
It's six combinations at once,
so the amount is quite copious,
but the moment you drink it all down,
you'll learn the combined skills instantly.
I've gotta chug this whole foul brew?
There's a freaking branch in it!
Go on! All at once, now!
I'd never do this if it weren't a game.
Go on, all at once!
Yes!
Go on!
Wow, I learned 'em all at once!
That's six new skills from the ones I linked!
Plus nine I learned or that changed while I leveled up.
I hope at least some of 'em are powerful.
Congratulations to you!
Isn't it lovely?
Oh, that's right. If you'd like...
There are Skill Grimoires
you can acquire only here in Rabituza.
Would you like to buy one?
Skill Grimoires?
And as my sister is so very fond of you,
I'll give you a discount.
You mean it? Awesome!
Do be cautious, Sunraku!
Despite appearances, Big Sister Elke is quite a moneygru—
Wow, I can tell you're related! Your sister's fast, too.
Don't sweat it, Emul.
When it comes to merch you can only buy
in special areas like this...
I'm always prepared to pay some high prices.
What a wise bird-man you are!
If I might ask, how much do you have to spend?
I've been having a fire sale on materials lately,
so I've got about 80,000 mahni on-hand.
Gracious me!
You could easily afford these, then.
They're so expensive!
And this is with the discount?
Are you sure you got this right?
Hang on... are you ripping me off?
Well, what do you say?
Surely you're not such a fool
as to let this special offer go, are you?
Th-Then...
I'll take the Vorpal Blade Tech...
Moon's Reflection... if you please.
Why, thank you!
That'll be 80,000 mahni!
Thank you so much for your business!
I just couldn't say no.
Sunraku, are you all right?
I thought she was gonna tear the feathers off my head.
Why, Big Sister Elke would never...
Actually, she might.
I wanted to buy that waist armor in Thirdrema, too.
I'll have to make some more money
before the Wethermon fight.
Hey, what time is it?
Whoa, just in time!
Who knows what they'd do to me
if I was late to another meeting?
Emul, open a gate!
Righty-o!
A fine evening to you.
Oh, Sunraku.
You're actually on time for once.
You have a good day or something?
I wouldn't say that, exactly.
But I've made up my mind.
About what?
Regarding our fight against
Wethermon the Tombguard in two weeks.
There's just one problem.
Problem?
What is it? We're both over level 50 now.
Currently, the only ones who know
the conditions to meet Wethermon
are my clan, the Ashura Kai.
They've been using the unique monster system—
the fact that you get experience
just for encountering them—
to level up and build their PVP skills.
Ashura Kai?
Those guys, huh?
Unlike Lycagon, you can always meet Wethermon
at a given time and place.
Must be pretty ideal for grinding, huh?
So the issue is...
On the night of the new moon, when we fight Wethermon...
we'll end up at odds with the members of the Ashura Kai
who've already accepted the unique scenario. Right?
Yes.
But aren't you part of their clan?
Can't you work together or something?
Like... ask them to stand down this month?
Not a chance.
They're actively opposed to defeating Wethermon.
I'm not sure I see where you're going with this.
What exactly is it you've "made up your mind" about?
The Ashura Kai...
are universally hated for their player-killing habits.
I'll bet, yeah.
And there was recently an update that gives players
who've done PKing a special sort of status.
A special status?
If a player kills a PKer,
in addition to a bounty,
they earn the right to any items
and equipment the PKer was carrying.
All of it, including stuff they've got in storage.
Oh?
High-level PKers like the Ashura Kai
tend to end up with some pretty rare items.
Which makes us basically walking treasure chests.
It's created a new class of player,the PK Killer.
Of course, we've found loopholes in the system
to reduce the damage they can do to us,
but someone could get around all of that
by attacking our hideout.
Your hideout?
Hang on. So the thing you made up your mind about...
You mean...
That's right.
Naturally, I know just where that hideout is.
And that gang of cowards is a thorn in my side at this point.
So...
I was thinking we'd go squash the Ashura Kai.
The fully immersive VR game, Shangri-La Frontier...
Its major summer update has finally arrived.
Indeed, on the night of this major update...
Sunraku and his party will take on
Wethermon the Tombguard.