Squish
Dragonfly
Sunraku
Round 1
Dragonfly
Sunraku
Palace of Rabituza
Elke
Linkable Skills
Strong Puncher Lv.1
Loop Slash Lv.8
Accel Lv.MAX
Deerstep Lv.7
Cutwater Lv.6
Crossing Slash Lv.4
Oppression Kick Lv.5
Armor Piercer Lv.3
Fighting Spirit Lv.7
Unbreakable Lv.5
Highrunner Lv.6
Naked Sense Lv.4
Starving Impulse Lv.4
Link 6/6
Accel Lv.MAX
Fighting Spirit Lv.7
Link 6/6
Climax Boost
Skill Linking Fee
6000 mahni
Cash on Hand: 80,150 mahni
Sunraku LV:51
Mercenary (Twin Blade User)  Skill Points Remaining: 5
Cash on Hand  80,150 mahni
New Skills
Infight Lv.1
Hand of Fortune Lv.1
Climax Boost Lv.1
Assassin Pierce Lv.1
Offroad Lv.1
Hunger Wolf
learned.
Skate Foot
Best Step
Parry Protect
Five-Boat Leap
Great Climb
Sharp Turn
Infight Lv.1
Hand of Fortune Lv.1
Climax Boost Lv.1
Assassin Pierce Lv.1
Offroad Lv.1
Hunger Wolf
Skill Grimoire Shop
Vorpal Sword Tech  [Half-Moon Slash]
Vorpal Spear Tech  [Moonlight Thrust]
Vorpal Blade Tech  [Moon's Reflection]
Vorpal Judo Tech  [Crescent Throw]
Secret
The Serpent's Apple
Two Weeks Later...
Constant Progress
Major Summer Update!!
The Severed Sea
The Frontier Fleet
The New Land
New Job!!
Rider