Thank you for coming!
Huh? Sold out?
Here, too?
Fourfolkshire and Sixenveldt were also picked clean.
How is it possible for so many
expensive items to get bought out?
What's going on here?
I don't know,
but our leader ordered us to buy
as many resurrection items as we could.
We'll go to the other towns.
Our leader's in a meeting with
other clan leaders right now, right?
You think we're running some kind of clan co-op raid?
Against an enemy powerful enough
that we need resurrection items for it?
What else could it possibly be?
Dunno.
On the day of Shangri-La Frontier's major update,
with many in its player base
breathlessly excited about what was to come,
another plan was moving into motion.
Hey, Reiji.
What's changed in the major update?
A new area got unlocked,
a new scenario and a job got added,
there's balance adjustments to some monster stats...
Then there's tweaks to things like how often
your luck triggers the "Endure" condition and stuff...
You think they added new weapons, too?!
S-Sure, probably!
I'd love a bigger, stronger bow!
How about we check in at a weapon shop, then?
Yeah!
Then, if you like, we can scope out all the new changes
for ourselves by going on an adventure together...
A monster!
M-Mia! Monsters don't spawn in towns!
But... I heard a weird voice!
Just put your weapon away!
But I know I heard a monster's voice!
Others were breathless for very different reasons.
Do it, Saiga Rei!
The day of the update is the perfect time to invite him!
Send it now while he's still logged in!
I actually sent it!
Y-You're good, you're good!
You spent two weeks working on that letter.
Not too formal, not too casual.
The exact perfect text you pored over for typos!
You're good, you're good, you're good, you're good!
You're back?
Did he log out?
It's from my sister?
The location of the Ashura Kai's
home base has been leaked.
We're still attempting to confirm its accuracy,
but please cease whatever it is you're doing
and join the rest of us immediately.
Sunraku.
What is it, old lady of mine?
I'm not your old lady!
The time has come, hasn't it?
Yeah, the time's come.
There's something I'd like to give you, Sunraku.
Just until you come back!
Wh-What the hell? A bird?!
The Toxic Eagle's back?!
Shoo, shoo!
Only I am allowed to ride atop Sunraku!
I'm not your damn perch!
Mailbird?
Oh, it's SLF's internal mail system.
Just realized I've never used it before.
From Psyger-0?!
Salutations.
Though this time of year has been blazingly hot
and plagued by powerful summer sunlight,
I hope that you have passed the time comfortably.
I apologize for springing this upon you so suddenly,
but I thought it might be presumptuous to ask you directly,
so I opted to send you this letter instead.
It struck me that an enjoyable pastime might be
to explore the new update's miscellany as a pair.
Would you find that agreeable?
It's so damn formal!
I thought she was calling me out for a duel at first!
Still, I'm kinda booked solid today.
I'm gonna have to turn her—
You don't give up, do you?!
But you cannot take Sunraku from me!
Knock it off. That's a bird of prey.
Though birds and rabbits
both spend a lot of time on two legs.
I guess you're kind of similar?
Knock it off! It hurts! Stop it!
Harrumph!
Another one from Psyger-0?
Please forgive me for this follow-up
so immediately on the heels of my prior invitation.
I fear an urgent personal matter has arisen,
and I will no longer be able to accompany you.
I guess I should reply to say, like, "It's cool."
Thanks for the help!
Okay, Emul, head's back in the game!
Let's go shopping in Thirdrema to make those final tweaks!
Tonight's the new moon, then?
Yo.
Da—I mean, Boss!
Don Vash, when did you—
Ah, I've been here a while.
You heading out there tonight, then?
Y-Yes!
Tonight's the night.
Those are the eyes of determination.
Go send that fool who's outlived his time
to his final rest already.
I will.
And don't you forget your vorpal soul!
Sir!
Sunraku, Sunraku!
I'll be staying home this time, right?
Yeah.
So as you face down Wethermon
the Tombguard, I wish to entrust this to you.
A necklace?
Daddy...
I mean, the boss brought it back for me one time.
I had it made into a necklace.
It's like an amulet of protection!
An amulet, huh?
Not that we'll need one to own this fight.
But with this amulet on top of my already awesome skills,
it's gonna be even more awesome.
Thanks a lot, Emul.
We'll win for sure, thanks to you.
I'll put it on you!
I shall await your speedy return.
Sure thing.
ID Shard Necklace. No effect.
It is a remnant, a fragment, a scrap, a shard.
It is impossible to know
who it identified, or where it was used.
But at one time, it was most certainly used
as proof of a certain person's existence.
Okay, time to roll.
All right, let's begin.
What's taking her so long?
Pencilgon... she said she'd be here any minute, but...
Whatever.
We can go to the Hidden Garden without h—
A raid?!
The Attack Master?!
Schwarz Vulf is here?!
The Ashura Kai meets its end tonight.
Suffer the fate that awaits all evildoers!
Orcelott?!
It's not just Schwarz Vulf!
Team 10PM...
The Tigers of Indra...
The Knights Tempura?!
They forged a multi-clan alliance to take us down?!
The hell is going on here?!
Let your screams play as a requiem
to the players you've killed, you bullies...
I mean, you bastards!
Run! Retreat to the Hidden Garden!
How'd they learn about this hidden area?!
Who could've leaked that info?!
Ta-da! Look at this glorious new equipment!
It's got my vitality skyrocketing from 7 to 22!
A glorious rise from tissue paper armor to wet cardboard.
Look, you never know what they might throw at you.
I wanna leave it all on the table.
By the way, that brand of energy drinks you recommended?
It's crazy, makes Energy Kaiser feel like sugar water!
The newest flavor of Riot Blood, yeah?
A friend of mine in the US wouldn't stop hyping about it,
so I worked up the courage and tried it.
I definitely couldn't do that on the regular, though.
Oh, right! And they found this awesome new bug in BERP!
For real?! Teach me later!
How'd it go?
So well, it was practically anticlimactic.
The Attack Master, Psyger-0,
seemed particularly worked up.
Must have some bad blood
with the Ashura Kai or something.
But, who doesn't?
I fear an urgent personal matter has arisen
and I will no longer be able to accompany you.
What's the matter?
Nothin'.
If they learn you sold 'em out,
they're gonna beat you to a pulp, right?
Not if I beat them first.
Of course!
Now, let's go over the plan one last time.
I've got items I want to give you, too.
First...
How'd they know where we were?!
Hardly anyone knew about that hidden area!
You don't think... there was a spy in our ranks?
A spy?
No... could it be?
O-Orcelott!
The entrance to the Hidden Garden is...
Someone's already in there!
Sh-She screwed us...
She screwed us!
She sold out the Ashura Kai!
That...
That stupid bitch of a sister!
What's up?
I thought I'd heard the braying of a lousy sore loser,
but I guess it was just my imagination.
Now, we've done our last checks.
Have you got any questions?
Nah.
Let's get this done.
Though, now I think of it, Setsuna's not here today.
She says you can't see her
without the light of the full moon.
It's time now.
I won't let your memories be sad ones.
Set...
No, Setsuna.
I will...
No, we will make your wish come true.
Now, let's go see him.
Is that our guy?
I'll bet.
Wethermon the Tombguard has been encountered.
You're up, Sunraku.
Got it.
Wethermon the Tombguard.
Let's have a good fight...
Wind Slash!
...man to man!
Skill, Infight!
I'm gonna test you to your limits,
robo-samurai!
Close call!
A simple upward slash is that fast?
Wind Slash!
Aiming for my head?!
You bastard!
Parry Protect!
I see through your little trick, dumbass!
He really grasped the timing on the first try.
"Wind Slash."
A quickdraw move believed to have single-frame execution.
That's pretty darn fast.
It has a guard-pierce effect,
so you either need to see it coming and evade, or counter it.
So, we need to figure out the timing on the first try?
Easier said than done.
And he's got a whole bag of even nastier skills,
so that's a thing to look forward to.
A constant barrage of insta-kill attacks
at a 150-level handicap?
Sounds like you'd really need to pull out
all the stops for an opponent like that.
So it sounds like...
Right. Wethermon is likely a "special condition" type.
A "special condition" type.
An enemy you beat not by reducing their HP to zero,
but by achieving a particular condition.
Possibilities that come to mind...
"Pick up or destroy a particular in-game object."
"Last a certain length of time."
"Survive a particular attack."
You occasionally see
"persuade in the middle of battle," too.
Any idea what the condition is?
I've tried a few different things,
and I think it's "Last a certain length of time."
We'll proceed under that assumption.
Wethermon the Tombguard's
combat conditions change as time passes.
First, we need to survive the ten minutes of the first phase.
That's where you'll come in, Sunraku.
Someone with skills on par with a pro gamer
can surely figure out the way through his attacks!
The motion when he executes "Wind Slash"
is a swing down from the right-hand side,
then slashes horizontally with both hands,
followed by a strike on a delay or an upward slash...
Yes. With these two at my side...
I'll bet everything I have on this battle!
I get it...
That's some sturdy armor you've got!
No sweeping the leg, either?
There isn't a single attack that fazes him!
And any one of his attacks would kill me on the spot!
He's every bit as advertised, I guess.
Yeah, just as advertised...
He's...
Wind Slash!
...not someone you can beat!
Katzo!
Way ahead of you!
Take this!