Thank you for coming!
Huh? Sold out?
Here, too?
Fourfolkshire and Sixenveldt
were picked clean, too.
How it is possible for so many
expensive items to get bought out?
What's going on here?
I don't know,
but our leader ordered us to buy as
many resurrection items as we could.
We'll have to search the other towns.
Our leader's in a meeting with other
clan leaders right now, right?
You think we're running some
kind of clan co-op raid?
Against an enemy powerful enough that
we need resurrection items for it?
What could it possibly be?
Dunno.
On the day of Shangri-La
Frontier's major update,
with many in its player base breathlessly
excited about what was to come,
another plan was moving into motion.
Hey, Reiji-kun.
What's changed in the major update?
A new area got unlocked,
a new scenario and job got added,
there's balance adjustments
to some monster stats...
Then there're tweaks to things
like how often your luck triggers
the "Endure" condition and stuff...
You think they added new weapons, too?!
S-Sure, probably!
I'd love a bigger, stronger one!
How about we check in at a weapon shop, then?
Yeah!
Then, if you like, we can scope out
all the new changes for ourselves
by going on an adventure together...
A monster!
M-Mia! Monsters don't spawn in towns!
But I heard a weird voice!
Just put your weapon away!
But I know I heard a monster's voice!
Others were breathless for
very different reasons.
Do it, Rei Saiga!
The day of the update is the
best time to invite him!
Now, send it quickly,
while Hizutome-kun is still logged in!
I actually sent it!
Y-You're good, you're good!
You spent two weeks working on that letter.
Not too formal, not too casual.
The exact perfect text
you pored over for typos!
You're good, you're good,
you're good, you're good!
You're back?
Did he log out?
It's from my sister?
The location of the Ashura Kai's
home base has been leaked.
We're still attempting
to confirm its accuracy,
but please put an end to your free time
and join the rest of us immediately.
Sunraku-san.
What is it, old lady of mine?
I'm not your old lady!
The time has come, hasn't it?
Yeah, the time's come.
There's something I'd like
to give you, Sunraku-san.
Just for now!
Wh-What the hell? A bird?!
The Toxic Eagle's back?!
Shoo, shoo!
Only I am allowed to ride atop Sunraku-san!
I'm not your damn perch!
Mailbird?
Oh, it's SLF's internal mail system.
Just realized I've never used it before.
From Psyger-0?!
Salutations.
Though this time of year has been
blazingly hot and plagued
by powerful summer sunlight,
I hope that you have passed
the time comfortably.
I apologize for springing
this upon you so suddenly,
but I thought it might be
presumptuous to ask you directly,
so I opted to send you this letter instead.
It struck me that an
enjoyable pastime might be
to explore the new update's
miscellany as a pair.
Would you find that agreeable?
It's so damn formal!
I thought she was calling
me out for a duel at first!
Still, I'm kinda booked solid today...
I'm gonna have to turn her—
You don't give up, do you?!
But you cannot take Sunraku-san from me!
Knock it off. That's a bird of prey.
Though birds and rabbits both
spend a lot of time on two legs...
I guess you're kind of similar?
Knock it off! It hurts! Stop it!
Harrumph!
Another one from Psyger-0?
Please forgive me for this
follow-up so immediately
on the heels of my prior invitation.
I fear an urgent personal matter has arisen,
and I will no longer be
able to accompany you.
I guess I should reply to
say, like, "It's cool."
Thanks for the help!
Okay, Emul, heads back in the game!
Let's go shopping in Thirdrema!
Time to make those final tweaks!
Tonight's the new moon, then?
Yo.
Da—I mean, Boss!
Aniki Vash, when did you—
Ah, I've been here a while.
You heading out there tonight, then?
Y-Yes!
Tonight's the night.
That's a fine focus you've got in your eyes.
Go send that fool who's outlived
his time to his final rest already.
I will.
And don't you forget your vorpal soul!
Sir!
Sunraku-san, Sunraku-san!
I'll be staying home this time, right?
Yeah.
So as you face down Wethermon the
Tombguard, I wish to entrust this to you.
A necklace?
Daddy—
I mean, the boss brought
it back for me one time.
I had it made into a necklace.
It's like an amulet of protection!
An amulet, huh?
Not that we'll need one to own this fight.
But with this amulet on top
of my already awesome skills,
it's gonna be even more awesome.
Thanks a lot, Emul.
We'll win for sure, thanks to you.
I'll put it on you!
I shall await your speedy return.
Sure thing.
ID Shard Necklace. No effect.
It is a remnant, a fragment,
a scrap, a shard.
It is impossible to know who it identified,
or where it was used.
But at one time, it was most certainly used
as proof of a certain person's existence.
Okay, time to roll.
All right, let's begin.
What's taking her so long?
Pencilgon-san... she said she'd
be here any minute, but...
Whatever.
We can go to the Hidden Garden without h—
A raid?!
The Attack Master?!
Schwarz Vulf is here?!
The Ashura Kai meets its end this night.
Suffer the fate that awaits all evildoers!
Orcelott-san?!
It's not just Schwarz Vulf!
Team 10PM...
The Tigers of Indra...
The Knights Tempura?!
They forged a multi-clan
alliance to take us down?!
The hell is going on here?!
Let your screams play as a requiem to
the players you've killed, you bullies—
I mean, you bastards!
Run! Retreat to the Hidden Garden!
How'd they learn about this hidden area?!
Who leaked that info?!
Ta-da!
Look at this glorious new equipment!
It's got my vitality
skyrocketing from 7 to 22!
A glorious rise from tissue paper
armor to wet cardboard armor.
Look, you never know what
they might throw at you.
I wanna leave it all on the table.
By the way, that brand of energy
drinks you recommended...
It's crazy. It makes Energy
Kaiser feel like sugar water!
The newest flavor of Riot Blood, yeah?
Yeah, a friend of mine in the US
wouldn't stop pushing it on me,
so I worked up my courage and tried it.
I definitely couldn't do
that on the regular, though.
Oh, right! And they found
this awesome new bug in BERP!
For real?! Teach me later!
How'd it go?
So well it was practically anticlimactic.
The Attack Master, Psyger-0,
seemed particularly worked up.
Must have some bad blood with
the Ashura Kai or something.
Well, I guess everyone does.
I fear an urgent personal matter has arisen,
and I will no longer be
able to accompany you.
What's the matter?
Nothin'.
If they learn you sold 'em out,
they're gonna beat you to a pulp, right?
Not if I beat them first.
Of course!
Now, let's go over the plan one last time.
I've got items I want to give you, too.
First...
How'd they know where we were?!
Hardly anyone knew about that hidden area!
You don't think...
there was a spy in our ranks?
A spy?
No... could it be?
O-Orcelott-san!
The entrance to the Hidden Garden is...
Someone's already in there!
Sh-She screwed us...
She screwed us!
She sold out the Ashura Kai!
That...
That stupid bitch of a sister!
What's up?
I thought I'd heard the braying
of a lousy sore loser,
but I guess it was just my imagination.
Now, we've done our last checks.
Have you got any questions?
Nah.
Let's get this done.
Though, now I think of it,
Setsuna's not here today.
She says you can't see her without
the light of the full moon.
It's time now.
I won't let your memories be sad ones.
Set-chan...
No, Setsuna.
I will...
No, we will make your wish come true.
Now, let's go see him.
Into the gap between moments
spills a single wish
Is that our guy?
I'll bet.
Wethermon the Tombguard encountered.
Sunraku-kun.
Got it.
Wethermon the Tombguard.
Let's have a good fight...
Wind Slash!
...man to man!
Skill—Infight!
I'm gonna test you to your limits,
robo-samurai!
Close call!
A simple upward slash is that fast?
Wind Slash!
Aiming for my head?!
You bastard!
Parry Protect!
I see through your little trick, dumbass!
He really grasped the
timing on the first try.
"Wind Slash."
A quickdraw move believed to
have single-frame execution.
That's pretty darn fast.
It has a guard-pierce effect,
so you either need to see
it coming and evade,
or counter it.
So, grasp the timing on the first try?
Easier said than done.
And he's got a whole bag
of even nastier skills,
so that's a thing to look forward to.
A constant barrage of insta-kill
attacks at a 150 level handicap?
Sounds like you'd really need to pull out
all the stops for an opponent like that.
So it sounds like...
Right.
Wethermon is likely a
"special condition" type.
A "special condition" type.
An enemy you beat not by
reducing their HP to zero,
but by achieving a particular condition.
Possibilities that come to mind...
"Pick up or destroy a
particular in-game object."
"Last a certain length of time."
"Survive a particular attack."
You occasionally see "reason with
him in the middle of battle," too.
Any idea on what the condition is?
I've tried a few different things,
and I think it's "Last a
certain length of time."
We'll proceed under that assumption.
Wethermon the Tombguard's combat
conditions change as time passes.
First, we need to survive
the ten minutes of Phase 1.
You'll be the key to that, Sunraku-kun.
Someone with skills
on par with a pro gamer
can surely figure out the
way through his attacks!
The motion when he executes "Wind Slash"
is a swing down from the right-hand side,
then slashes horizontally with both hands,
followed by a strike on a
delay or an upward slash...
Yes. With these two at my side...
I can stake everything I am on this battle!
I get it...
That's some sturdy armor you've got!
No sweeping the leg, either?
There isn't a single attack that fazes him!
And any one of his attacks
would kill me on the spot!
He's every bit as advertised, I guess...
Yeah, just as advertised...
he's...
Wind Slash!
...not someone you can beat!
Katzo-kun!
Way ahead of you!
Take that!