Putting Feelings Into a Moment, Part 1
Option Falcon
Psyger-0-san will send Sunraku-san this mailbird.
Cancel  Confirm
From: Psyger-100
Dear Psyger 0,
The location of the Ashura Kai's home base has been leaked.
We're still attempting...
Rabbit
Mailbird Arrived
You've received a mailbird from
Psyger-0.
ID Shard Necklace
equipped.
No effect.
Important business until
tomorrow morning
Stay out!
Ashura Kai's Hideout
Lass
Branch
Ketchum
Remy
Iori
Lifestide Sash
Friends  Nearby Players
Sunraku
Oikatzo
You've received a party request from
Arthur Pencilgon. Accept?
No                      Yes
Arthur Pencilgon
has joined your party.
Other players are
fighting this unique
monster.
Unique Monster
Wethermon the Tombguard
Encountered.
Arthur Pencilgon
Sunraku
Oikatzo
Wind Slash
Empire Bee Twinblades
equipped.
Known Wethermon Info
When the battle begins, a badstat(?) field gimmick(?)
is applied to all players.
Levels will be reduced and equipment with level requirements
will be force-unequippable. (Demonstrably, armor will feel
unusually heavy and hard to move in,
weapons will fly from hands.) Normal attacks can generally
be dodged by attentive players, but one hit will even kill
most tanks, so be careful!!
Most annoying is the frequency with which he uses his
finishing move (which he always announces — telegraphing?).
How to deal with his mecha-steed remains unclear.
Slashes and magic attacks don't seem to deal damage, and if you let it be
Katzo Tataki
Pencil Knight
Reward Scales
Rebirth Tearjewel
Divine Lifesalve
Sunraku
Rebirth Tearjewel