Only Resentments About the End of Life Remain
Prismatic Forest Grotto
Setsuna of Bygone Days
Bonus Unique Scenario
Vorpal Epic
When the souls of the Divinity are shaken,
a rabbit shall tell an epic tale.
Rec. Level: 80
Unique Scenario EX
From the Living World, With Love
Begin now?
Unique Scenario EX
From the Living World, With Love
Begin now?
Yes
No
Unique Scenario EX
From the Living World, With Love
Begin now?
Unique Scenario EX
From the Living World, With Love
Begun.
Submission Pose
Sunraku
Katzo Tataki
Rakuro's Mother
Eika Hizutome
Entomology Geek
Rakuro's Younger Sister
Rumi Hizutome
Fashionista
Towa Amane
Rakuro's Father
Senji Hizutome
Likes Fishing More
Than Three Meals a Day
Sunraku
Dragonfly
Ever
Improving