We live in a world filled with countless games...
though the vast majority simply come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of them all
is the fully immersive VR game boasting over
30 million players worldwide.
It rightly earns the status of "god-tier," Shangri-La Frontier!
One lover of trash games, Hizutome Rakurou,
is trying out this very Triple-A!
What adventures await him there?
On the night of the full moon,
if you look at the luminescent moss
on the wall of the Prismatic Forest Grotto,
there's a small portion that remains dark.
If you examine it...
A secret passage!
To think I beat the Prismatic Forest Grotto
and missed a whole hidden area...
That really stings, man!
How'd you even find out about this?
It's truly incredible!
I was just lucky to find these time-specific hidden areas.
I came here to grab some items I needed
and stumbled upon it.
Which means people who find unique stuff
must be blessed by IRL fortune, eh?
Wipe that look off your face. It's pissing me off.
This is the face of an emperor on high,
gazing down upon a struggling peasant with beneficent pity.
And that's how you react, you filthy ingrate?
I will destroy you.
Quit it with the comedy act.
We're here.
What beautiful flowers!
All unique stuff aside, this area is my favorite.
It's pretty, but... creepy, too, right?
Spider lilies, huh?
Not one of your more auspicious flowers, is it?
Into the gap between moments
Sunraku, look!
spills a single wish
Distant days, so blurred by tears...
She's transparent!
Is it a bug?
You always assume bugs over plot reasons, huh?
Hey, Set!
It's been a whole month.
Oh, Arthur. It has been a while.
The clothes she's wearing...
Not very "fantasy," are they?
Looks more like something you'd wear in our world.
Is she from the setting's age of antiquity, the Divinity?
Could she hold a key to that unique scenario I unlocked?
This isn't the same group you brought before.
Yeah, let me make some introductions.
Howdy, we're Pencilgon's band of merry men!
The man of a hundred skills, Sunra—
Stooge 1, Stooge 2, and their mascot.
Hey, don't treat us like that!
I even came up with a cool pose!
They're my ace in the hole...
to finally put Wethermon to rest.
I'm Emul, daughter of Vysache!
Hey, don't get ahead of me!
And I'm Oikatzo!
You, too!
Arthur, this is quite a party you've assembled.
Don't you worry.
They might not be much to look at now,
but I'll train them up before the battle.
That's not what I meant.
I've never met a person
with Sooty's presence applied to them twice.
And accompanied by Cinderella's child, at that...
You reminded me of someone from long ago.
Okay...
It's nothing, really. Just nostalgia.
It was so long, long ago.
I'm sure it's been quite a while since her passing, of course...
You've stirred up some lovely old memories.
Thank you.
You're... welcome?
Set, I'd like you to tell them about Wethermon, as well.
Very well.
This is it!
He... Wethermon was my dearest love.
We had a minor misunderstanding, I died,
and he's spent all the time since...
All the time since... guarding my grave.
Your grave?
Hence "Tombguard," eh?
I don't know how much time has passed since my death...
but the next thing I knew, I was in this state.
Although I feel no resentment about the way my life ended.
Death is an ending.
Things that end should lie in the past.
They shouldn't tie down
someone's present... or their future.
I can't stand knowing that he remains tied down by my past.
He used a program—
a spell that I wrote, to create a barrier here.
She used a kind of anachronistic word just now.
By using the mana that dwells within moonlight
and inverting the coordinates
to the underside of the dimension,
he's made it impossible to reach that location.
But on the night of a new moon,
when the moon loses all its light,
a crack forms in the barrier preventing access
to the underside coordinates where he waits.
So we gotta jump through the crack and fight him?
Please put Wethermon...
Please put my love to rest.
Leave it to us, Set.
We're not like those noobs who've tried it in the past.
If that jerk is making you suffer,
we'll put him six feet under!
Did you hear that?
Is that the Pencilgon we know?
The one who, in Unite Rounds, dragged an NPC king along
behind her carriage to try to lure in enemies!
Yahoo!
The Pencil Knight who tied an NPC princess
to the chandelier to bait players into trying to rescue her!
She's having a pleasant chat with an NPC?!
Has she regained some sliver of her humanity?!
What is... this feeling? Is this... a soul?
I think there's a limit to how much crap I can take.
You want to learn how much violence
someone at max level can dish out?!
Hold on a minute! My HP's already at critical!
Look out, Sunraku, she's not gonna let us off easy!
She's in a PKing mood!
Honestly.
If we didn't have the Wethermon fight coming up,
I wouldn't back off
until I'd spawn-killed you five times over.
There's that heartless Pencilgon we know and love.
She's such an easy mark.
Maybe I should kill you after all.
Look, sometimes even I like to play it straight with an NPC.
With her name being Setsuna,
and her backstory... it just got me invested.
Okay, look, fine!
I can get emotionally invested in a game
now and then, too, okay?!
Sure, that's fine by me.
Getting serious about a game is a great thing.
Everything's more fun when you let yourself immerse in it!
That's right!
Taking your playtime seriously is what makes it fun.
Of course, that's also the job for a pro gamer like me.
Wait. You're a pro, you're taking the game seriously,
and you haven't even found
a single unique thing for yourself?!
Okay, now you've done it!
Say goodbye to those feathers
and hello to a head full of goosebumps!
Katzo, stop! One more hit and I'm dead!
Please, cease your fighting at once!
Oh, right, I forgot!
You guys are as stupid as I am!
We're facing a unique monster
that forces a 150-level handicap,
something unprecedented in boss battle history...
Wethermon the Tombguard.
But I know we can do this!
Let's take this seriously and win!
Right!
Morning already?
I've been grinding nonstop since I met Setsuna.
It's been late nights all the time.
I dove headfirst into killing Lifestide Lake Serpents,
and the next thing I knew, I was level 51.
Katzo's still just level 46, right?
Gotta work on my skills next.
Emul says Rabituza's got one of those
Skill Garden places where you can link skills, too, so...
Maybe I'll ask her to take me there.
If you're worried about your levels,
that won't be a problem.
What I'm after is pure player skill.
The rest comes down to my personal skill, then.
Morning.
Oh, good morning!
I know you're enjoying your summer vacation,
but I'm glad you haven't forgotten our agreement, Rakurou.
I don't need you physically logging me out again, yeah.
Well, you did have it coming.
Hey, Mom!
I told you, no bugs in the kitchen!
Aw, but he's a cute little one!
Aren't you, Augustus III?
And don't give them names, darn it!
How am I supposed to keep an appetite like that?
Oh, great. Amane Towa.
Hey, what? Are you a fan of her now, Big Bro?
She's the megastar model Japan gave to the world!
Nickname, Towa!
A day in her life is enough to fill a whole fashion magazine!
It's like she was born to be a model!
A fan of hers took pictures of her in secret
and uploaded them to social media,
and even though she didn't know it was happening,
Towa?
she looked perfect in every one!
With her name being Setsuna,
and her backstory... it just got me invested.
Towa, "Eternity," who lives in the moment,
and Setsuna, "Moment," who lives for eternity...
Even if it's just a clever coincidence
and fiction within the game...
I guess the NPCs act so realistically,
she ended up comparing herself to her?
Huh? What is it?
Pencilgo—
Er, Amane Towa deserves her privacy, you know?
You shouldn't screensho—
er, take pictures of her without permission.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm part-timing as a model today myself!
Wow, like one of those extras?
I'll have to watch out for candid photos myself!
Yeah, and I'll have to ask Dad for publicity, too!
Where is Dad, anyway?
He went out fishing yesterday...
I'm home!
And I guess he just got back.
Behold! A striped beakfish!
That thing's huge!
Goodness me!
I managed to fish it up right before the meet-up!
Guess we're having fish every day for a while again.
We have an agreement in our household, sorta like a rule.
For breakfast and dinner on Sundays,
we have to eat and talk together as a family.
The idea is, if we didn't, we'd get so lost in our hobbies,
we'd basically never see each other.
I made friends with a marlin fisher,
so I might go on a real excursion next time!
What are you doing, Dad?!
Are you gonna clean it here?
Of course I am! Freshness matters!
Do it in the kitchen!
Goodness me.
Everyone would think our family's a little cuckoo.
But we just all have our own little worlds.
We're perfectly sane.
The juice! You got the juice on my clothes!
I'm on my way to a shoot!
Say something to him, Mom!
I need to tend to my butterflies.
Dear, clean up the kitchen, would you?
Okay!
Darn it!
Still, I'm probably the most normal of the bunch.
Now!
Time to go back to my little world.
Two weeks 'til the battle with Wethermon.
It's gonna be a tough match.
According to the info Pencilgon gave me,
Wethermon is a non-stop source of single-digit
frame attacks, insta-kill moves, and area attacks.
So I know just where to train up!
The trash game where constant glitches
make all attacks come at crazy speed...
Berserk Online Passion.
BERP for short!
Man, this game is so deserted.
I know it's early, but it's still Sunday. Get it together.
Well, whatever. I'll fight the final boss of the story mode.
Hey, a player!
And he's got his versus icon lit up.
Hey, there!
Oh, hello!
"Dragonfly"?
Never seen that name before.
Um, you've got your fight icon on. Wanna go?
Yes!
I'm really new and I haven't even beaten the final boss yet,
so I'd love if you could give me some tips!
He hasn't beaten the last boss?
Wow! A new player!
Talk about an endangered species!
It might not be the best training
in the world, but who cares?
I want to face down against this rare specimen!
Glitches are fair game, right?
Yes! Thank you for having me!
Looks like an all-rounder build.
He's the type that makes a lot of bugs,
but he probably won't know how to use them.
Well, let's see what you've got.
Battle start! Round one, fight!
He's charging? He's not even a speedster build!
But you can't expect a beginner
to conform to conventional strats.
Twist your hand, pull back, and...
That move!
By drawing your fist back
just as you unleash the punch motion,
you generate a bug that extends your arm like rubber!
If the hit lands,
it'll deal a two-hit combo with double the damage!
Its called...
Pile Bunker!
He disappeared?
Your leg...
This is a bug move: the Yo-Yo.
It throws off your avatar's texture and hitbox at once.
Looks like you can use some basic bug moves.
But there's way more to this game than that.
I came in to practice for the Wethermon battle...
But BERP is full of bugs that the players
have discovered through trial and error...
And I'll give you a full demonstration.
My most esteemed Sunraku.
I pray that this initial letter might find you well.
I hope you have not taken ill in this summer's frightful heat.
I was both pleased and honored
by your acceptance of my friend request.
It's formal. Too formal!
I'm just trying to invite him to play the game with me!
If I start off like this, it'll just freak him out!
I've got to make it more friendly.
Yes, make it approachable!
So he'll accept my invitation without a second thought!
Heya, Sunraku! What's up, my guy?
It's your online bud, Psyger-0!
You down to rock a play sesh, co-op style?
Writing letters is so hard!