This world is filled with
too many games to count,
though the vast majority simply
come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of all games
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide—
Shangri-La Frontier, which rightly
earns the title of "god-tier game"!
One lover of trash games, Rakuro Hizutome,
is trying out the god-tier
game, Shangri-La Frontier!
What adventures await him there?
Want to take out the unique monster,
Wethermon the Tombguard,
with just the three of us?
It looks like, in two weeks,
I'll be picking a fight with
"Wethermon the Tombguard."
It's looking like I'll have to leave
you out of the party while I do...
What's wrong?
Picking a fight with Wethermon?!
D-Da... Bo...
Daboo... Bodadd...
I've got to tell my daddy!
Emul filled me in,
but I'd like to hear it directly from you.
You're picking a fight with that
fool who's outlived his time?
"Outlived his time"? Wethermon?
What does that mean?
But for now...
This event got sprung on me out of nowhere,
and it's gotta be an important one.
Roleplaying based on the
world and its characters—
That's my best choice in this situation.
Stay calm.
If you play your cards right,
you could get valuable info on Wethermon.
You beat Failia, right?
You can do this!
Get Vash on your side, here.
The keyword is "vorpal soul."
I don't think I need to tell you
how weak you still are.
You're right, of course.
I'm not doing this because
I know I can win, Aniki.
What's that?
I'll actually be playing a support role.
A friend of mine will
do most of the fighting.
Are you aware, Aniki, what's happening
with Wethermon the Tombguard now?
Nah.
Last I saw of him was some time ago.
This friend of mine says a
group of PKers—rather...
a no-good band of killers is exploiting
Wethermon to make themselves stronger.
They're using him as a tool.
Since... well, you get lots of
experience just for encountering him.
The mastermind of our upcoming raid
is technically part of that band,
but she truly wants to defeat
Wethermon the Tombguard.
She's gone to unthinkable lengths to do it.
No matter what lengths you go to,
if there's no chance of victory,
it's still a reckless move.
When did I say "vorpal soul" meant walking
straight into the mouth of death?
Not one of us would go into a
fight with the intention to lose.
But my friend is determined
to beat Wethermon,
and I and our other companion
believe in her cause.
"We only get one chance at this."
"Win or lose, this is our last shot."
Those are the words my friend
came to me with, and so...
I feel honor-bound to offer my aid.
I realize I'm still weak and inexperienced,
but I have two weeks to do what I can—
To transform the brash arrogance
of a cocky greenhorn
into the grit of a contender
who's challenging a champion.
Honor-bound, eh?
He's an awkward one, you see.
He's talking about Wethermon?
Serious to a fault,
never knows when to let up...
He lost his wife to a lousy little lie,
and ended up with that undying body of his.
He's a living corpse,
unable to even put himself to rest.
And so...
Someone has to take him down and
bring him that well-earned slumber.
I made up my mind not to
interfere with "them"...
But if you insist on doing
this, I won't stop you.
My sweet daughter's made a request, as well.
Come along.
I'll lend you a bit of a hand after all.
A forge?
I moved on to the next stage of the event!
So far, so good, man!
Hey, Bilac! You here?
Yeah?
Hey, Pops.
How about that, eh?
Ain't seen you here in a while.
Bee! Big Sis!
Heya, Emul.
Another of Emul's siblings?
Did Vash father the entire
population of Rabituza?
Probably not... right?
You the guy Pops and Emul told me about?
Hey.
Sunraku-san is his name!
Gotcha. You got an air about
you kinda like Evelle.
"Evelle"?
Another rabbit name drop?
Please, don't spring any more on me!
Well, take out your vorpal weapons already.
Aha.
These blades see you as
a good master, for sure.
They've got a fine countenance, too.
They'll do us just fine.
Bilac. I'm gonna ascend these.
"Ascend"? Make them better?
The best they can be!
Hang on...
You're gonna wield the hammer, Pops?
It'd be boring to just sit back and watch
while he challenges that fool
who's outlived his time.
Hey, there we go!
I'll get the forge lit!
Got any decent materials on you?
Ah, you know... from opponents
you struggled to beat?
Struggled to beat?
Lycagon's the toughest I've faced...
Though that was "struggled, got beat"...
And I sold the stuff I got
from the Mud Digger...
I didn't exactly get it
through my own efforts,
but I've got a material from a
monster that was pretty darn tough.
Hand it over.
The shell of a Quad Beetle, eh?
It held up against
Empire Bee attacks for ages.
I figured it had to be a
pretty excellent material.
It'll do.
Now, let's get started.
You're a lucky guy, y'know that?
Pops hasn't wielded the hammer for years.
Is that true? Um... Bilac?
My brother inherited the...
kingship, you'd say? Of Rabituza.
And I inherited his forge.
I suppose I never told you, Sunraku-san!
Dadd—er...
The boss is a blacksmith!
A blacksmith?
And not just any blacksmith.
He's a Master Craftsman—a label given to
those who master the blacksmith's art—
and an Ancient Craftsman—one who can
forge the lost weapons of the Divinity.
Combining the two masteries
makes him a Divine Craftsman.
The superlative forger,
peerless in the world of smithery—
That's our Pops.
It's about to begin, Sunraku-san!
The heck was that?
Magic circles?
With each strike, they rise, then
draw back into the weapon...
To "ascend" a weapon
means reading the memories and
experiences it's acquired in its battles
and coaxing it into a more appropriate form.
In other words, his transcendent
skill grants it its "true" form.
It's "true" form?
Weapons that bear the name "vorpal"
remember the battles they've
fought against strong foes.
The memories you've forged with 'em
and the power of the strong
foe you handed Pops earlier...
He mixes 'em together in the forging process
and changes the weapon's shape.
And since you managed to
mix it up with Lycagon,
I'm real curious to see what
your weapons will turn into.
The fire of the forge
against the sleeping sky...
Is he singing—
All right.
The Vorpal Chopper has taken
its true name and form.
Its name...
Moonblade (Waxing)
and Moonblade (Waning).
A twin weapon?!
One blade in the form of two.
Each needs the other to have meaning.
It's been a while since I saw
one change form, you know?
Let's check this baby out!
"Waxing—
when fighting an opponent of higher level,
successful criticals reduce your HP, but a
power bonus is added to your next attack."
"Waning—
restores HP under the same circumstances."
Hey, I get it. They really
do compliment each other!
Eh? "A certain number of successful
criticals adds to the fusion gauge"?
These weapons freaking combine?!
Gracious, how splendid!
Don't mimic me!
Let's equip these babies
and give 'em a whirl!
Stat requirements?
C-Calm down, dude.
It's a simple math problem.
I need 150 stat points in total.
My current total in the relevant stats is 57.
I get five points per level raised, so...
I need to be level 50 to use 'em?!
Well, guess you need to toughen
up a bit more to use 'em.
S-Sunraku-san?
Sunraku-san?!
But I wanna use them now!
So, in conclusion...
I'm late. Sorry!
I really mean it, kinda.
I hope you figured out your last words!
We were supposed to meet
three damn hours ago!
That's too late to just "sorry" away!
The truth is, I was plugging
along on a unique scenario,
and Wethermon's name came up...
So I thought it might be worth pursuing.
All right. Spill, and I'll call us even.
Huh? Just scot-free like that?!
Though... that's a bold little
avatar you got, Katzo.
Actually, I guess you're... Oikatzo here?
Like the soup base, Oigatsuo?
He always picks names like that.
His real name combines into
the character "Katsuo,"
so he always sticks "Katzo" in there.
I don't need pointers on
character design from you,
criminal exhibitionist Sunraku-kun.
I'm sure you don't appreciate how
hard it was for me to get here.
I chose a back-alley place
with especially low traffic,
so you can relax while you're here.
No wonder it was so hard to find.
Anyway, let's get to brass tacks.
Mind telling me what you learned?
Sure.
I see.
He called Wethermon the Tombguard
"a living corpse" who'd "outlived his time"?
Are we talking about an undead monster here?
His movements did seem a bit janky
when the fight first started.
I see.
I'd assumed he was a cyborg-type, but...
Being undead would explain a lot.
Anything there that can help with our strats?
I've got some things to take care of.
Let's split up until nightfall.
Sure, but... what should we do next?
I'll give you guys these for now.
Go grind in the Iron Ruins in the meantime.
Grind levels, huh?
I'm all for it, but...
A map, and...
...a fishing rod?
It'll make sense when you get there.
I've been wondering since
you first arrived...
Sunraku-kun, do you actually
think that disguise is working?
Pray tell? This is merely
the latest fashion trend...
Huh? What is it?
I guess he fooled one of us?
Maybe if you haven't seen her,
it doesn't seem off?
Well, whatever.
See you back here tonight.
Sure.
Later.
Okay, let's get down to business!
The Iron Ruins of the Divinity, right?
Hold on while I plan a
safe route to the gate.
What a pain.
I gotta sneak around now, too, huh?
Sunraku-san! Sunraku-san!
I'm getting a terrible earache!
Might I please move around a bit?
Sunraku!
Your equipment's talking!
It is, isn't it?!
Okay, go on.
I thought it'd be fun to see
how long it took him to notice.
Indeed...
Is this NPC that unique one?
Can I have a closer look?
What are you doing?!
Unhand me!
Man, I want unique stuff, too!
Let me go, I say!
Get your own, then.
Here we are. The entrance at last!
I want unique stuff too. You lucky dog!
That's all you've been
saying this whole time.
Let's get going.
I wanna get to level 50 ASAP.
Fine, fine.
But this is my first time in a party in SLF.
My first time with another player, too.
It's got a pretty different vibe
from the rest of the world so far...
Seems like it could be fun.
Yeah. The Iron Ruins of the Divinity, huh?