This world is filled with countless games...
though the vast majority simply come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of them all
is the fully immersive VR game boasting over
30 million players worldwide.
It rightly earns the status of "god-tier," Shangri-La Frontier!
One lover of trash games, Hizutome Rakurou,
is trying out this very Triple-A!
What adventures await him there?
Want to take out the unique monster,
Wethermon the Tombguard, with just the three of us?
It looks like in two weeks,
I'll be picking a fight with "Wethermon the Tombguard."
Seems I'll have to leave you out of the party while I do...
What's wrong?
Picking a fight with Wethermon?!
D-Da... Bo...
Daboo... Bodadd...
I-I've got to tell my daddy!
Emul filled me in,
but I'd like to hear it directly from you.
You're picking a fight with that fool who's outlived his time?
"Outlived his time"? Wethermon?
What does that mean?
But for now...
This event got sprung on me out of nowhere.
So it's gotta be an important one.
Roleplaying based on the world and its characters
is my best choice in this situation.
Stay calm.
If you play your cards right,
you could get valuable info on Wethermon.
You beat Failia, right?
You can do this!
Get Vash on your side.
The keyword is "vorpal soul."
I don't think I need to tell you how weak you still are.
You're right.
I'm not doing this because I know I can win, Don Vysache.
What's that?
I'll actually be playing a support role.
A friend of mine will do most of the fighting.
Have you heard anything recently about
Wethermon the Tombguard?
Nah.
Last I saw him was some time ago.
This friend of mine says a group of PKers—rather...
a no-good band of killers is exploiting him
to make themselves stronger.
They're using him as a tool,
since... well, you get lots of experience
just for encountering him.
The mastermind of our upcoming raid
is technically a part of that band,
but she truly wants to defeat Wethermon the Tombguard.
She's gone to unthinkable lengths to do it.
None of that really matters.
No amount of planning can prepare you
for something so impossible.
When did I say a "vorpal soul" meant
walking straight into the jaws of death?
Not one of us would go into
a fight with the intention to lose.
But my friend is determined to beat Wethermon.
I and our other companion believe in her cause.
"We only get one chance at this."
"Win or lose, this is our last shot."
Those are the words my friend came to me with, and so...
I feel honor-bound to offer my aid.
I realize I'm still weak and inexperienced,
but I have two weeks to do what I can.
To transform the brash arrogance of a cocky greenhorn
into the grit of a contender who's challenging a champion.
Honor-bound, eh?
He's an awkward one, you see.
Is he talking about Wethermon?
Serious to a fault, never knows when to let up...
He lost his wife to a lousy little lie
and ended up with that undying body of his.
He's a living corpse, unable to even put himself to rest.
And so...
someone has to take him down
and bring him his well-deserved slumber.
I made up my mind not to interfere with them...
but if you insist on doing this, I won't stop you.
My sweet daughter's made a request, as well.
Come along.
I'll lend you a bit of a hand, after all.
A forge?
I moved on to the next stage of the event!
So far, so good, man!
Hey, Bilac! You here?
Yeah?
Hey, Pops.
How about that, eh?
Ain't seen you here in a while.
Bee! Big Sis!
Heya, Emul.
Another of Emul's siblings?
Did Vash father the entire population of Rabituza?
Probably not... right?
You the guy Pops and Emul told me about?
'Sup.
His name is Sunraku!
Gotcha. You got an air about you kinda like Evelle.
"Evelle"?
Another rabbit name drop?
Please, don't spring any more on me!
Well, take out your vorpal weapons already.
Aha.
These blades recognize you as a good master, for sure.
They've got a fine countenance, too.
They'll do us just fine.
Bilac. I'm gonna ascend these.
"Ascend"? Make them better?
The best they can be!
Hang on...
You're gonna wield the hammer, Pops?
It'd be boring to just sit back and watch
while he challenges the defier of time.
Hey, there we go! I'll get the forge lit!
Got any decent materials on you?
Ah, you know... from opponents you had trouble beating?
Trouble?
Lycagon's the toughest I've faced...
But I didn't beat it per se...
And I sold the stuff I got from the Mud Digger...
I didn't exactly defeat it by myself,
but I've got material from a monster
that was pretty darn tough.
Hand it over.
The shell of a Quad Beetle, eh?
It fended off against Empire Bee attacks for ages.
I figured it had to be a pretty excellent material.
It'll do.
Now, let's get started.
You're one lucky guy, y'know that?
Pops hasn't wielded the hammer for years.
Is that true? Um... Bilac?
My brother inherited the... kingship,
you'd say? Of Rabituza.
And I inherited the forge.
I suppose I never told you, Sunraku!
Dadd—er...
The boss is a blacksmith!
A blacksmith?
And not just any blacksmith.
He's a Master Craftsman, a label given to those
who master the blacksmith's art,
and an Ancient Craftsman, one who can forge
the lost weapons of the Divinity.
The two masteries make him a Divine Craftsman.
The incomparable forger, peerless in the world of smithery.
That's our Pops.
It's about to start, Sunraku!
The heck was that?
Magic circles?
With each strike, they pop out,
then draw back into the weapon...
To "ascend" a weapon means reading the memories
and experiences it's acquired in its battles...
and coaxing it into a more appropriate form.
In other words, his transcendent skill
grants it its "true" form.
It's "true" form?
Weapons that bear the name "vorpal"
remember the battles they've fought against strong foes.
The memories you've forged with 'em...
and the power of the strong foe you handed Pops earlier...
He mixes 'em together in the forging process
and changes the weapon's shape.
And since you managed to mix it up with Lycagon,
I'm real curious to see what they'll turn into.
The fire of the forge against the sleeping sky...
Is he singing—
All right.
The Vorpal Chopper has taken its true name and form.
They will be known as...
the Twinblades of the Waxing and Waning Moon.
A twin weapon?!
One blade in the form of two.
Each needs the other to fulfill their purpose.
It's been a while since I saw one change form, you know?
Let's check this baby out!
"Waxing.
When fighting an opponent of higher level,
successful crits reduce your HP,
but a power bonus is added to your next attack."
"Waning restores HP under the same circumstances."
Hey, I get it. They really do complement each other!
Eh? "A certain number of successful crit
adds to the fusion gauge"?
These weapons freaking combine?!
Gracious, how splendid!
I said don't mock me!
Let's equip these babies and give 'em a whirl!
Stat requirements?
C-Calm down, dude.
It's a simple math problem.
I need 150 stat points in total.
And I'm currently sitting on 57 on those stats.
I get five points per level raised, so...
I need to be level 50 to use 'em?!
Guess that means you need to toughen up
a bit more before you can try 'em.
S-Sunraku?
Sunraku?!
But I wanna use them now!
So, in conclusion...
I'm late. Sorry!
I really mean it, kinda.
I hope you've said your last goodbyes!
We were supposed to meet three damn hours ago!
You can't just get away with it and say you're sorry!
The truth is, I was plugging along on a unique scenario,
and Wethermon's name came up.
So I thought it might be worth pursuing.
All right. Spill and I'll call us even.
Huh? Just scot-free, like that?!
Though... that's a bold little avatar you got, Katzo.
Actually, I guess you're... Oikatzo here?
Like the soup base, Oigatsuo?
He always picks names like that.
His real name combines into the character "Katsuo,"
so he always sticks "Katzo" in there.
I don't need pointers on character design
from a criminal exhibitionist like you, Sunraku.
I'm sure you don't appreciate
how hard it was for me to get here.
I chose a back alley place with especially low traffic,
so you can relax while you're here.
No wonder it was so hard to find.
Anyway, let's get to brass tacks.
Mind telling me what you learned?
Sure.
I see.
He called Wethermon the Tombguard
"a living corpse" who'd "outlived his time"?
Are we talking about an undead monster here?
His movements did seem a bit janky
when the fight first started.
So that's how it was.
I'd assumed he was a cyborg-type.
But being undead would explain a lot.
Anything there that can help with our strats?
I've got some things to take care of.
Let's split up until nightfall.
Sure, but... what should we do next?
I'll give you guys these for now.
Go grind in the Iron Ruins in the meantime.
Grind levels, huh?
I'm all for it, but...
A map, and...
...a fishing rod?
It'll make sense when you get there.
I've been wondering ever since you got here.
But honestly, Sunraku,
do you think that disguise is working?
Pray tell? This is merely the latest fashion trend.
Huh? What is it?
I guess he fooled one of us?
Maybe if you haven't seen the rabbit, it doesn't seem off?
Well, whatever.
See you back here tonight.
Sure.
Later.
Okay, let's get down to business!
The Iron Ruins of the Divinity, right?
Hold on while I plan a safe route to the gate.
What a pain.
I gotta sneak around now, too, huh?
Sunraku! Sunraku!
I'm getting a terrible earache!
Might I please move around a bit?
Sunraku!
Your equipment's talking!
It is, isn't it?!
Okay, go on.
I thought it'd be fun to see how long it took him to notice.
Indeed...
Is this NPC that unique one?
Can I have a closer look?
What are you doing?!
Unhand me!
Man, I want unique stuff, too!
Let me go, I say!
Get your own, then.
Here we are. The entrance at last!
I want unique stuff too. You lucky dog!
That's all you've been saying this whole time.
Let's get going.
I wanna get to level 50 ASAP.
Fine, fine.
But this is my first time in a party in SLF.
My first time with another player, too.
It's got a pretty different vibe
from the rest of the world so far.
Seems like it could be fun.
Yeah. The Iron Ruins of the Divinity, huh?