The Glimmer of Truth
"Roleplaying"
To play one's given role in the setting.
Good Communication
Bilac
Ascend
"Bring to Truth"
Master Craftsman
Ancient Craftsman
Divine Craftsman
Moonblade (Waxing)
A twinblade with a crescent-shaped blade.
Moonblade (Waning)
Waxing
When fighting an opponent of higher level, successful criticals reduce your HP, but a power bonus is added to your next attack.
Waning
When fighting an opponent of higher level, successful criticals restore your HP.
A certain number of successful criticals adds to the fusion gauge.
Cannot be wielded due to
failure to meet stat requirements.
Waxing / Waning
Stat Requirements
Thirdrema
The Serpent's Apple
Oikatzo
Kei Uomi
Modor Katzo
Oikatzo
Katzo Tataki
Katsuo (Skipjack Tuna)
Give
Drop
Iron Ruins of the Divinity