Clan Leader, Ashura Kai
Orcelott
[The Saint] Advanced Players Teach Beginners the Ropes  #81 [Cute]
74: Add (Advanced)
Seriously, to unlock the elite jobs you've got to at least make it to Sixburg.
How many times do I have to tell people this?
Maybe we should put it on the FAQ.
75: Alinoiyu (Beginner)
I have a question for our esteemed elders. I was picking up equipment
in Secondale when I ran into this player. He had the cutest talking bunny
with him. How can I befriend this monster?
New Chapter
"A Bouquet Thrown With Love From the River's Edge"
A Dazzling Sea of Trees
Sunraku
You've received a friend request from
Psyger-0. Accept?
No
Yes
Sunraku has been added to your
friend list.
Prismatic Forest Grotto
Storage Papillon
Empire Worker Bee
Mimic Mantis
Quad Beetle
Marsh Daggers
equipped
Storage Papillon Nectar Pouch
Used by the Storage Papillon to store its nectar. It's very fragile, so it's difficult to obtain with the nectar intact. The nectar is fun to eat and fun to throw.
Throwing Knife
equipped.
Practical Training  Opponent 5
Toxic Eagle
Spiral Edge
Storage Papillon Nectar Pouch
Empire Worker Bee Pollen Hair
Empire Hunter Bee Stinger
Empire Hunter Bee Mandible
Mimic Mantis Stealth Wing
Mimic Mantis Scythe Arm
Empire Hunter Bee
Empire Queen Bee
Storage Papillon Nectar Pouch
Dropped Items
Quad Beetle Horn
Quad Beetle Mandible
Quad Beetle Shell
Quad Beetle Elytron