You've disgraced the name of Ashura Kai.
We're sorry, Sir Orcelott.
We weren't expecting the Attack Master to join in.
I mean... how could we?
There's a Unique Scenario on the line.
You should've expected top players to show up.
Why didn't you do it yourself, then?
I've got better things to do.
Oh, yeah?
Anyway, this rabbit is definitely the key
to some unique stuff.
And we're dealing with a beginner
who barely knows the system.
Threaten him however you need to.
Just get the info from him.
Sir.
Fine.
Not that I have a problem with pet rabbits...
But as Ashura Kai, shouldn't we figure out
how to deal with that first?
This again?
I told you my policy on that.
Unique monsters are programmed to be unbeatable.
At the moment, we're the only ones
who know that thing's spawn conditions.
Just encountering it nabs us experience,
so if we play our cards right,
we can use it to increase Ashura Kai's battle power.
There's nothing to be gained by fighting that thing.
Going whole-hog on that fight
would just be throwing good items away.
Agreed.
God...
These people really are useless.
Hey, where are you going?
You're supposed to wait until the others arri—
So sorry.
I've got better things to do.
Stupid woman.
Ashura Kai used to get hate from everyone around them
and made "thrive on hate" their philosophy.
But since the update patch
made player-killing a riskier venture,
they've changed.
Avoiding danger, seeking stability...
The current Ashura Kai can't defeat that.
Hard to believe...
that I'm putting my neck on the line for one little NPC.
Who would have thought?
It's a huge gamble, win or lose...
I'll bet everything I have, and win.
To bury that Unique monster, one of the Seven Colossi...
Wethermon the Tombguard.
Watch me, Set.
Okay, I've decided!
We'll head for the Prismatic Forest Grotto first!
Would you like to know my reasoning, Emul?
It's gonna be a pain in the ass
if there's guns and such in the ruins, so hard pass.
Haven't we seen that person before?
A person?
I-Isn't that... That's Psyger-0, right?
Talk about intimidating...
Wait, is he here to get payback for stepping on him?!
Bad news, Emul! Run!
What?!
Any sightings of the birdman?
Nah.
He might've moved on to a new area already.
Clear the way!
You're running so quickly!
What's with that guy?
There's some weirdos out there.
Wait, look!
It's Sunraku!
What?!
That's it! He thinks he can trick us with that weird armor!
Thinks he's pretty clever, eh?
Look at that!
A monster?!
And there he goes.
What was that all about?
There he is!
Get back here, you!
Dammit.
Emul, let's move on to the next area!
Of course!
I know where he's going.
He's making a beeline for the Iron Ruins.
Let's tell 'em to set an ambush at the gate!
Got it. We're on our way.
Excuse me, Sunraku?!
What?
Wasn't our destination the Prismatic Forest Grotto?
This is the way to the Iron Ruins of the Divinity!
Yeah, it's a fake-out!
If I went straight to my real destination,
they'd catch on in a minute!
I'll make 'em think I'm heading for the ruins
while I cut through an alley and head for the Grotto!
If I can just shake 'em off for a second...
they'll just go to wait for me at the wrong gate!
Dammit. Where'd he go?
Just head for the gate that leads to the Ruins!
Right.
You see that, Emul?
There's an art to deception.
Always prepare at least one obvious lie,
one truth that seems like a lie,
and one lie that seems like the truth.
How educational!
I learned that from Pencilgon, actually.
Okay, perfect.
Deception comple—
How did he know?!
Don't tell me... he's more than some
muscle-headed gaming addict?!
Huh?
A friend request?
I-I'd like to... s-start as... friends.
I can barely hear you, man...
Wait, could she be a girl?
The friend system is proof of close bonds within a game.
A friend request is an expression
of intent to build such a bond.
Why send me a friend request?
Is this a plot to get my guard down?
No... if that were the case, I'd be cut in half already.
Or is he trying to make me think he wants to be friends
so I'll spill all the info about the scenario?
Psyger-0...
You're observant enough to see through my perfect
diversion and suss out where I was really headed.
You've got to be plotting something.
But I'm a gamer who's been through all kinds of PvP before.
So bring it on.
I'll play into your hands and still beat you!
I did it!
When I first lost him, I got so upset.
And right after I finally found him!
The first time I came to Thirdrema,
I traveled to the Forest Grotto first, right?
It was a total guess.
But I'm so glad I found him!
U-Um...
I-If you'd like... I could... h-help you through the game...
Help me?
I knew it!
You're trying to make me feel like I owe you one
and shake me down for info later!
The thing is, I'm not a huge fan of
power-leveling my way through games.
I appreciate the offer, but I'll have to say no.
O...
Of course you would!
Um, so... I'm sorry if I've ruined any of your fun!
I-I suppose I've been very rude.
Then... good luck with your game!
Oh... yeah.
And sorry about using you as a springboard earlier.
O-Oh, not at all!
W-Well, another time, maybe!
Right.
Well... later, then.
Eh? She backed off pretty quick.
That pioneer looked very strong indeed!
Yeah, she's quite the gamer.
Probably four or five times stronger than I am.
Though I'm sure your vorpal soul is way stronger!
I appreciate that.
Though I wish she'd tell me
what the hell a vorpal soul is already.
Still... maybe I'm overthinking it?
Well, I'll write it off as an encounter
with a more rational Lycagon,
put it behind me and move on!
That girl with him didn't have a name over her head.
I guess she was an NPC, huh?
I was so shocked, at first, I ended up hiding, but...
One way or another, Hizutome accepted my friend request!
I've made progress, Miss Mana!
So tell him how you feel.
Dammit.
He's not heading for the ruins after all?
A diversion, eh?
Seems he knows what he's doing.
Let's head for the Prismatic—
Th-The Attack Master?!
W-We'll try this one later!
Yeah!
We can finally relax!
Sheesh, even with that thing on, I was still recognized.
Even in a cave, it's so bright!
Right, Sunraku?
Photoluminescent moss, huh?
So it's one of those deals.
I've been greeted by plenty of sights
as I come out at the end of a tunnel.
Rifles pointed at me,
shooting stars passing in front of my eyes...
But this is really what it says on the tin, huh?
Whoa, it's awesome!
Nothing beats the excitement of a new area!
This little one's making it pretty obvious.
I'm counting on a pricey item drop from you.
I'm a little low on cash from stocking up on items.
Tally-ho, Sunraku!
Gotcha!
Pretty light on your wings despite that big ol' potbelly.
But a butterfly's speed is still...
too slow!
Aha!
I thought so!
If I don't damage the stomach, I can snag it as an item!
What's this say? "Storage Papillon Nectar Pouch"?
It's fun to throw?
That was quite a skillful display, Sunraku!
You said it!
Let's keep gathering up these drops!
And earn a lot of money!
Then beat the area boss!
We fear nothing!
There it is.
I fear I don't see it.
Well, just you watch.
You bought a knife?
A Throwing Knife.
Since melee is my only combat option,
I got pretty traumatized by the shitbird in the arena.
It's a consumable item,
but it's an invaluable way to attack from a distance.
I knew you were there, you mantis bastard!
You keep running off and camouflaging yourself.
Why don't you just turn into loot for me?
How truly brilliant!
Okay, so those guys are a cinch
without their camouflaged ambushes.
And you've collected no shortage of items!
Yeah, it's going pretty smooth,
but there's one I haven't beaten yet...
Speak of the devil!
He's hefty!
Beetle boy there's gotta be at least five meters long.
That's a Quad Beetle!
Is it fighting?
It's drinking tree sap on the Empire Bees' turf!
Yeah, that's a way to piss 'em off.
Look at that!
It seems the Empire Bees are attacking en masse
under the orders of their queen.
But the intruder is unaffected by their stings!
Which team will the goddess of victory smile tonight?!
Emul on color commentary, what do you think?
C-Color commentary?!
I-I don't know that much about them!
At least say "There's no telling how it'll turn out just yet!"
Just improvise, girl. It's all about feeling.
This is all very tricky.
The fierce battle between monsters is escalating!
The Quad Beetle is attacking with all four of his horns
as he proceeds, undaunted, to the nest!
Is this the end for our intrepid defenders?!
Well, Emul? Give the people a word!
I-It's a very large bug!
What in the world?
Goodness me!
The unrelenting wave of attacks
has created an exploitable crack in the Quad Beetle's armor!
The Empire Bee Queen gives the crucial order to attack!
Our intruder's in big trouble now!
That's match!
Once he had her in firing range,
the Quad Beetle flew right into the queen!
With their queen gone, the bees are scattering!
And right back to his meal, huh?
With a near-death injury and everything...
That's what I call a power move.
He's coming right for us!
Oh, gracious!
Hey, I wanted to collect those Empire Bee drop items!
What's with the hair-trigger temper?
I didn't do anything to him!
Perhaps he thinks you were there for the sap!
Sap, huh?
Let's try it!
Looks like he really was after the nectar.
Those cracks in your armor the Empire Bees left...
I'll put 'em to good use!
Hell yeah!
Make 'em do the work and reap all the rewards!
I've got an inventory full of items now,
so I'll hold off on any more collecting.
Exploiting the labor of others doesn't quite seem fair to me.
What're you talking about?
It's a bug-eat-bug world.
You gotta do what it takes to be the last one standing.
Harrumph.
The area boss here is a spider, right?
Yes, indeed!
It's called the Clown Spider!
So... we're probably getting close.
Okay!