You've disgraced the name of Ashura Kai.
We're sorry, Orcelott-san.
We weren't expecting the
Attack Master to join in.
I mean... how could we?
There's a Unique Scenario on the line.
You should've expected
top players to show up.
Why didn't you do it yourself, then?
I've got better things to do.
Oh, yeah?
Anyway, this rabbit is definitely
the key to some unique stuff.
And we're dealing with a beginner
who barely knows the system.
Threaten him however you need to.
Just get the information from him.
Sir.
Fine.
Not that I have a problem with pet rabbits...
But as Ashura Kai, shouldn't we figure
out how to deal with that first?
This again?
I told you my policy on that.
Unique monsters aren't made to be beatable.
At the moment, we're the only ones who
know that thing's spawn conditions.
Just encountering it nabs us experience,
so if we play our cards right,
we can use it to increase
Ashura Kai's battle power.
There's nothing to be gained
by fighting that thing.
Going whole-hog on that fight would
just be throwing good items away.
Agreed.
Ah, I figured.
These people really are useless.
Hey, where are you going?
You're supposed to wait
until the others arri—
So sorry.
I've got better things to do.
Screw you, Big Sis.
Ashura Kai used to get hate
from everyone around them
and made "thrive on hate" their philosophy.
But since the update patch made
player-killing a riskier venture,
they've changed.
Avoiding danger, seeking stability...
the current Ashura Kai can't defeat that.
Hard to believe
I'm putting my neck on the
line for one little NPC.
Who would have thought?
It's a huge gamble, win or lose...
I'll bet everything I have, and win.
To bury that Unique monster,
one of the Seven Colossi...
Wethermon the Tombguard.
Watch me, Set-chan.
Okay, I've decided!
We'll head for the
Prismatic Forest Grotto first!
Would you like to know
my reasoning, Emul-kun?
It's gonna be a pain in the ass if there're
guns and such in the ruins, so hard pass.
Haven't we seen that person before?
Huh? Person?
I-Isn't that... That's Psyger-0, right?
Talk about intimidating...
Wait, is he here to get
payback for stepping on him?!
Bad news, Emul!
Run!
What?!
Any sightings of the birdman?
Nah.
He might've moved on to a new area already.
Clear the way!
You're running so quickly!
What's with that guy?
There's some weirdos out there.
Wait, look!
That's Sunraku!
What?!
That's it! He thinks he can
trick us with that weird armor!
Thinks he's pretty clever, eh?
Look at that!
A monster?!
And there he goes.
What was that all about?
There he is!
Get back here, you!
Damn it.
Emul, let's move on to the next area!
Of course!
I know where he's going.
He's making a beeline for the Iron Ruins.
Let's tell 'em to set an ambush at the gate!
Got it. We're on our way.
Excuse me, Sunraku-san?!
What?
Wasn't our destination the
Prismatic Forest Grotto?
This is the way to the Iron
Ruins of the Divinity!
Yeah, it's a fake-out!
If I went straight to my real destination,
they'd catch on in a minute!
I'll make 'em think I'm
heading for the ruins,
while I cut through an alley and head
for the Prismatic Forest Grotto!
If I can just shake 'em off for a second...
They'll just go to wait for me
at the wrong gate!
Damn it. Where'd he go?
Just head for the gate
that leads to the Ruins!
Right.
You see that, Emul?
In order to truly deceive another,
you must always prepare
at least one obvious lie,
one truth that seems like a lie,
and one lie that seems truthful.
How educational!
I learned that from Pencilgon, actually.
Okay, perfect.
Deception comple—
How did he know?!
Don't tell me... he's more than
some muscle-headed gaming addict?!
Huh?
A friend request?
I-I'd like to... s-start as... friends.
I can barely hear you, man...
Wait, is the player a girl?
The friend system is proof
of close bonds within a game.
A friend request is an expression
of intent to build such a bond.
Why send me a friend request?
Is this a plot to get my guard down?
No... if that were the case,
I'd be cut in half already.
Are you trying to build
a friendly relationship
so I'll voluntarily spill
info about the scenario?
Psyger-0...
You're observant enough to
see through my perfect diversion
and to suss out my true destination.
You've got to be plotting something.
But I'm a gamer who's been through
all kinds of PvP before...
So bring it on.
I'll play into your hands
and still beat you!
I did it!
When I first lost sight
of him, I got so upset...
After I finally found him!
The first time I came to Thirdrema,
I traveled to the Forest Grotto first, right?
It was a total guess, but...
I'm so glad I found him!
U-Um...
I-If you'd like... I could...
h-help you through the game...
Help me?
I knew it!
You're trying to get me in your debt
and shake me down for info later!
Um... I'm not a huge fan of
power-leveling my way through games.
I appreciate the offer,
but I'll have to say no.
O...
Of course you would!
Um, so... I'm sorry if I've
ruined any of your fun!
I-I suppose I've been very rude...
Then... good luck with your game!
Oh... yeah.
And sorry about using you
as a stepping stool earlier.
O-Oh, not at all!
W-Well, another time, maybe!
Right.
Well... later, then.
Eh? She backed off pretty quickly...
That pioneer looked very strong indeed!
Yeah, she's quite a gamer.
Probably four or five times stronger than me.
Though I'm sure your vorpal
soul is by far the stronger!
I appreciate that.
Though I wish she'd tell me what
the hell a vorpal soul is already.
Still... maybe I'm overthinking it?
Well, I'll write it off as an encounter
with a more rational Lycagon,
put it behind me and move on!
That girl with him didn't
have a name over her head.
I guess she was an NPC, huh?
I was so shocked, at first,
I ended up hiding, but...
One way or another, Hizutome-kun
accepted my friend request!
I've made progress, Mana-san!
So tell him how you feel.
Damn it.
He's not heading for the ruins after all?
A diversion, eh?
Seems he knows what he's doing.
Let's head for the Prismatic—
Th-The Attack Master?!
W-We'll try this one later!
We can finally relax!
Sheesh, even with that thing
on, I was still recognized.
Even in a cave, it's so bright!
Sunraku-san!
Photoluminescent moss, huh?
So it's one of those deals.
I've been greeted by plenty of sights
as I come out at the end of a tunnel.
Rifles pointed at me, shooting stars
passing in front of my eyes...
But this is really what
it says on the tin, huh?
Awesome!
Nothing beats the excitement of a new area!
Your little tummy sways
in such an alluring way...
I'm counting on a pricey item drop from you.
I'm a little low on cash
from stocking up on items.
Sunraku-san, fight!
Gotcha!
Pretty light on your wings
despite that big ol' potbelly.
But a butterfly's speed
is still too slow!
Aha!
I thought so!
If I don't damage the stomach,
I can snag it as an item!
What's this say?
"Storage Papillon Nectar Pouch"?
"Fun to throw"?
That was quite a skillful
display, Sunraku-san!
You said it!
Let's keep gathering up those item drops!
And earn much money!
Then beat the area boss!
We fear nothing!
There it is.
I fear I don't see it.
Well, just you watch.
You bought a knife?
A Throwing Knife.
Since melee is my only combat option,
I got pretty traumatized by
the shitbird in the arena.
It's a consumable item, but it's an
invaluable way to attack from a distance.
I knew you were there, you mantis bastard!
You keep running off and
camouflaging yourself...
Just turn into loot already!
How truly brilliant!
Okay, so those guys are a cinch
without their camouflaged ambushes.
And you've collected no shortage of items!
Yeah, it's going pretty smooth,
but there's one I haven't beaten yet...
Speak of the devil!
He's a hefty guy!
Beetle boy there's gotta be
at least five meters long.
That's a Quad Beetle!
Is it fighting?
It's drinking tree sap
on the Empire Bees' turf!
Yeah, that's a way to piss 'em off.
Look at that!
The Empire Bees are attacking
en masse on their queen's orders.
But Quad Beetle is unaffected
by their stings!
Upon whom shall the goddess
of victory smile?!
Emul-san on color commentary,
what do you think?
C-Color commentary?!
I-I don't know that much about them!
At least say "There's no telling
how it'll turn out just yet!"
Just improvise, girl. It's all about feeling.
This is all very tricky.
The fierce battle between
monsters is escalating!
Quad Beetle is attacking
with all four of his horns
as he proceeds, undaunted, to the nest!
Is this the end of the Empire Bees?!
Well, Emul-san?
Give the people a word!
I-It's a very large bug!
What in the world?
Goodness me!
The unrelenting wave of attacks
has created an exploitable crack
in the Quad Beetle's armor!
The Empire Bee Queen gives
the crucial order to attack!
Quad Beetle's in big trouble now!
And it's done!
Once he had her in firing range,
Quad Beetle flew right into the queen!
With their queen gone,
the bees are scattering!
And right back to his meal, huh?
With a near-death injury and everything.
That's what I call a kingly air.
He's coming right for us!
Oh, gracious!
Hey, I wanted to collect
those Empire Bee drop items!
What's with the hair-trigger temper?
I didn't do anything to him!
Perhaps he thinks you were there for the sap!
Sap, huh?
Let's try it!
Looks like he really was after the nectar.
Those cracks in your armor
the Empire Bees left...
I can't leave them unexploited!
Hell yeah!
Make them do the work and
reap all the profits!
I've got an inventory full of items now,
so I'll hold off on any
more collecting for now.
Exploiting the labor of others
doesn't quite seem fair to me.
What're you talking about?
It's a bug-eat-bug world.
You gotta do what it takes
to be the last one standing.
Harrumph.
The area boss here is a spider, right?
Yes, indeed!
It's called the Clown Spider!
So... we're probably getting close.
Okay!