Putting Feelings Into a Moment, Part 3
Head Equipment Changed
Spiked Battlehelm [4A]
Moonblade (Waxing)
equipped.
Moonblade (Waning)
Spiked Battlehelm [4A]
equipped.
Vorpal Blade Tech
Moon's Reflection
Assassin Pierce
Drill Piercer
Whip Puppet: Snake
Oikatzo
Divine Lifesalve
Evil Force
Oikatzo
Combo Spirit Fist
Flame Crimson
Arthur Pencilgon
STR↑        AGI↑          VIT↑         Stamina↑
Dual Impact
Spear of Sunlight
Sunraku
Climax Boost
Hunger Wolf
Sunraku
Clear Sky Conquest
Recast Time
= Time needed before a skill can be reused
Parry Protect                           Skate Foot
Use Item
Rebirth Tearjewel
Divine Lifesalve
Potion
High Potion
Sky Clear
Rebirth Tearjewel