SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
The Day Starts Early for a Girl in Love
Mini!
The day starts early for a girl in love.
Why are you up so early?
W-Well, it's just... er...
I th-thought it might be nice... if we
could walk to school together, maybe...
Even on the most ordinary of days,
the most trivial things can
change the scenery you see.
As a girl in love, Rei Saiga's gaze is focused.
W-Well, I know the route Hizutome-kun
walks to school, so...
How did you find that out?
I-It was a total coincidence!
It just happened that, miraculously,
the planets aligned such that I happened
to catch sight of Hizutome-kun...
Then, a series of coincidences
ended up with me happening to
come this way a few times...
And it happened enough times that
I ended up happening to catch sight of
Hizutome-kun a few different times...
And from those coincidental
sightings, I coincidentally...
I mean, it really was a
coincidence that I happened to
realize that he tended to
come by this way a lot...
I mean, it wasn't on purpose at all.
It was just a little curiosity...
Well, I guess "curiosity" is
a rude way of putting it...
Forget I said that.
Well, with all the information I had,
I kind of put it together...
I mean, it really wasn't on purpose!
I mean it!
But in the end, I did kind of find
out where Hizutome-kun lived...
Um, that is...
As she speaks on with the
force of a raging bonfire,
there is embarrassment in her voice,
combined with a strange sense of hope.
After having a brief breakfast at home,
Ms. Rei Saiga arrives at a certain corner.
But her eyes are unfocused and hesitant.
What are you doing?
Well... it's just, well...
Maybe I... you know...
might not be brave enough to...
Touching her pinkened—no, reddened—cheek,
Ms. Rei Saiga stares around the corner.
Hizutome-kun generally passes this way
between eight o'clock and ten-after.
He sometimes comes running
at twenty-after, too, but...
I-It's him!
Love — it is that which fuels courage.
Ms. Rei Saiga hides behind the wall,
but as the high schooler
passes by in front of her,
she reaches out her hand, and speaks...
So, as you were about to talk to him,
you caught sight of a middle-school
girl running alongside him,
and you hid?
That was probably his sister, you know.
Yes, probably...
At this rate, you might graduate
before you ever talk to him!