In SLF, the keys to victory
come from the story.
I'd always assumed Wethermon
was some kind of cyborg,
who'd modified his body with
technology from the Divinity...
But...
His classification is "undead monster"!
For undead, you use holy water!
Hey, the guy's screaming!
Is his field attack incoming?
No...
This isn't that animation.
Bingo!
I canceled his field attack!
Guess he didn't appreciate getting
splooshed with the saint's special water.
Hey, can you not make it gross?
The saint is like the idol of the SLF world.
Hey, what's going on with Wethermon?
H-H-Hey!
I-I think that thing just transformed!
What in the world is that thing?!
I dunno,
but I'm betting we don't wanna
let it combine with Wethermon, either!
An exclusive new form for stage 3?
Wh-What the hell do we do now?!
A new form calls for a new approach.
Pencilgon, go help Katzo!
Wethermon's body has started
gradually crumbling.
For phases 1 and 2,
we had to hold out ten minutes.
Maybe for phase 3, we have
to hold out until he falls apart.
I'd say this all but confirms the
"time passes" victory condition.
Given how it's gone up until now,
I'm betting it's ten minutes more—
That's our final time limit!
Leave this to me.
I'll survive ten minutes, no problem.
All right.
Just... don't get too reckless.
Until I can get back to acting as support,
one death could spell the end for you.
I'm leaving this to you, Sunraku-kun.
Sure thing.
Sorry, Pencilgon.
Ever since you mentioned the thing about
hanging in there through the time limit,
I've been thinking...
Where the hell is the fun in that?
A boss where you just turtle up
for thirty minutes straight...
What kind of game would that be?
I'll say it flat-out—one
that's boring as shit.
Game design that puts the story first?
I've played tons of games like that...
Games that go for a balance between
the fiction and the gameplay and fail
are regularly given the "trash game" stamp.
But Shangri-La Frontier...
You're supposed to be a god-tier game!
Yeah, thought so.
It popped into my head when I
saw that holy water attack...
In the state he's in now,
he might just take damage!
A passable compromise between
the fiction and the gameplay...
Any player who endures those
twenty minutes gets a reward...
A turn to fight back!
What, is that your first time
being parried by a helmet?
Time to unveil the new armor I created
from Quad Beetle materials...
Before you get a chance to fall apart,
I'm gonna beat you down...
Wethermon the Tombguard!
Pretty awesome, huh?
I practiced the helmet parry a ton.
"But why parry with a helmet," you ask?
'Cause if you can parry with your head...
it leaves your hands free!
Wind Slash!
Damn it!
That one did deal damage, right?
I landed a damn critical,
and he's not even fazed...
I didn't go as hard as Pencilgon,
but I still dropped a ton
of cash on you, got it?
That money-grubbing bunny...
I'm gonna use the 80,000 mahni I paid
her to rub your face into the dirt!
Vorpal Blade Tech...
Moon's Reflection!
Better watch your back, man.
Your six is wide open!
The Moon's Reflection was a bluff!
The real attack... is here!
Assassin Pierce!
Oh, I haven't even started to get my revenge!
Drill Piercer!
If "scars on the back are a swordsman's
greatest shame," then sorry...
I'm about to deal you a whole lot of shame.
How did I just know he'd end up in a brawl?
He's cackling like a madman over there!
Is that guy okay?!
I guess as long as the
cackling goes on, he's fine.
The bigger of an underdog Sunraku-kun is,
the more his motivation
and player skill spike.
But...
If we can't hold this thing in place,
he'll still end up an unwinnable fight.
I tried punching it a few times,
and it's looking like
it'll take damage now!
Still tough as hell, though...
Okay, look.
It's not worth sticking out
our necks to beat this thing.
Staying alive and drawing
Kirin's aggro from Sunraku-kun
is enough to earn us a passing grade.
A passing grade, sure.
But...
Whip Puppet: Snake!
If I'm gonna be graded,
I'd rather get a perfect score!
These two, I swear...
Okay, maybe not.
I didn't leave a dent!
What's this?
Evil Force.
It increases the user's
stats for fifteen minutes!
Even in your current state,
it should give you abilities
on par with level 99 or so!
Level 99?!
That's a god-tier item!
Why didn't you whip this
awesome thing out earlier?!
Using it comes with a serious penalty.
I've used it before, and it
was a pretty rough time...
Penalty?
I'll admit, I'm getting tired
of this one-sided fight, too...
You said you want a perfect score, right?
So I'm sure you're prepared for the risk—
A penalty?
Sounds fine to me.
I'm gonna turn you to scrap
and get a big old A-plus!
H-Huh? Why's everything
suddenly in photo-negative?
I feel like my hearing's gone fuzzy, too...
It's probably screwing with your
sense of smell and taste, too!
Is this the "penalty"?
Well, it does feel a little weird,
but it's not nearly as bad as I expected!
Actually... that's not the bad part.
Every thirty seconds,
your level decreases by one.
Huh?
Huh? My level goes down?!
Th-This thing lasts fifteen minutes!
Does it stick around after the battle, too?!
Yeah.
I've used it myself, and the
sense of loss was palpable.
If it's every thirty seconds...
For fifteen minutes... I lose thirty levels?!
So when the fight's over,
I'll have to start back from level 20?!
Why didn't you say that sooner?!
Ah, it went down...
You ate it before I could!
Oh, and I'll use my remaining Scale
points to boost my own stats!
Hey!
Still, I can't believe you chewed it.
I know it's just flavor text stuff in a game,
but I learned what those are made of,
and I haven't been able
to stomach one since...
What the hell did you let me eat?!
Okay, now I'm pissed!
You're gonna be my punching
bag, you robot jerk!
Red plus black makes crimson!
Combo Spirit Fist: Flame Crimson!
And I'll max out my buffs...
Let's get to it, Katzo-kun!
Infight!
Into...
Dual Impact!
With my right fist, I create
a cross-shaped seal...
Then I pound it with a right straight punch!
Nice! You finally staggered it!
Looks like the medicine did its thing!
Now I'm gonna stab its
knee until it shatters!
Spear of Sunlight!
I know it dealt damage... but even
with all those stacked buffs...
I still can't even crack it?!
Pencilgon!
Sheesh...
I wish you'd be clearer about
when your stagger phase ends!
I guess we'll need more than stat
boosts to make a breakthrough here.
Its armor seems thickest around the waist.
That's probably where all the
important bits are stored...
But how the heck do we
go about prying it open?
Okay!
I think I've got the hang of
the head-parry-slash combo.
What's the matter, man?!
Are you that depressed
that your robo-samurai sword
techniques won't work on me?!
I knew these Moonblades were
a good match for my skills.
I've got a skill I can only activate
when my HP fall below one-third—
Climax Boost.
For five minutes after activating,
it boosts my stats in proportion to
the level gap between me and my enemy.
But I've got so little HP,
there's no way to use Wethermon's attacks
to fine-tune them down to one-third.
But...
With the Moonblades' ability to shave down
and recover my HP with every attack,
I can do it.
And one more thing...
Hunger Wolf.
It only lasts for one minute,
but in exchange for depleting
my stamina and such,
it increases my strength,
agility, and vitality!
Thunderclap!
The stat increase is in proportion to how
few HP you've got, and your "hunger" level!
Nimbus Fist!
SLF has a gauge to represent your hunger.
It fills back up when you eat,
and if you go hungry for too long, it
impacts your stamina recovery rate.
Naturally, I micromanaged that too!
I'm at just the right level of hunger!
If I can combine these skills just
right, I know I can win this!
His sword's at his hip.
Another Wind Slash?!
I'll block it with a head-parry
from Parry Protect!
Here it comes!
Parry!
Huh?
What the... Where's the slash?
A...
Alice.
He's an awkward one, you see.
He's a living corpse,
unable to even put himself to rest.
So as you face down Wethermon the
Tombguard, I wish to entrust this to you.
Alice.
Alice?
A...lice...
ID key...
fragment.
Alice... is still... known?
This isn't a skill incantation.
For endless eternity...
He's talking?
I have lain here... rotting...
I did not... see... their fate...
I thought he was a corpse animated
by the machinery,
but maybe not?
Indeed...
the frontier... has been established...
"They"? "Frontier"?
Are they seriously giving
me story stuff now?!
Let us do battle... Child of the Second Plan.
I've got every neuron in my body
hard-focused on beating you.
Don't make me think about anything else.
If you intend... to infringe upon my vow...
Then be crushed by my
Clear Sky Conquest.
Guess he's finally getting serious!
Sounds great! Bring it on!
Wind Slash.
I thought maybe you'd changed things up,
but a standard Wind Slash—
Thunderclap.
Not a second's break between them?!
What's the big hurry, Wethermon?!
Nimbus Fist.
You kidding me?!
The freaking lightning
hasn't even stopped yet!
He's chaining attacks like crazy,
with basically no time lag between them...
Tidal Rush!
You can do that one with your
sword in hand, too, huh?!
Wind Slash.
At the head?
The torso?!
Wind Slash.
The legs?!
Okay, I get it now!
You can spam attacks without recast time!
That's pretty messed up!
Am I supposed to see every move coming?
That feels like pretty broken game balance...
The hell is he telegraphing?!
Pyroclastic Wyrm.
A new move, now?!
Black clouds?
Ash Blizzard!
A combination attack?!
What's the matter, man?
If you don't get me on the first hit,
you miss your chance!
Still, I don't have much in the way
of stamina or dodge skills left...
If this chain attack barrage keeps up...
Well, bring it on!
I'll hang on with pure chutzpah!
It's gonna take more than this to beat me!
And I've got a few ideas of my—
Clear Sky Conquest.
Through the cycle of rebirth
and a parting gift,
He's fast!
I'm already running as fast as I can!
I bring the ultimate end.
What the hell? My legs—
With transformation of "clear sky,"
This isn't like his other moves.
I deal the ultimate
I'll have to take it head-on!
I'll use this helmet to parry,
no matter what!
strike.
That which can cleave even dragons...
Sky Clear!
What the heck was that?
"Sky Clear," he called it, I guess...
But this move is way too nasty.
Will it reach?!
Wait!
But it's like I told you...
It's gonna take more than that to beat me!