In SLF, the keys to victory come from the story.
I'd always assumed he was some kind of cyborg
who'd modified his body with technology from the Divinity.
But...
his classification is "undead monster"!
Holy water is effective against them!
Hey, the guy's screaming!
Is his field attack incoming?
No, this isn't that animation.
Bingo!
I canceled his field attack!
Guess he didn't appreciate
getting splooshed with the saint's special water.
Hey, can you not make it gross?
The saint is like the idol of the SLF world.
Hey, what's going on with Wethermon?
H-H-Hey!
I-I think that thing just transformed!
What in the world is that thing?!
I dunno,
but I'm betting we don't wanna
let it combine with Wethermon, either!
An exclusive new form for the third phase?
Wh-What the hell do we do now?!
A new form calls for a new approach.
Pencilgon, go help Katzo.
Wethermon's body has started crumbling away.
For the first and second phases,
we had to hold out ten minutes.
Maybe for this one, we have to hold out until he falls apart.
I'd say this all but confirms
the "time passes" victory condition.
Given how it's gone up until now,
I'm betting it'll be another ten minutes.
That's our final time limit!
Leave this to me.
I'll be able to hold out, no problem.
All right.
Just... don't get too reckless.
Until I can get back to acting as support,
you're gone for good if you die.
I'm leaving this to you, Sunraku.
Sure thing.
Sorry, Pencilgon.
Ever since you mentioned the thing
about hanging in there through the time limit,
I've been thinking...
Where the hell is the fun in that?
A boss where you just turtle up for thirty minutes straight?
What kind of game would that be?
I'll say it flat-out. It's boring as shit.
Game design that puts the story first?
I've played tons of those.
Games that go for a balance between fiction and gameplay,
and fail are regularly given the "trash game" stamp.
But Shangri-La Frontier is supposed to be god-tier!
Yeah, thought so.
I had a thought when I saw that holy water attack.
In the state he's in now, he might just take damage!
A passable compromise between fiction and gameplay...
is when any player endures those first twenty minutes...
gets a turn to fight back!
What, is that your first time being parried by a helmet?
Time to unveil the new armor I created
from Quad Beetle materials.
Before you get a chance to fall apart,
I'm gonna beat you down...
Wethermon the Tombguard!
Pretty awesome, huh?
I practiced doing this move plenty.
"But why parry with a helmet," you ask?
'Cause if you can do it with your head...
it leaves your hands free!
Wind Slash!
Dammit!
That one did deal damage, right?
I landed a damn crit, and he's not even fazed.
I didn't go as hard as Pencilgon,
but I still dropped a ton of cash on you, got it?
That money-grubbing bunny...
I'm gonna use the 80,000 mahni I paid her
to rub your face into the dirt!
Vorpal Blade Tech...
Moon's Reflection!
Better watch your back, man.
Your six is wide open!
The Moon's Reflection was a bluff!
Here comes some real damage!
Assassin Pierce!
Oh, I'm just getting warmed up!
Drill Piercer!
If scars on the back are a swordsman's
greatest shame, then sorry.
I'm about to dish a whole lot.
How did I just know he'd end up in a brawl?
He's cackling like a madman over there!
Is that guy okay?!
I guess as long as the laughing goes on, he's fine.
The bigger of an underdog Sunraku is,
the more his motivation and player skill spike.
But...
if we can't hold this thing in place,
it'll be impossible for him to win.
I tried punching it a few times...
and it's looking like it'll take damage now!
Still tough as hell, though.
Okay, look.
It's not worth sticking out our necks to beat this thing.
Staying alive and drawing Kirin's aggro from Sunraku
is enough to earn us a passing grade.
A passing grade, sure.
But...
Whip Puppet: Snake!
If I'm gonna be graded, I'd rather get a perfect score!
These two, I swear...
Okay, maybe not.
I didn't leave a dent!
What's this?
Evil Force.
It increases stats for fifteen minutes!
Even in your current state,
it should give you abilities on par with level 99 or so!
Level 99?!
This is a god-tier item!
Why didn't you whip this awesome thing out earlier?!
Using it comes with a serious penalty.
I've used it before, and it was a pretty rough time.
Penalty?
I'll admit, I'm getting tired of this one-sided fight, too.
You said you want a perfect score, right?
So I'm sure you're prepared for the risk—
A penalty?
Sounds fine to me.
I'm gonna turn you to scrap and get a big ol' A-plus!
H-Huh? Why's everything suddenly in photo-negative?
I feel like my hearing's gone fuzzy, too.
It's probably also screwing with
your sense of smell and taste!
Is this the "penalty"?
Well, it does feel a little weird,
but it's not nearly as bad as I expected!
Actually... that's not the bad part.
Every thirty seconds, your level decreases by one.
Huh?
Huh? My level goes down?!
Th-This thing lasts fifteen minutes!
Does it stick around after the battle, too?!
Yeah.
I've used it myself, and the sense of loss was palpable.
If it's every thirty seconds...
For fifteen minutes... I lose thirty levels?!
So when the fight's over,
I'll have to start back from level 20?!
Why didn't you say that sooner?!
Ah, it went down...
You ate it before I could tell you!
Oh, and I'll use my remaining Scale points
to boost my own stats!
Hey!
Still, I can't believe you chewed it.
I know it's just flavor text stuff in a game,
but I learned what those are made of,
and I haven't been able to stomach one since.
What the hell did you let me eat?!
Okay, now I'm pissed!
You're gonna be my punching bag, you robot jerk!
Red plus black makes crimson!
Combo Spirit Fist: Flame Crimson!
And I'll max out my buffs.
Let's get to it, Katzo!
Infight...
into...
Dual Impact!
With my right fist, I create a cross-shaped seal...
then I pound it with a right straight punch!
Nice! You finally staggered it!
Looks like the medicine did its thing!
Now I'm gonna stab its knee until it shatters!
Spear of Sunlight!
I know it dealt damage...
but even with all those stacked buffs...
I still can't even crack it?!
Pencilgon!
Sheesh...
I wish you'd be clearer about
when your stagger phase ends!
I guess we'll need more than stat boosts
to make a breakthrough here.
Its armor seems thickest around the waist.
That's probably where all the important bits are stored.
But how the heck do we go about prying it open?
Okay!
I think I've got the hang of the head-parry-slash combo.
What's the matter, man?!
Are you that depressed that your robo-samurai
sword techniques won't work on me?!
I knew these Moonblades were a good match for me.
I've got a skill I can only activate
when my HP falls below one-third,
Climax Boost.
For five minutes after activating,
it boosts my stats in proportion
to the level gap between me and my enemy.
But I've got so little HP,
there's no way to use Wethermon's attacks
to fine-tune them down to one-third.
But...
with the Moonblades' ability to shave down
and recover my HP with every attack, I can do it.
And last but not least, Hunger Wolf.
It only lasts for one minute,
but in exchange for depleting my stamina and such,
it increases my strength, agility, and vitality!
Thunderclap!
The stat increase is in proportion to how few HP
you've got, and your "hunger" level!
Nimbus Fist!
SLF has a gauge to represent your hunger.
It fills back up when you eat,
and if you go hungry for too long,
it impacts your stamina recovery rate.
Naturally, I micromanaged that too!
I'm at just the right level of hunger!
If I can combine these skills just right, I know I can win this!
His sword's at his hip.
Another Wind Slash?!
I'll block it with a head-parry from Parry Protect!
Here it comes!
Parry!
Huh?
What the... Where's the slash?
A...
Alice.
He's an awkward one, you see.
He's a living corpse, unable to even put himself to rest.
So as you face down Wethermon the Tombguard,
I wish to entrust this to you.
Alice.
Alice?
Alice... ID key... fragment.
Alice... is still... known?
This isn't a skill incantation.
For endless eternity...
He's talking?
I have lain here... rotting...
I did not... see... their fate...
I thought he was a corpse animated by the machinery,
but maybe not?
Indeed...
the frontier... has been established...
"They"? "Frontier"?
Are they seriously giving me story stuff now?!
Let us do battle... Child of the Second Plan.
I've got every neuron in my body
hard-focused on beating you.
Don't make me think about anything else.
If you intend... to infringe upon my vow...
Then be crushed by my...
Clear Sky Conquest.
Guess he's finally getting serious!
Sounds great! Bring it on!
Wind Slash.
I thought maybe you'd changed things up,
but a normal Wind Slash—
Thunderclap.
Not a second's break between them?!
What's the big hurry, Wethermon?!
Nimbus Fist.
You kidding me?!
The freaking lightning hasn't even stopped yet!
He's chaining attacks like crazy
with basically no delay in between them.
Tidal Rush!
You can do that one with your sword in hand, too, huh?!
Wind Slash.
At the head?
The torso?!
Wind Slash.
The legs?!
Okay, I get it now!
You can spam attacks without recast time!
That's pretty messed up!
Am I supposed to anticipate every move?
That feels like pretty broken game balance.
The hell is he doing now?!
Pyroclastic Wyrm.
A new move?!
Black clouds?
Ash Blizzard!
A combo attack?!
What's the matter, man?
If you don't get me on the first hit, you miss your chance!
Still, I don't have much in the way
of stamina or dodge skills left.
If this chain attack barrage keeps up...
Well, bring it on!
I'll hang on with pure chutzpah!
It's gonna take more than this to beat me!
And I've got a few ideas of my—
Clear Sky Conquest.
Through the cycle of rebirth and a parting gift...
He's fast!
I'm already running at top speed!
I bring the ultimate end.
What the hell? My legs—
With the transformation of "clear sky..."
This isn't like his other moves.
I deal the ultimate...
I'll have to take it head-on!
I'll use this helmet to parry, no matter what!
...strike.
That which can cleave even dragons...
Sky Clear!
What the heck was that?
"Sky Clear," he called it, I guess...
But this move is way too nasty.
Will it reach?!
Wait!
But it's like I told you...
It's gonna take more than that to beat me!