SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
The Saiga Family Valentine
Mini!
SLF Theater
First, I got some chocolate bars.
Then I chopped it up.
Then I melted it with a water bath.
That all went as planned.
But what shape should I make them?
Valentine's Day chocolate for Hizutome-kun...
A-Am I really ready to give him hearts?
Well... maybe I should use that shape, then?
But just giving him his own head
would be annoying to him...
And giving him half-naked chocolate
might be a little embarrassing...
In that case...
Oh, Hizutome-kun would eat me?!
It's definitely way too soon for that!
No, no! Don't nibble me there!
Y-You're going to start there?
You're filling your mouth? That loudly?!
We're both underage!
No, it's no good.
I'll need to use a different shape.
It's too much for me, emotionally.
I-In that case...
I'll make it my sister!
But why?!
I've got myself so confused!
In that case...
I melted it in the water bath,
then reshaped it back into chocolate bars!
Even though it was tastier than store-bought, the fact
that it looked exactly like store-bought made it creepier.
By Mana Iwamaki