Putting Feelings Into a Moment, Part 4
Sky Clear
Rebirth Tearjewel
Use Items
Divine Lifesalve
Potion
High Potion
Sky                                                                 Clear
Use Items
Divine Lifesalve
Potion
High Potion
Climax Boost
Hunger Wolf
Vorpal Blade Tech
[Moon's Reflection]
Sunraku
Pencilgon
Twisted Steel Spear
Category: Spear
Durability:
Attribute: Corrode
Breakage Warning
Weapon change recommended
Spear of Sunlight
Weapon Durability Depleted
Breakage Warning
Weapon change recommended
Giant Killing Skewer
All or Nothing
Moonblade
Combination Possible
Head Equipment Changed
Staring Bird Mask
Moonblade
Combination Possible
Climax Boost
Hunger Wolf
Vorpal Blade Tech
[Moon's Reflection]
Moonblade
Twin Moon
Climax Boost
Cannot Activate
Sunraku
Endure
Hunger Wolf
STR, AGI, and VIT increase
in proportion to hunger and low HP,
but reduces Stamina, DEX, and TEC in exchange.
Climax Boost
All stats increase in proportion
to level deficiency against enemy.
Crescent Vorpal
Sky Clear