Sunraku-san... still hasn't returned.
Which means... he's still fighting.
Sunraku-san!
I guess we'll need more than stat
boosts to make a breakthrough here.
Its armor seems thickest around the waist.
That's probably where all the
important bits are stored...
But how the heck do we
go about prying it open?
I've got an idea.
Are you in?
An idea?
A surefire plan to break through
Kirin Armor's outer shell.
I call it...
Clear Sky Conquest.
That which can cleave even dragons...
Sky Clear!
What the heck was that?
"Sky Clear", he called it, I guess...
But this move is...
way too nasty.
Will it reach?!
Wait!
But it's like I told you...
It's gonna take more than that to beat me!
My ultimate technique, the self-revive!
It was a huge gamble, but I managed to
time it just right to revive myself!
Still, my equipment's not so lucky...
My Spiked Battlehelm is half trashed.
My Lifestide Sash is totally kaput.
That "Clear Sky" move
is nasty.
So it's got equipment-destroying
and armor-piercing effects...
Maybe the Insta-Death effect, too?
But...
Until you surpass my ultimate,
I shall not fall.
That stance again!
Clear Sky Conquest...
Thunderclap!
Hang on a damn minute!
We're back to the attack spam?!
Wind Slash.
Too damn close!
I get it.
That chain of attacks and
the final Sky Clear move...
All of it together makes
up "Clear Sky Conquest."
So... how do I solve it?
Last time, it took about thirty
seconds before the Sky Clear hit me.
Pyroclastic Wyrm.
There's lag time before
Pyroclastic Wyrm activates.
That one's not a huge threat.
Ash Blizzard.
Same with Ash Blizzard.
It's easy to dodge when I know it's coming!
Tidal Rush.
The moves he uses in Clear Sky
Conquest might be chosen at random,
but the actual dodging
is a memorization game!
Wind Slash.
Given all the moves in his arsenal,
the go-to strategy is to
preserve stamina and keep about
three meters from him at all times.
Thunderclap.
Keep your movements to the bare minimum.
This isn't so scary once you get used to it.
He got my leg again!
It's thirty seconds, for sure.
Now, here's the real challenge...
Sky Clear!
He's killed me plenty of times before,
but this one feels different.
It's more fundamentally...
an insta-kill attack, meant to slaughter
the player without you getting a say.
I'll bet...
Even if a level 99 player buffed
their defenses with full armor
and a shield at the ready,
he'd still split them in
half like a block of tofu.
Until you surpass my ultimate,
I shall not fall.
Clear Sky Conquest!
And the worst part of all is
that he keeps you from dodging!
Once you're rooted to the spot like that,
you don't have a choice but
to soak his Sky Clear attack.
Sky Clear!
Destroy his sword?
No, that's not a realistic option when
you're dodging the attack spam...
Same with taking down the guy himself.
That was my last Rebirth Tearjewel.
All I've got left are five Divine Lifesalves.
If the Sky Clear comes every thirty seconds,
that means I've got three
minutes left to live.
It's been less than five
minutes since Phase 3 started.
I won't make it to ten.
Until you surpass my ultimate,
I shall not fall.
Until I "surpass" it... he won't fall?
Clear Sky Conquest.
Wind Slash!
Thunderclap!
But then, the "survive ten minutes"
thing was just a theory from the start.
Right now, I'm thinking "survive the Clear
Sky Conquest" is a more likely scenario.
Sky Clear!
Solving the Sky Clear must be the
victory condition against Wethermon!
And the key to doing that
has gotta be to parry.
Against an opponent of Wethermon's caliber,
you'd need to deflect with
the timing of a critical...
You've gotta do it while rooted to one spot,
in a state where you can't
make any stance adjustments.
If you get the timing off by a millisecond,
he'll shatter your weapon.
Still, it's the only way to win.
My job right now is to work out
what I need in that final moment,
and make sure I have it at my disposal.
Soon.
Soon, I'll have everything I need...
Wait just a little while longer...
Wethermon.
Until you surpass my ultimate,
I shall not fall.
Let Sunraku-kun handle all that.
Yeah, we've got our own job to focus on.
Now, as far as your surefire way
to take down Kirin Armor goes...
It's not gonna be easy to
get him where we need him.
Can't do it, hmm?
Oh, please.
Don't go underestimating a fighting game pro.
In that case...
Get on that.
Wh-Why'd you just kill yourself?!
That took forever!
What's wrong with you?
H-Hey, that's my line!
A spear-wielder can't
fight with just one hand.
But resurrection sets me back to normal.
At least warn me first!
Now, let's start again fresh!
First, gotta find its weak spot...
The backbone linking the
top and bottom portions!
It feels just like the other parts!
Hey, hey! I'm right over here!
Not as easy to shake off this time, am I?
I've drugged myself into a major buff stack,
and I'm using two whips!
The second you lift up
the leg, the body falls!
Katzo-kun, well done!
If you wanna be a fighting
game pro in the VR game age,
you'd better know how the human body
moves under any set of circumstances!
This thing isn't really human!
It's humanoid! Basically the same thing!
Okay, and that's when...
I add more whips!
I've got you wrapped up
in every whip I've got!
I suppose that's the end of this weapon.
Adding armor-piercing buffs to your weapons
wears down their durability very quickly.
I've hit its back, arms, and legs multiple
times over the course of the fight,
but it's just as tough all over.
Still... there's one place where the
armor is tougher than the others.
That waist of yours is just too suspicious!
Katzo-kun! Move it forward!
Got it!
I won't be able to hold it for long!
Okay!
It's time to spill your guts, giant!
Spear of Sunlight!
Come on, you can hang in
there a little longer!
My buffs are about to run out, y'know!
I got it off!
Great! Then, let's finish the job!
It shredded all my whips!
The hell is this? A berserker mode?!
Looks like breaking the
waist armor set it off!
What's the plan? Fall back for a bit?
No, we press the attack.
If we just let it rampage,
one of those indiscriminate beams
or missiles might hit Sunraku-kun.
I think you can imagine
what that would lead to.
Huh? What was that?
While I was going toe-to-toe
with a unique monster,
someone couldn't even handle
distracting his pet horse?!
I'd sure love to hear all about that!
We'll be in for six months of that.
No doubt. I'd do the same thing.
Yeah, so would I.
Okay!
In that case, we've done all our prep...
So let's seal the deal
on your surefire plan!
You said it.
Time for Giant Killing!
I only have two spears left.
Boy, what a waste.
Do you know how much it
costs to make one of these?
Now's not the time to get stingy!
Must be nice to just use your fists...
Okay...
Thou art that which binds.
I am that which holds fast.
I merge with all of creation.
I find the incompatible darkness...
and strike!
Shadow Wedge!
Shadow Wedge...
It's a spell that lets you
seal a target in place
by stabbing your weapon into its shadow.
It lasts until the weapon breaks.
Given Kirin's size, that'll probably
be about five seconds from now.
We only get one chance at this!
Let's go... my last spear!
Giant Killing Skewer!
Perfect for a mammoth like
this, don't you think?!
It's time, Katzo-kun!
Okay! Hold it tight!
Pencilgon!
Drat.
It fired a missile before I locked it down?
Damn it...
That's no problem!
I said that a spear-wielder
can't fight with only one arm...
but I take that back.
Kirin Armor...
I only need one arm for you!
Go! Giant Killing!
All or Nothing!
It's all yours, Katzo-kun.
Red, Blue, Yellow.
Three colors merge.
Spirit Fist: Dark Overstrike!
Just go down already, you empty shell!
Human Pile Bunker!
Katzo-kun!
I'm 'kay.
Boy, I'm tired!
We were so screwed if
that hadn't clinched it!
I'm so drained from Dark Overstrike
that I can't move a muscle.
You're out of stamina.
Rest for a while and you'll—
How's Sunraku-kun?!
That was my last resurrection item.
I made it in time, Wethermon.
I've got everything I need now.
Hungry Wolf.
Climax Boost.
Their cooldowns are over.
And my Moonblades' fusion gauge is filled up.
Clear Sky Conquest!
In thirty seconds
you'll dish out your last Sky Clear.
Wethermon the Tombguard...
I'm gonna solve your ultimate strike
and bring on the finale!
Wind Slash!
Tidal Rush!
Nimbus Fist!
I'm using the cooldowns
to identify exactly how long his
Clear Sky Conquest has been going.
The Sky Clear is coming in two seconds.
It'll be your last Sky Clear...
Bring it on, Wethermon!
The key to beating it is the Moonblade...
Twin Moon!
The fusion of the blades
"Waxing" and "Waning."
It comes with a special effect:
the lower your stats are,
relative to your enemy's,
the greater the power and
likelihood of your criticals.
It's the best weapon possible
for these circumstances.
It raises the likelihood
that my parry will work!
And...
With the stacked effects of
Climax Boost and Hunger Wolf,
I'll raise my action speed!
With all this, I can block
his Sky Clear for sure!
I can't activate it?
I've got a skill I can only activate
when my HP fall below one-third—
I screwed up!
How'd I manage to blow my prep like this?!
I'm doomed!
I've soaked that attack
enough times to know...
Hunger Wolf alone won't let
me match the attack speed!
Think, man! There's gotta be a way!
Sunraku, think!
Think up a way!
Sky—
You guys are all so obsessed
with that Setsuna lady...
Today's major update changed
the activation conditions
for the luck-based "Endure" status...
If your luck stat is over fifty,
and your HP reaches zero due to
self-inflicted or recoil damage,
Just once, you can hang
in there with a single HP!
Clear Sky Conquest is a chain of
actions that concludes with Sky Clear.
In other words, until you release your
Sky Clear, you'll never give up...
Either on the Clear Sky Conquest action
or your oath to guard that
grave forever and ever!
On behalf of Vash, I'm putting you down!
Sky Clear!
Crescent Vorpal!
Go to sleep already...
Wethermon the Tombguard!
You were really strong...
But I've seen enough of your
attacks for a lifetime...
And your blade won't reach me ever again.
The ultimate strike has been solved.
Brilliant.
You have broken through my ultimate strike.
As "Clear Sky" transformed into
my ultimate, "Sky Clear"...
So, again, do the words transform...
to describe your talent.
"It is as clear as a cloudless sky."