Sunraku... still hasn't returned.
Which means... he's still fighting.
Sunraku!
I guess we'll need more than stat boosts
to make a breakthrough here.
Its armor seems thickest around the waist.
That's probably where all the important bits are stored.
But how the heck do we pry it open?
I've got an idea.
You in?
You do?
A sure-fire plan to break through Kirin Armor's outer shell.
I call it...
Clear Sky Conquest.
That which can cleave even dragons...
Sky Clear!
What the heck was that?
"Sky Clear," he called it, I guess...
But this move is...
way too nasty.
Will it reach?!
Wait!
But it's like I told you...
It's gonna take more than that to beat me!
My ultimate technique, the self-revive!
It was a huge gamble, but I managed to time it
just right to bring myself back!
Still, my equipment's not so lucky.
My Spiked Battlehelm is half trashed.
My Lifestide Sash is totally kaput.
That "Clear Sky" move?
It's downright vicious.
So it's got equipment-destroying
and armor-piercing effects.
Maybe the Insta-Death effect, too?
Be that as it may...
Until you surpass my ultimate, I shall not fall.
That stance again!
Clear Sky Conquest...
Thunderclap!
Hang on a damn minute!
We're back to the attack spam?!
Wind Slash.
Too damn close!
I get it now.
That chain of attacks and the final Sky Clear move...
All of it together makes up the "Clear Sky Conquest."
So... how do I solve it?
Last time, it took about thirty seconds
before the Sky Clear hit me.
Pyroclastic Wyrm.
There's lag before this skill activates.
It's not a huge threat.
Ash Blizzard.
Same with Ash Blizzard.
It's easy to dodge when I know it's coming!
Tidal Rush.
The moves he uses in the Clear Sky Conquest
might be chosen at random...
but the actual dodging is a memorization game!
Wind Slash.
Given all the moves in his arsenal,
the go-to strategy is to preserve stamina
and keep about three meters from him at all times.
Thunderclap.
Keep your movements to the bare minimum.
This isn't so scary once you get used to it.
He got my leg again!
It's thirty seconds, for sure.
Now, here's the real challenge...
Sky Clear!
He's killed me plenty of times before,
but this one feels different.
It's more like...
an insta-kill attack, meant to slaughter the player
without the means to fight back.
I'll bet...
even a level 99 player buffed their defenses
with full armor and a shield at the ready...
they'll get split in half like a block of tofu.
Until you surpass my ultimate...
I shall not fall.
Clear Sky Conquest!
And the worst part of all is that he keeps you from dodging!
Once you're rooted to the spot like that,
you don't have a choice but to soak his Sky Clear attack.
Sky Clear!
Should I go for his sword?
No, that's not a realistic option
when you're dodging the attack spam.
Same with taking down the guy himself.
That was my last Rebirth Tearjewel.
All I've got left are five Divine Lifesalves.
If the Sky Clear comes every thirty seconds,
that means I've got three minutes left to live.
It's been less than five minutes since the third phase started.
I won't make it to ten.
Until you surpass my ultimate,
I shall not fall.
Until I "surpass" it... he won't fall?
Clear Sky Conquest, Wind Slash!
Thunderclap!
But then, the whole surviving thing
was just a theory from the start.
Right now, I'm thinking "beating the
Clear Sky Conquest" is a more likely scenario.
Sky Clear!
Solving the Sky Clear must be
the win condition against Wethermon!
And the key to doing that has gotta be to parry.
Against an opponent of Wethermon's caliber,
you'd need to deflect with absolutely perfect timing.
You've gotta do it while rooted to one spot,
in a state where you can't make any stance adjustments.
If you get the timing off by even a millisecond,
he'll shatter your weapon.
Still, it's the only way to win.
My job right now is to work out
what I need in that final moment,
and make sure I have it at my disposal.
Soon, I'll have everything I need.
Wait just a little while longer...
Wethermon.
Until you surpass my ultimate,
I shall not fall.
Let Sunraku handle Wethermon.
Yeah, we've got our own problems to worry about.
Now, as far as your sure-fire way
to take down Kirin Armor goes...
It's not gonna be easy to get him where we need him.
Can't do it, hmm?
Oh, please.
Don't you underestimate a fighting game pro.
In that case...
get to it.
Wh-Why'd you just kill yourself?!
That took forever!
What's wrong with you?
H-Hey, that's my line!
A spear-wielder can't fight with just one hand.
But resurrection sets me back to normal.
At least warn me first!
Now, let's do this one more time!
First, gotta find its weak spot.
The backbone linking the top and bottom portions!
It feels just like the other parts!
Hey, hey! I'm right over here!
Not as easy to shake off this time, am I?
I've drugged myself into a major buff stack...
and I'm using two whips!
The second you lift up the leg, the body falls!
Well done, Katzo!
If you wanna be a fighting game pro in the VR game age,
you'd better know how the human body moves
under any set of circumstances!
This thing ain't really human, though!
It's humanoid! Basically the same thing!
Okay, and that's when...
I add more!
I've got you wrapped up in every whip I've got!
That's that for this weapon, I guess.
Adding armor-piercing buffs to your weapons
wears down their durability very quickly.
I've hit its back, arms, and legs
multiple times over the course of the fight,
but it's just as tough all over.
Still... there's one place
where it's particularly thicker than the rest.
That waist of yours is just too suspicious!
Katzo! Move it forward!
Got it!
I won't be able to hold it for long!
Okay!
It's time to spill your guts, you big oaf!
Spear of Sunlight!
Come on, hang in there a little longer!
My buffs are about to run out, y'know!
I got it off!
Great! Then, let's finish the job!
It shredded all my whips!
The hell is this? A berserker mode?!
Looks like breaking the waist armor set it off!
What's the plan? Fall back for a bit?
No, we press the attack.
If we just let it rampage,
any one of those beams and missiles
will probably hit Sunraku.
I think you've got a good idea what'll happen next.
Huh? What was that?
While I was going toe-to-toe with a unique monster,
someone couldn't even handle distracting his pet horse?!
I'd sure love to hear all about that!
We'll be in for six months of that.
No doubt. I'd do the same thing.
Yeah, so would I.
Okay!
In that case, we've done all the prep work.
So let's seal the deal on that plan of yours!
You said it.
Time to thrash this tin can!
I only have two spears left.
Boy, what a waste.
Do you know how much it costs to make one of these?
Now's not the time to get stingy!
Must be nice to only be using fists as weapons.
Okay...
Thou art that which binds.
I am that which holds fast.
I merge with all of creation.
I find the incompatible darkness...
and strike!
Shadow Wedge!
Shadow Wedge.
It's a spell that lets you seal a target in place
by stabbing your weapon into its shadow.
It lasts until the weapon breaks.
Given Kirin's size, that'll probably be
about five seconds from now.
We only get one chance at this!
I'll use... my last spear!
Giant Killing Skewer!
Perfect for a mammoth like this, don't you think?!
It's time, Katzo!
Okay! Hold it tight!
Pencilgon!
Drat.
It fired a missile before I locked it down?
Dammit...
Katzo, don't!
I said that a spear-wielder can't fight with only one arm.
I take that back.
Kirin Armor...
one arm is all I need to take you on!
Go! Giant Killing!
All or Nothing!
It's all yours, Katzo.
Red, Blue, Yellow.
Three colors, merge.
Spirit Fist: Dark Overstrike!
Just go down already, you hunk of scrap!
Human Pile Bunker!
Katzo!
I'm 'kay.
Boy, I'm tired!
We were so screwed if that hadn't clinched it!
I'm so drained from Dark Overstrike
that I can't move a muscle.
You're out of stamina.
Rest for a while and you'll—
How's Sunraku?!
That was my last resurrection item.
I made it in time, Wethermon.
I've got everything I need now.
Hunger Wolf.
Climax Boost.
Their recast time is over.
And my Moonblades' fusion gauge is filled up.
Clear Sky Conquest!
In thirty seconds...
you'll dish out your last Sky Clear.
Wethermon the Tombguard...
I'm gonna surpass your ultimate strike
and end this phase once and for all!
Wind Slash!
Tidal Rush!
Nimbus Fist!
I'm using my recast time to keep tabs on exactly how long
his Clear Sky Conquest has been going.
The Sky Clear is coming in two seconds.
And it'll be your last.
Bring it on, Wethermon!
The key to beating it is the Moonblade...
Twin Moon!
The fusion of the blades "Waxing" and "Waning."
It comes with a special effect.
The lower your stats are relative to your enemy's,
the greater the power and likelihood of your crits.
It's the best weapon possible for these circumstances.
It raises the likelihood that my parry will go through!
And with the stacked effects
of Climax Boost and Hunger Wolf,
I'll raise my agility!
With all this, I can block his Sky Clear for sure!
I can't activate it?
I've got a skill I can only activate
when my HP falls below one-third.
I screwed up!
How'd I manage to blow my prep like this?!
I'm doomed!
I've soaked that attack enough times to know.
Hunger Wolf alone ain't fast enough
to match his attack speed!
Think, man! There's gotta be a way!
Sunraku, think!
Something, anything!
Sky—
You guys are all so obsessed with that Setsuna lady.
Today's major update changed the trigger conditions
for the luck-based "Endure" status.
If your luck stat is over fifty,
and your HP reaches zero
due to self-inflicted or recoil damage,
just once, you can hang in there with a single HP!
Clear Sky Conquest is a chain of actions
that concludes with Sky Clear.
In other words, until you release that attack,
you'll never give up.
Either on the Clear Sky Conquest action
or your oath to guard that grave forever and ever!
On behalf of Vash, I'm putting you down!
Sky Clear!
Crescent Vorpal!
Go to sleep already...
Wethermon the Tombguard!
You were really strong,
but I've seen enough of your attacks to last me a lifetime...
And your blade won't reach me ever again.
I've broken through your ultimate strike.
Brilliant.
You have indeed surpassed it.
As "Clear Sky" transformed into my ultimate, "Sky Clear"...
So, again, do the words transform... to describe your talent.
"It is as clear as a cloudless sky."