Awesome...
That's gotta be high-level
equipment... right?
And that crest...
It's from that achievement-focused
clan, right?
What's someone like that doing
here in the starting town?
I'd heard Hizutome-kun gives all
his characters the same name,
so I thought I'd be able to find him...
Since there's no way a starting
player wouldn't come to this town...
Maybe I just missed him.
Give me something to enjoy here,
SLF!
First, let's watch your patterns.
It's still a boss for beginners.
Its movements are easy to read,
and it won't have any
insta-kill moves!
I can beat this thing without taking a hit.
Since even one hit would kill me anyway!
I knew your durability was getting low,
but did you just break on your first hit?!
I was getting attached to
these little guys, too!
A tough hide, eh?
In that case...
I've got something I'd like to try out.
I'll make you into snake fillets!
Screw Pi—
Wh-What the heck is this?
Poop?!
Well, hmm.
I might've underestimated this thing.
Well, don't you look proud of yourself?
I'll have you know,
I've beaten trash games with
mechanics way cheaper than this.
A little poop-flinging won't
be enough to get me down!
The poison deals me one
damage every ten seconds.
Which means I've got about four minutes left.
I'll need a reliable way to land
criticals if I wanna make it in time!
Criticals in this game
don't trigger at random.
They seem to trigger when you
land an attack in an ideal way,
or hit an enemy in their weak point.
This thing's covered in tough scales...
In other words, the only weak point
has gotta be the head!
Still, it's hard to land a hit there!
In that case...
I'll have to make my own weak point!
Screw Pierce!
Yes!
Now, stack more hits on the wound!
The defensive properties of
a wounded section change,
allowing criticals to trigger there!
Now, just hack away until
my stamina gives out!
Crud! I don't even know how
much HP this thing has!
Am I even gonna make it?!
Yeah...
Beating Failia Chronicle
made me pretty cocky.
"It's just a mass-appeal game for casuals..."
"I can no-hit this thing easy,
no need for recovery items..."
That's what I thought.
I was arrogant.
But...
Flash Counter!
You're not gonna eat me that easily!
You're gonna regret covering
me with your poop!
Screw Pierce!
Heck yeah!
I freaking did it!
You see that, poopsnake?!
I bet these dropped items
could fetch some major dough!
Oh, crap! I'm still running out of time!
Is that all the loot it dropped?
I didn't miss anything?
I gotta distribute my level-up points...
No, there's no time!
Just dump it all into stamina and agility!
The minute I get to town,
I'll buy an antidote...
Wait, I dunno where the shops are!
I won't make it!
I'd better register my respawn point first!
That'd be an inn, right?
But I don't know where
that is either, damn it!
You want to tame a dog-type
monster, right, Mia?
Yeah.
I'm not allowed to have pets in my apartment,
but I know you can have monsters
as pets in this game...
So I hope you'll help me
out today, Yamamoto-kun!
After three months of trying,
I finally got the girl I'm crushing
on to start playing SLF with me!
And I've maneuvered myself into the
role of the advice-giving veteran!
I can't let this chance pass me by!
Um... Yamamoto-kun?
S-Sorry, it's nothing!
Mia, game etiquette dictates that
we don't use real-life names here.
We use character names.
Oh, really?
Reiji-kun, then, right?
Yes!
I even got her calling me by my given name!
I owe you big, SLF!
What's that?
A monster?!
Wait, wait!
It's got a character name!
It's not a monster, it's a player!
So I shouldn't attack?
If you PK, you'll end up with
a skull in front of your name!
I wouldn't want that...
But what's he running like that for, then?
I bet he got hit with that poison poop.
Hey!
You, over there! Sunraku!
Keep going straight! That white
building there is the inn!
But your respawn point won't register
until you get into the bed,
so be careful!
Thanks, man!
You saw this a lot back
when the game started,
before there was a whole
lot of fan documentation...
Players who got poisoned by that snake
and had to run full-tilt into town.
Looking at the guy,
I'm betting he's going for an agility build
and sold off his armor at the start.
Reiji-kun, you sounded like a
real veteran just now! I love it.
You think?
Thanks, Mr. Bluebird!
You want to stay the night, then?
We provide places of sanctuary
where pioneers can rest easy.
For instance—
Skip the explanation and rent me a dang bed!
Understood.
I'll see if I can find you an free roo—
Hurry up!
Hur! Ry! Up!
I'm down to my last HP, here!
Please proceed to room 102, then.
Right, thanks!
Heck yeah!
Respawn point registered.
I made i—
That was close!
I made it just in time.
Still, I ended up dead.
I'm just glad I didn't lose my items.
That player who told me where the inn was...
I'm gonna have to thank him
the next time I see him.
Still... SLF, the god-tier game.
It's pretty darn cool!
All righty...
Secondale here is my first
SLF town experience.
I'll need a map, some recovery items,
and new equipment.
I'll need a powerful main weapon
to replace my Mercenary Twinblade!
I wanna give this thing
all I've got, after all!
I'm gonna hit the top player ranks!
Who is that half-naked bird-man?
A player?
Looks like a meme build or something.
Scary!
Yeah, maybe I'll buy clothes first.
I'll take the cheapest thing you've got.
Thank you for your patronage!
I'm not in this for the DEF.
I just want the other players to
stop treating me like a weirdo.
Now, the matching headpiece...
Maybe I'll pass.
Oh? A Goblin Hand Axe?
You expect me to buy this garbage?
Yeah, I guess that figures.
Show me your lineup of weapons, then.
Sure thing.
Nothing too hot here.
My Vorpal Choppers are way better.
Well, the Vorpal Chopper
is a pretty rare weapon.
Oh, I was wondering about that.
If you want something to top
that, I'd have to make it.
You can make me stuff?
If you bring me materials.
The path from Secondale to
the third city, Thirdrema,
passes through the Diremarsh Waste.
There's a location within
it where ores can be mined.
So if I bring him some ore from
here, he'll make me a weapon.
One, two...
Another Stone?!
Where's all the stupid ore?!
He said I'd need five or six
pieces to make a good weapon...
But I've been swinging this pickax for
thirty minutes and I've only got two!
Plus the marsh mud makes it hard to move...
And this pickax I bought to do the mining...
is too darn heavy!
What do you want?
Buzz off already. I've got stuff to do!
Okay. I get the picture.
Since you weren't being aggressive,
I thought we could coexist...
But if you wanna be turned
into materials that bad,
I'll oblige!
How do you like that, dummy frog?!
Now I'll finish you off!
The Splitblade Leather armor I'm wearing now
is made from Mud Frog Skin,
and it has slash resistance.
So it's pretty likely slash attacks
won't work on froggy here, either.
Which means my only options are
bludgeon and pierce attacks!
And so...
It's time for my Goblin Hand Axe,
whose edge is so blunt it actually
deals bludgeon damage, to shine!
This is taking forever!
Why can't I run in this stupid marsh?!
The marsh slows down player
movement significantly,
forcing them into a walking state.
With a body shape like that, I bet it
can't get off its back very easily!
That was so easy, it didn't even cheer me up.
Back to mining, I guess.
It's a pain, but...
It'll be fine.
I'm seeing more new players around...
There's no way we can do it at night.
Sure we can!
No way, no way!
We totally can! You can't be afraid to try!
I'll probably be seeing more soon,
with summer break starting.
Which means it's only a matter of time
before the race for materials begins.
If I don't wanna get caught up in that,
I'd better collect as much
as I can, while I can!
W-Wow.
You got quite a lot in just three hours!
It's gotta be enough to make
something pretty good, huh?
Hold on. I'll bring up the list.
Hey, hey...
You've got a Marshcoffin Fossil!
Yeah, I remember picking up that weird thing.
I can use that to make this!
Hey, nice.
I'll take it, then.
And make it a double!
Sure thing.
I'll have them made right away.
There you are. A pair of Marsh Daggers!
Wow, god-tier weapons!
And halving durability reduction
for a time after a critical
makes them perfect for my playstyle!
Make sure to find and bring
back even more materials.
Raising your weapons is part of our job, too.
"Raising" my weapons?
Users of forging magic like me
can do more than just make weapons.
We can also upgrade them.
But see, weapons are like
children to a blacksmith,
so we prefer to say we "raise" them
to uncouth concepts like "upgrade."
I get it!
By the way, I gotta say,
the NPC speech and mannerisms
here are something else.
He's having a properly responsive
conversation with me.
What kind of AI does this thing use?
Oh, hey, it's getting dark.
Make sure you don't leave
town in armor like that.
How come?
Because nocturnal monsters
are dangerous, of course.
Oh, the game's got that going on, huh?
Got it. I'll be careful.
Sure, see you later!
That's what I told him...
But my penalty for dying's already passed.
And I got some good info!
Heck yeah!
Time to use those
"dangerous nocturnal monsters"
to break in my new weapons
and pile on some levels!
Curious.
I've searched the entire beginners' area.
Highest Strength Enchant Hell Flame...
Apocalypse!
The only remaining possibility
is that he managed to defeat this snake
without stopping by town or dying
and headed for Secondale...
Could a brand-new player really
accomplish such a thing?
Well, Hizutome-kun... probably could.
Not bad at all!
Okay... let's lay out what I've learned.
First, monster spawns change
based on if it's day or night.
Most nocturnal monsters are as aggressive
and dangerous as the weapons seller said.
That's helped me to make
progress leveling up,
and to learn some new skills, too.
But...
this particular guy seems a
little too powerful, doesn't he?!
It's totally broken!
This thing's movement and attacks are on a
whole other level from the forest Goblins!
It's got lots of HP, and incorporates
feints into its fighting style
like it's been doing it all its life!
But the worst part of all...
Oh, come on!
Call Allies is supposed to
be a weak monster ability!
I had enough trouble with one,
but look at all these!
Even running away at full
tilt, I might not survive...
Running away?
Hey, man, are you losing it?
Are you enjoying this, or aren't you?!
Is that all you got?!
Give me even more to enjoy!
I've been underestimating this game.
I've been having a lot of fun.
I've been telling myself,
"god-tier games are pretty neat."
You could even say I was getting into it.
But this game...
SLF has way more to offer!
On this day, in this instant...
I encountered the true Shangri-La Frontier.
Unique monster, Lycagon the
Nightslayer, encountered.
Unique... monster?