Starting Town
Firstia
The Rampant Forest
Sugar
Kit
Orga
Hades
Jaffrey
Ninto
Lily
Bolbol
Kalbo
Meina
Breo
A Peculiar One
Ravenous Python
Area Boss
Rec. Level:
Rec. Party Size:
Tap Step
Adds a bonus to evasion.
Status Effect
Poison
Take damage every ten seconds.
Status Effect
Poison
Take damage every ten seconds.
Sunraku
Poison
Shelve Weapon
Dropped Item
Python Scale
Python White Hair
Sunraku
Poison
Reiji
Mia
*Tame = To befriend and domesticate an animal
Sunraku
PK = Player Kill: To kill another player
Mia
Inn
Respawn point registered.
Sunraku
Poison
Death Penalty
All stats temporarily reduced.
Town Before the Swamp
Secondale
Bar
Florist
Armor Shop
Splitblade Leather
Equipment Set
Leather clothing made
from Mud Frog Skin.
Grants slash resistance.
4000 mahni
Splitblade Leather Mask
Weapon Shop
A sword forged from Gray Ore.
A simple, straightforward weapon.
Iron Dagger
A dagger forged from Gray Ore.
A simple, straightforward weapon.
Iron Spear
A hammer forged from Gray Ore.
A simple, straightforward weapon.
Wood Staff
A staff made from wood.
A simple, straightforward weapon.
Stone Staff
Fossil Rod
A rod made from some kind of fossil.
Extremely fragile.
Wood Shield
A shield made from wood.
A simple, straightforward shield.
Diremarsh Waste
Secondale
Stone
A completely unremarkable piece of rock.
Gray Ore
Has no special characteristics,
but can be put to various uses.
Mud Frog
It protects itself
with a coating of mud
Dropped Item
Mud Frog Skin
Marsh Dagger
Weapon Shop Avenue
Item Shop Avenue
Marsh Daggers
After landing a critical, reductions to
durability are temporarily halved.
A CHARACTER CONTROLLED BY THE COMPUTER.
Weapon Shop
Redcap Goblin
Unique Monster
Lycagon the Nightslayer
Encountered
Unique Monsters Dispatched: 0
World Story
Progress: 0%