This world is filled with
too many games to count,
though the vast majority simply
come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of all games
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide—
Shangri-La Frontier, which rightly
earns the title of "god-tier game"!
One lover of trash games, Rakuro Hizutome,
is trying out the god-tier
game, Shangri-La Frontier!
What adventures await him there?
Okay, let's get climbing!
Wait for me, Crystal Scorpions!
First, I'll use Moon Jumper to
boost my vertical jumping power.
Then... Six-Boat Leap!
Over-level-100 monsters,
the Crystal Scorpions...
I gotta find out what they are!
It'd be pretty rude not to
say hi while I'm in the area!
What, you expect me to find out about an
unexplored area filled with unknown monsters
and just forget about it?!
What's the point of playing games
if you can't go buck wild?!
Hey, would you look at that?
It's way more fantastical
than the area down below...
Really hard to make progress...
The footing's just terrible.
Okay, let's find those Crystal
Scorpions I've heard so much a—
So they're the type to camouflage
into the field, huh?
You're the one I'm here
to see, Crystal Scorpion!
Too damn close!
This thing's like a runaway train!
Guess it utilizes the field's awful footing
to drive the players into a dead end, huh?
Well, what's the matter?
Is a straight-up charge
the only trick you know?
My first time around,
I'm just here to say hi.
I don't expect to beat the
thing in my current state.
Scout out the area, take back
any rare materials I find—
That's my mission today!
If I can do that, I'll take it as a win...
Huh?
They're a bunch of tough
nuts not even I could crack.
Crystal Scorpions attack as a swarm,
so if one sees you, you're dead.
Yeah...
Okay, I'm dead.
I wonder when Sunraku-san
might finally return...
Oh, what if he's unable
to return to Rabituza?!
Perhaps I should have waited for
him in Eighthold after all?!
Freaking damn it!
That's too many of those
stupid scorpion jerks!
Hey, Emul!
Can I get a gate back to Eighthold?
Sunraku-san...
You have been fighting the
Crystal Scorpions, haven't you?!
Ah, crud.
We told you the
Crystal Scorpions were dangerous!
Man, this sucks.
What did you just say?!
Here you are! The carrot I promised you!
Hooray!
Truly delicious!
You're so predictable, it's kind of scary.
Okay, I'm gonna give it another go.
Really, must you go?
I can't hang it up until
I get something out of it.
And this won't be my first visit.
I won't die empty-handed.
Okay... let's move slow and keep hidden.
I noticed a pretty interesting spot last time.
Hey, there it is.
I got a glimpse at it
just before they got me.
A shiny li'l number that's
just begging for my pickax.
I bet it gives up items unique to this area!
Damn it! I'm not giving up!
I'm gonna get me some loot, no matter what!
That one went by fast.
It's no use.
They're so big, and so fast...
And they overwhelm you with numbers in an
area that's already hard to maneuver in.
How am I supposed to survive that?
It's just as we told you, yes!
Yeah... but I also told you something, Emul.
I won't die empty-handed.
Let's have a look.
Let's have a look!
"Aroncaleth Hard Lapis"
"Produced via repeated compression and
refinement through ingestion
by geophagic monsters,
this crystal possesses an
extremely dense magic content.
Its beautiful blue color
recalls the land itself."
I dunno what I'd use it for,
but it's gotta be worth more
than what I spent to get it.
I'm gonna check the game guide site later!
Are you satisfied now?
Maybe.
I hate to give up here, but I should
probably take a break for the day.
Yes, you should have a nice sleep!
The Crystal Scorpions...
The slightest vibration on the
crystals gets them swarming you.
Though the AI's not particularly clever...
Go to sleep, go to sleep,
They just charge at me mindlessly, so...
beneath your bunny's ears...
When they collided, they tore
off each other's carapace...
Hang on a freaking minute here!
Could I get the torn-off
carapace bits as an item?!
Man, I wanna find out!
Now that I got the idea, I wanna find out!
Emul, open the gate!
I'm going back!
What? You still haven't given up?
They're just going to kill you again!
As long as there's unknowns out there,
a pioneer must never fear death!
You're clearly fueled by greed.
But... even if I could pick it up,
how would I go about doing it?
It was pretty much luck that
let me recover that mineral...
Honestly.
The mana used to open gates
isn't free, you know!
That's it!
You just gave me a great idea, Emul!
That'll work just fine!
Wh-What are you going to do?!
Just you wait!
I'm gonna take that Crystal Scorpion
minefield swarming with
level-100-plus monsters...
and turn it into a walk in the park!
Please put me down now!
What's wrong, buddy? I'm right here!
So scary!
Oh, gosh, I'm surrounded!
What do I do? I'm in so much trouble!
Just kidding.
Six-Boat Leap!
Okay, great!
Carapace breakage confirmed!
You wanna run me through
the scorpion blender, huh?
Part of me would like to find
out what that feels like,
but it might be kinda traumatic,
so I'll pass this time.
Enter Travel!
Three cheers for civilization! Inventoria!
Technology always gets the last laugh!
I got the idea from watching
Emul use that item.
I can move myself instantly to the Inventoria,
like I'd transmit an item or a weapon.
That means I can create myself
a safe space wherever I need it!
This Inventoria thing is seriously
OP if you use it right!
Now... guess it's time to head back.
Exit Travel!
Hell yeah!
Just like I thought,
the Crystal Scorpions cleared out!
Time to loot all the spoils!
Materials from monsters that
tough have gotta be pretty rare!
Bet you Bilac could make
something awesome out of them!
I'm so awesome! I'm a genius!
I'm gonna make materials
out of every one of you!
Come at me in the tens or the hundreds!
Just you wait, Bilac!
I'm gonna have a huge collection for you!
Players have a hard limit
on inventory capacity.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
If you carry too much, it gets
too heavy, and slows you down.
But...
The Inventoria lets you store unlimited
objects with no penalty at all!
Yay! Yay! Unlimited!
So if you use it just right...
I can get unlimited materials from
the over-level-100 Crystal Scorpions!
You rock, Inventoria!
I just hide out in the Inventoria until
the Crystal Scorpions' aggro dies down...
Then I return to the real world when the
heat's off, and would you look at that?
The Crystal Scorpions are gone,
back to hiding in the scenery,
and the ground is littered with items
generated from their infighting!
Figuring out these little tricks
is what I love about gaming!
I'm gonna get so many valuable materials!
Although...
Looks like I'm pretty low on MP.
I'm down to my last use of the Inventoria.
But I still got tons of sweet item drops!
I'll do one last run, then head back.
Still, there's something so satisfying
just looking through rare items...
Eh? What's this?
Wait a minute!
I still don't have a stinger?
You can't fight a scorpion and
not get a stinger, can you?
It's kind of the most defining feature!
Maybe the stinger's too sturdy to
tear off just from basic infighting?
Seems pretty plausible, which means...
The Crystal Scorpion's stinger
could be the rare drop!
Okay, I get it.
I definitely wanna get me one of those.
But...
In order to get that rare drop,
I'm gonna have to face a horde
of level-100-plus monsters,
in a place with awful footing,
and pinpoint target the stinger.
And the part I'm after is so super-tough
that normal attacks won't break it off.
C'mon, guys.
This is some trash game-tier stuff, y'know?
But that's what's gonna make it fun!
Let's get it done!
I'm gonna tear off your precious
stinger, no matter what it takes!
On my honor as a trash gamer!
Even with my buff stack, it's a no-go?!
Figures it'd be that tough!
Didn't even leave a crack!
I had a feeling I might
need some help on this.
I'll have to get their attacks
to focus on a single stinger!
I can't fully control my enemies' attacks.
Getting the best possible pull out
of the random number generator...
That's what being a gamer is about!
Dodge the stingers' attacks.
Land.
Stay to the very last second to
lure the other scorpions' attack...
Yes, that could do it!
I only get one chance at this.
Enter Travel!
Then right back to reality!
Perfect placement!
You rock, Goddess of RNG!
Now that the stinger's pretty busted...
Glowing Pierce!
Just break already!
Yeah! How you like that?!
That's what I can do when
I put my mind to it!
Got me a rare drop!
The second I claim it,
even if I'm insta-killed,
I'll still get to keep the...
Hey. Hang on.
Huh?
I'm not as close as I thought I was.
Huh? You're kidding me, right?
I almost had it.
If my trajectory had been
just a little different,
I could've had it.
Hey, you listening? Goddess of RNG?
Why you gotta be so cruel?
A-Are you all right, Sunraku-san?!
You haven't moved this whole time,
and you seem to be trembling...
Yeah...
I can break off the scorpion's stinger,
and it's possible to retrieve it.
I know that now, so... I guess that's enough.
It's enough. Yeah, it is.
Like hell it is!
It doesn't mean jack if
I don't get the thing!
Screw you, Goddess of RNG! You totally suck!
Missing it when you almost had it is the
biggest psychological blow you can take!
And despite getting stuck
in the scorpion blender,
why didn't it tear up the Staring Bird Mask?!
Was it a miracle? Why is that
where I pull the miracle RNG?!
It actually kinda makes me more pissed!
Sunraku-san has grown rather unstable.
That pissed me off way too much.
I don't wanna look at any
more scorpions for a while.
There's only one way to
bounce back from this.
Wh-What is is?
I'm gonna brag to Bilac
about the materials I got
and bathe in her praise!
I just know she'll appreciate how
valuable these materials are!
Time is money! Let's go, Emul!
R-Righty-o...
Nothing beats the moment when you brag
to someone about your accomplishments!
That's rather perverse thinking!
Sorry, but I take that as a compliment!