Rare Items, Worth More Than Life Itself
Moon Jumper
Crystal Nest Cliff
Crystal Scorpion
Crystal Scorpions
Respawn
Rabituza
Overheat
Climax Boost
Nitro Gain
Aroncaleth Hard Lapis
Produced via repeated compression and
refinement through ingestion by
geophagic monsters, refinement through ingestion
by geophagic monsters, its beautiful blue color
recalls the land itself.
I want materials
Six-Boat Leap
Enter Travel
Inventoria
Exit Travel
Dropped Item
Crystal Leg
Crystal Scorpion's Carapace
Dropped Item
Crystal Pincer
Crystal Talon
Inventoria Key
Dropped Item
Crystal Leg
Crystal Scorpion's Carapace
Dropped Item
Crystal Pincer
Crystal Talon
Sunraku
Crystal Leg
Crystal Talon
Crystal Pincer
Crystal Scorpion's Carapace
Aroncaleth Hard Lapis
Lapisteria Stellar Crystal
Amurcidian Quartz
Crystalline Sand
Lowenanva Amber Crystal
Overheat
Climax Boost
Nitro Gain
Overheat
Climax Boost
Nitro Gain
Overheat
Climax Boost
Nitro Gain
Glowing Pierce
Random Number
Generator