SLF Theater!
SLF Mini
Records of Battles With Lycagon
Mini!
Equip
Cannot equip.
Curse you, Lycagon!
What now? Still wasting your time on that?
There could be a glitch that gives a
fraction-of-a-percent chance of breaking
through Lycagon's curse to put on armor.
Well, dreaming is free.
Everything past that will cost you.
So stingy!
Speaking of, quite a few people
have fought Lycagon, right?
It's just that no one's beaten it.
Yeah, that's true.
Momo-cha—
Someone I know is pretty passionate about it.
But they haven't beaten it?
Just don't mention that her.
I have, of course.
You...
So, just for my edification,
how did this person fight it?
Well, from what I've heard,
they came at it with a V formation,
but it got behind them and blew
them away like bowling pins.
Then they tried the Dynamite
Bone-in Muscle Burst.
Momo-chan said that one
went pretty well, I think.
The what?
Oh, would you look at the time?
Sorry, I've got an early
morning. Better log out.
Hey! Wait a minute!
You can't just not explain that one!
Dynamite Bone-in Muscle Burst?
S-Sunraku-san, what are you doing?
Bone-in meat and a muscle burst!
Bone-in meat and a muscle burst?!
So I just need the dynamite.
An explosion.
That's where you come in, Emul.
Wh-What are you going to get me to do?
Explosion? Are you going to explode me?!
You're going to become the dynamite!
No!