The 300-Limit Pandemonium
Unique Scenario
Invitation From Rabituza
Practical Training  Opponent 10
Aberrant Woodmage
Clear Condition
Survive for five minutes
Practical Training  Opponent 10
Aberrant Woodmage
Level 120
Sunraku
Drain          Exhaustion         Speed↓
Title
Honorary Rabituzan
acquired.
Vorpal Soul Collar
lost.
Accessory
Unique Scenario
Invitation From Rabituza
cleared.
Bonus Unique Scenario
Vorpal Epic
Begin now?
No  Yes
Bonus Unique Scenario
Vorpal Epic
When the souls of the Divinity are shaken,
a rabbit shall tell an epic tale.
Rec. Level: 80
Level 31
Peatz
Staring Bird Mask
equipped
Sunraku
Ritual Medjed Keffiyeh
Prismatic Forest Grotto
Fellfate Caldera
Iron Ruins of the Divinity