This world is filled with
too many games to count,
though the vast majority simply
come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of all games
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide—
Shangri-La Frontier, which rightly
earns the title of "god-tier game"!
One lover of trash games, Rakuro Hizutome,
is trying out the god-tier
game, Shangri-La Frontier!
What adventures await him there?
You beat the ninth already, did you?
Guess it's perfect timing.
Vash?
Dadd—I mean, Boss!
I thought I'd make your tenth
opponent a monster I caught.
I went on a bit of an excursion for it.
A human? Yeah, don't think so...
A sorcerer type?
One of those dummies from
long, long, long ago
who tried to fuse with a
tree to gain longer life.
I doubt you can beat him
in the state you're in now,
so I'll pick a different win criteria.
What's that?
Survive five minutes.
Unique Scenario.
"Invitation From Rabituza."
Practical training, opponent 10:
Aberrant Woodmage.
Clear condition update:
survive for five minutes.
An endurance battle, huh?
Five minutes is really all I need?
So if I just stay in motion—
Was that attack even telegraphed?
I'm a fan of your confidence, kid,
but I'd like to see you back it up.
I get it! This might be a long five minutes!
The hell is this thing made of?!
Physical attacks won't work on it?!
Guess I've just gotta dodge my ass off!
One minute has passed!
You have four remaining, Sunraku-san!
Now, show me every last bit
of your vorpal soul.
Aberrant Woodmage.
To put it lightly...
This guy's a beast!
Root-spear attacks that
are barely telegraphed...
Chains that look like they'll
debuff you on contact...
Both chase me around like it's
their natural right to catch me,
which really does a number
on my will to keep dodging.
But the worst part of all...
is these magic attacks he slips
in there every now and then!
Not to mention...
that the more time passes,
the more he mixes up the magic types!
Is the battle programmed so
the attacks get denser, too?!
The number of chains and roots increases,
and the magic attacks start
covering a wider area.
If the density of the
attacks keeps increasing...
I'm gonna be dead before
I ever reach five minutes!
Another new spell for his arsenal?!
The hell is this thing?
He nullifies physical attacks and
constantly adds attacks of his own?!
I think I'd stand a better
chance against Lycagon!
Talk about hell for a first-time encounter.
This is hopeless.
I can barely think. I'm so tired.
I'm gonna get some carbs in me,
think up a strat and try again.
It's not like I'm penalized
if I die or anything.
Who cares...
Hang on, man.
What's got you writing
yourself off all of a sudden?
Since when have you been such a pushover?
I don't expect to go ten
in a row on my first try.
Nah, I'm done for.
I'm totally screwed.
It was the same with the Mud Digger.
You relied on Emul.
You gave up just like that.
Next thing you know,
you're cutting corners all over the place.
What a mess.
I think playing so many trash games
almost turned my brain to trash, too.
Sunraku-san!
I guess it's not good to
overdose on trashgamium.
I've gotta even it out with some godgamium!
Giving up when it's not
a forced loss event...
or cutting corners on a game that
hasn't been broken wide open yet...
just doesn't make any sense!
Breaking through the waves of
attacks to reach melee range, eh?
But what's the point, when all he
can do is dish out basic strikes?
I'm tired, damn it!
So...
I'm gonna win this thing
and go the frick to bed!
Even if you nullify physical damage,
the attack itself still gets through, I'll bet.
That's a pretty fancy staff for
a monster to be carrying around.
I wonder what'll happen if
you've gotta do without it!
Looks to me like you can't cast without it!
In a post-apocalyptic world,
you survive by looting!
The shakedown skills I
learned in Unite Rounds
are not to be trifled with!
Those are some sticky fingers
you've got there, kid.
But you've got two minutes left.
I don't think you want
to be breathing easy yet.
Now, show me what you can do.
Losing the staff is your
berserk button, huh?!
That's too many damn attacks!
You're kidding me!
A tantrum like this over one little staff?!
Give a little warning before
you go off like this, damn it!
Sunraku-san, you're so close!
Only one minute remains!
Dodge, evade, withdraw, and run!
My mobility build is built for this!
I'm not gonna just die
after getting this close!
A wall?
Not good!
Figured those chains would
be debuff generators.
And they've got enough punch
to override Lycagon's Mark...
I won't be able to dodge like this.
Give it back!
You want it back that badly...
Then go get it, asshole!
Dude, did you actually go fetch it?
You're such a dumbass.
You didn't need the silly staff.
You'd have won if you'd kept
the roots and chains coming.
What a blockhead. A woodblock head, even.
Eh?
Hang on a minute! I survived five minutes!
Isn't it over?!
Well, the five minutes was my idea, not his.
It's right on the line,
but I guess I'll pass you!
You certainly showed me
your vorpal soul, in spades.
Huh? I thought he nullified physical attacks?
You've done it!
I simply knew you would, Sunraku-san!
That's only when he's holding the staff.
Without the staff he's just an animated tree.
Well, that explains why
he wanted it back so bad!
And... hey, does that mean I beat the quest?!
Sure does.
And you'll get your reward.
Finally!
I hearby declare you an Honorary Rabituzan.
Simply spectacular, Sunraku-san!
Yay! Yay!
Well... that's nice and all...
But doesn't it come with
a rare item or something?
Oh, that's right.
I almost forgot.
I'm sure you won't need that anymore.
Well, be seeing you again soon.
Unique scenario, Invitation
From Rabituza, cleared.
W-Wait!
I don't get to keep it?!
Bonus unique scenario,
Vorpal Epic. Begin now?
Not a single piece of real loot?!
Sheesh, it's the middle of the night.
"When the souls of the Divinity tremble,
a rabbit shall tell an epic tale"... huh?
Yeah, I'm not following a word of that.
The bonus unique scenario I
just spawned, "Vorpal Epic"...
I hit "yes" to accept the quest,
but I don't know how to kick it off.
Plus, the recommended level is 80...
"Divinity"...
I think that was on the guide site.
It's that civilization that died
out a long time ago, right?
All the lore and speculation got
pretty overwhelming, though,
so I backed out of that pretty quick.
Pulling usable info from
that mess won't be easy.
There're whole clans dedicated
to finding out the game lore,
so no wonder there's a ton
of stuff to sift through.
Maybe I'll put the unique
stuff on hold for now,
check out the town and then
head for the next area.
Are we venturing forth?!
Yep.
Wait, that's right...
If I head out looking like this,
I'm gonna be mobbed by PKers
and info hunters again.
Even if I change my headgear,
Lycagon's Mark is gonna draw attention.
Not being able to wear torso and leg
armor is screwing me over so hard!
That lousy mutt!
Then why not hide your entire form?
That's what I'm trying
to figure out how to do.
I know just the place to get what you need!
Eh? Izzat you, Emul-neechan?
Hey, an exclusive Palace of Rabituza shop?!
Sunraku-san!
Allow me to introduce my
younger brother, Peatz!
He acquires goods and sells them in Rabituza!
Hey, nice to meet you!
Not just Rabituza.
You can find me in other towns, too.
I don't go out too often, since I
gotta turn into a human to do it.
But if you happen to see me,
come by and say hi...
Mr. Birdman, darling of the Night Emperor.
"Birdman"?
I'll have you know this is a mask,
and there's a real human face underneath it!
See?
What's with the big show of surprise?
Y-You actually took it off!
I had assumed there was some
deeper reason you couldn't!
Of course I can.
But that's even more convenient!
Peatz, did you not recently acquire
that very intriguing textile?
Say, yeah.
It's a pretty neat thing so I
figured it'd put it up for sale,
but it looks pretty mundane
relative to the price tag,
so it's been hard to find a buyer.
Textile?
Er...
A map of the area around Thirdrema.
Is that all?
Yes, that's all.
Thank you for coming.
Actually, I've got way more to say!
The hell is with this gear?!
I'll admit it covers
Lycagon's Mark, but still!
This is a total meme costume!
Sunraku-san, shouting like
that will attract attention!
I already stick out like a sore thumb!
Just endure it until we leave town!
I'm sure it will all work out!
Yeah, I guess it's fine.
I got the recovery items
and map I needed anyway.
But boy, you burn through MP fast
when you're in human form, huh?
Let's get moving to the next
area before our items run out.
Looks like there're three places
we can go from Thirdrema.
Right-o!
The Prismatic Forest Grotto
en route to Fourfolkshire.
A maze of caverns overgrowing with plant life,
in which flowers of all colors bloom!
The Fellfate Caldera en route to Fivelle.
Water has collected in the crater of
a long-extinct volcano to form a lake.
And the Iron Ruins of the
Divinity en route to Sixenveldt.
Ruins from the era of the Divinity,
it gets its name from its
many hovering iron boards!
I see.
Which area to visit first?
It's like in a wargame,
where you have to decide which faction
to play, which one to exploit,
and which one to suck up to.
An extremely complex decision
on the level of that.
I recommend the Fellfate Caldera!
Could you please be quiet, Emul?
Okay, I've decided!
We'll head for the
Prismatic Forest Grotto first!
Would you like to know
my reasoning, Emul-kun?
First, the area we must avoid at all costs
is clearly the Iron Ruins of the Divinity.
One might hear the name and be swayed by
the promise of scientific bounties within,
but that is a trap.
Science means civilization.
Yes, the wisdom of centuries!
Haven't we seen that person before?
So if there're guns and stuff in the ruins,
it's gonna be a pain in the ass
to deal with at my current stats,
so hard pass.
Huh? Person?