SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
What Sunraku Saw!
Mini!
Look at that fancy box.
Is that Vash's secret stash?
What rare treasures could the
boss of Rabituza have to offer?
What the heck is in there?!
A c-carrot?
I guess beneath all of it,
Aniki Vash is still a rabbit.
SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
Memory: XX Seconds
Mini!
Now, then...
The newly released Great Max Tan-Tan Noodles.
I'm gonna want something
to wash it down with.
Hm?
But didn't I hear water
makes spicy stuff worse?
Man, I'm so thirsty.
Crap. I just chugged it like always!
And it's only been a minute!
But I've still got two minutes to kill.
Oh, right. That game's got a log-in bonus.
Maybe I'll do that real quick.
I forgot about it!
They soaked it all up.
They're basically broth-free tan-tan noodles.
Guess I'll eat it.