This world is filled with too many games to count...
though the vast majority simply come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of them all
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide.
It rightly earns the status of "god-tier," Shangri-La Frontier!
One lover of trash games, Hizutome Rakurou,
is trying out this very Triple-A!
What adventures await him there?
You beat the ninth already, did you?
Guess I got here just in time.
Vash?
Dadd—I mean, Boss!
I thought I'd make your tenth opponent a monster I caught.
I went on a bit of an excursion for it.
A human? Yeah, don't think so...
A sorcerer type?
One of those dummies from long, long, long ago
tried to fuse with a tree to gain longer life.
I doubt you can beat him in the state you're in now,
so I'll bend the rules for you a little.
What's that?
Survive for five minutes.
Unique Scenario: "Invitation From Rabituza."
Practical training, tenth opponent.
Aberrant Woodmage.
Clear condition update: survive for five minutes.
An endurance battle, huh?
Five minutes is really all I need?
So if I just keep moving—
Was there even any warning for that attack?
I'm a fan of your confidence, kid,
but I'd like to see you back it up.
I get it! This might be a long five minutes!
The hell is this thing made of?!
Physical attacks won't work on it?!
Guess I've just gotta dodge my ass off!
One minute has passed!
Four more to go, Sunraku!
Now, show me every last bit of your vorpal soul.
Aberrant Woodmage.
To put it lightly...
This guy's a beast!
Root-spear attacks that are hard to predict...
Chains that look like they'll debuff you on contact...
Both chase me around like they're out to get me,
which really does a number on my will to keep dodging.
But the worst part of all...
are these magic attacks he slips in every now and then!
Not to mention...
The longer this gets, the more he mixes up the magic types!
Is the battle programmed so the attacks get denser, too?!
The number of chains and roots increases,
and the magic attacks start covering a wider area.
If he keeps ramping them up...
I'm gonna be dead before I ever reach five minutes!
Another new spell in his arsenal?!
The hell is this thing?
He nullifies physical attacks
and constantly adds attacks of his own?!
I think I'd stand a better chance against Lycagon!
Talk about hell for a first-time encounter.
This is hopeless.
I can barely think. I'm so tired.
I'm gonna get some carbs in me,
think up a strat, and try again.
It's not like I'm penalized if I die or anything.
Who cares...
Hang on, man.
What's got you writing yourself off all of a sudden?
Since when have you been such a pushover?
I don't expect to go ten in a row on my first try.
Nah, I'm done for.
I'm totally screwed.
It was the same with the Mud Digger.
You relied on Emul. You gave up just like that.
Next thing you know,
you're cutting corners all over the place.
What a mess.
I think playing so many trash games
almost turned my brain to trash, too.
Sunraku!
I guess it's not good to overdose on trashgamium.
I've gotta even it out with some godgamium!
Giving up when it's not a forced loss event...
or cutting corners on a game
that hasn't been broken wide open yet...
...just doesn't make any sense!
Breaking through the waves of attacks
to reach melee range, eh?
But what's the point, when all he can do
is dish out basic strikes?
I'm tired, dammit!
So...
I'm gonna win this thing and go the frick to bed!
Even if you can cancel any physical damage,
the attack itself still gets through, I'll bet.
That's a pretty fancy staff for a monster
to be carrying around.
I wonder what'll happen if you've gotta do without it!
Looks to me like you can't cast without it!
In a post-apocalyptic world, you survive by looting!
Don't underestimate the shakedown skills
I learned in Unite Rounds!
Those are some sticky fingers you've got there, kid.
But you've got two minutes left.
I don't think you want to be breathing easy yet.
Now, show me what you can do.
Losing the staff is your berserk button, huh?!
That's too many damn attacks!
You're kidding me!
A tantrum like this over one little staff?!
Give a little warning before you go off like this, dammit!
Sunraku, you're so close!
Only one minute to go!
Dodge, evade, withdraw, and run!
My build's literally made for this!
I'm not gonna just die
after getting this close!
A wall?
Not good!
Figured those chains
would be debuff generators.
And they've got enough punch
to override Lycagon's Mark.
I won't be able to dodge like this.
Give it back!
You want it back that badly?
Then go get it, asshole!
Dude, did you actually go fetch it?
You're such a dumbass.
You didn't need the silly staff.
You'd have won if you'd kept the roots and chains coming.
What a literal blockhead.
Eh?
Hang on a minute! I survived five minutes!
Isn't it over?!
Well, that was my idea, not his.
It's right on the line, but I'll consider it as a pass!
You certainly showed me your vorpal soul, in spades.
Huh? I thought he nullified physical attacks?
You've done it!
I simply knew you would, Sunraku!
That's only when he's holding the staff.
Without it, he's just an animated tree.
Well, that explains why he wanted it back so bad!
And... hey, does that mean I beat the quest?!
Sure does.
And you'll get your reward.
Finally!
I hereby declare you an Honorary Rabituzan.
Simply spectacular, Sunraku!
Yay! Yay!
Well... that's nice and all...
But doesn't it come with a rare item or something?
Oh, that's right. I almost forgot.
I'm sure you won't need that anymore.
Well, be seeing you again soon.
Unique scenario, Invitation
From Rabituza, has been cleared.
W-Wait! I don't get to keep it?!
Bonus unique scenario, Vorpal Epic. Begin now?
Not a single piece of real loot?!
Sheesh, it's the middle of the night.
"When the souls of the Divinity are shaken,
a rabbit shall tell an epic tale"... huh?
Yeah, I'm not following a word of that.
The bonus unique scenario I just spawned, "Vorpal Epic"...
I accepted the quest,
but I don't know how to trigger it.
Plus, the recommended level is 80.
"Divinity"?
I think that was on the guide site.
It's that civilization that died out a long time ago, right?
All the lore and speculation
got pretty overwhelming, though,
so I backed out of that pretty quick.
Pulling usable info from that mess won't be easy.
There're whole clans dedicated to finding out the game lore,
so no wonder there's a ton of stuff to sift through.
Maybe I'll put the unique stuff on hold for now,
check out the town, then head for the next area.
Are we venturing forth?!
Yep.
Wait, that's right...
If I head out looking like this,
I'm gonna be mobbed by PKers and info hunters again.
Even if I change my headgear,
Lycagon's Mark is gonna draw attention.
Not being able to wear body and leg armor
is screwing me over so hard!
That lousy mutt!
Then why not hide your entire form?
That's what I'm trying to figure out how to do.
I know just the place to get what you need!
Eh? Izzat you, Sis?
Hey, an exclusive shop in the Rabituza Palace?!
Sunraku!
Allow me to introduce my younger brother, Peatz!
He acquires goods and sells them in Rabituza!
Hey, nice to meet you!
It's not just Rabituza.
You can find me in other towns, too.
I don't go out too often,
since I gotta turn into a human to do it.
But if you happen to see me, come by and say hi...
Mr. Birdman, the darling of the Night Emperor.
"Birdman"?
I'll have you know this is a mask
and there's a real human face underneath it!
See?
What's with the big show of surprise?
Y-You actually took it off!
I had assumed there was some deeper reason you couldn't!
Of course I can.
But that's even more convenient!
Peatz, did you not recently acquire
that very intriguing textile?
Say, yeah.
It's a pretty neat thing so I figured it'd put it up for sale,
but it looks pretty mundane relative to the price tag,
so it's been hard to find a buyer.
Textile?
Er...
A map of the area around Thirdrema. Is that all?
Yes, that's all.
Thank you for coming.
Actually, I've got way more to say!
The hell is with this gear?!
I'll admit it covers Lycagon's Mark, but still!
This is a total meme costume!
Sunraku, shouting like that will attract attention!
I already stick out like a sore thumb!
Just endure it until we leave town!
I'm sure it will all work out!
Yeah, I guess it's fine.
I got the recovery items and map I needed anyway.
But boy, you burn through MP fast
when you're in human form, huh?
Let's get moving to the next area
before our potions run out.
Looks like there're three places we can go from Thirdrema.
Right-o!
The Prismatic Forest Grotto en route to Fourfolkshire.
A maze of caverns overgrowing with plant life,
in which flowers of all colors bloom!
The Fellfate Caldera en route to Fivelle.
Water has collected in the crater
of a long-extinct volcano to form a lake.
And the Iron Ruins of the Divinity en route to Sixenveldt.
Ruins from the era of the Divinity,
it gets its name from its many hovering iron boards!
I see.
Which area to visit first?
It's like in a wargame where you have to decide
which faction to play, which one to exploit,
and which one to suck up to.
An extremely complex decision on the level of that.
I recommend the Fellfate Caldera!
Could you please be quiet, Emul?
Okay, I've decided!
We'll head for the Prismatic Forest Grotto first!
Would you like to know my reasoning, Emul?
First, the area we must avoid at all costs
is clearly the Iron Ruins of the Divinity.
One might hear the name and be swayed by
the promise of scientific bounties within,
but that is a trap.
Science means civilization. Yes, the wisdom of centuries!
Haven't we seen that person before?
So if there're guns and stuff in the ruins,
I'm gonna be a pain in the ass to deal with
at my current stats, so hard pass.
Huh? Person?