SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
Animalia Expedition ~ Monster-Bird of
the Forest Grotto
The "Rabbit-Eared Shoebill" Really Exists!
Mini!
SLF Theater
The Prismatic Forest Grotto—
Within it is a legend,
spoken of only in whispers.
The mysterious monster-bird,
the Rabbit-Eared Shoebill!
Does this legendary bird really exist?!
Animalia Expedition
Monster-Bird of the Forest Grotto
The "Rabbit-Eared Shoebill"
Really Exists
The mysterious monster-bird...
We'll use all of SF-Zoo's animal
knowledge to find it, or die trying!
Captain! Look at this!
Is this... a footprint from
the Rabbit-Eared Shoebill?
Looks more humanoid than bird-like...
Following the footsteps,
the expedition moved further into the forest.
And that's when they heard it!
Captain! That call...
It must be the Rabbit-Eared Shoebill!
The piercing call caused
them to tremble in fear!
And then they saw it!
We found it!
Let's chase it down!
Right!
They were unable to get
a clear image on camera.
But the Rabbit-Eared
Shoebill truly did exist!
Their desperate search proved in vain,
and they were unable to
get a clear shot of it.
Nevertheless, the Animalia
Expedition's search continued.
Some day, they would find
that mysterious animal!
Man, watching that huge beetle send
you flying was hilarious, Sunraku.
I'm just glad I survived.
I'm still not sure that I did!