Regrets Always Lie in the Past
Known Wethermon Info
When the battle begins, a badstat(?) field gimmick(?)
is applied to all players.
Levels will be reduced and equipment with level requirements
will be force-unequippable. (Demonstrably, armor will feel
unusually heavy and hard to move in,
weapons will fly from hands.) Normal attacks can generally
be dodged by attentive players, but one hit will even kill
most tanks, so be careful!!
Most annoying is the frequency with which he uses his
finishing move (which he always announces — telegraphing?).
How to deal with his mecha-steed remains unclear.
Slashes and magic attacks don't seem to deal damage, and if you let it be
Sunraku
Katzo Tataki
Iron Ruins of the Divinity
Grinding = Repeatedly leveling up
Suppression Drone
Type: Pyramid
Crush Uppercut
Buff = Enhancement
Spirit Fist: Red
Job: Monk
It worked!
Tearlight Lake
Lifestide Salmon
Lifestide Lake Serpent
Empire Bee Twinblades
equipped.
Spiral Edge
Corrosive Poison
Combine...
Fighter-type Skill
Power Direct Lv. 5
Critical-enhancement Skill
Critical Assist Lv. 3
Link
Chance of KO effect
on critical hit
Knockout
Repel Counter
Flash Counter
Loop Slash Lv.5
Accel LV.6
Sub-jobs
Guilds
Oikatzo
Sunraku
Save Tent