This world is filled with countless games...
though the vast majority simply come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of them all
is the fully immersive VR game boasting over 30 million players worldwide.
It rightly earns the status of "god-tier," Shangri-La Frontier!
One lover of trash games, Hizutome Rakurou,
is trying out this very Triple-A!
What adventures await him there?
Shall we begin our strategy meeting?
The first problem we'll encounter during the battle.
At the start of the battle...
he activates a skill that sets the max level of characters around him in the battle area to 50.
Max level 50?
That's what you meant about our levels not being a problem?
His level is 200.
Two hundred?!
Which means a 150-level gap, minimum.
That's why player skill is the key.
Perfect for my low-level friends, right?
You won't need to grind all the way to the level cap.
Although...
you absolutely do have to reach 50.
So work hard at grinding, all right?
Level 50, huh?
She said there was a hidden area in the Iron Ruins perfect for grinding,
but I still gotta wonder how long it'll take.
Guess we won't know until we try.
It's like a whole different game in here.
The black panels are sliding all around!
Man, you can do some great stuff, glitching out moving platforms like that.
You need to soak your eyeballs and wash away that trash game filter, man.
Hang on! I thought I'd experienced this vibe before!
It's the final boss stage in Brave Galaxy Fighter!
Never heard of that one.
It's the pinnacle of sci-fi fighting games, renowned in the whole world o—oh, right.
Why would I know about some god-tier game?
By the way, Katzo.
What're you up to now?
Level-wise, you mean?
Twenty-five.
My, my! Still in your twenties, are you?
So young!
I happen to be 31.
It's not that big a difference!
He's clearly worried about how frail and helpless you are, Oikatzo!
You're so wise, Emul!
But I'm not!
Darn it, she's got it all wrong!
Sunraku!
Something's approaching!
So there're enemies mixed in with the floating panels, huh?
You can sit this one out, Sunraku!
No matter how low your level might be...
SLF still gives you a fighting chance!
Are you sure we don't need to lend our aid?
Eh... nah.
Repel Counter!
What a simple attack pattern.
Wonder if you're supposed to practice counters on these guys.
Crush Uppercut!
Hey, one punch!
You're actually quite powerful!
What's with the red aura? Some kind of buff?
Yeah.
It's a spell that gives bonuses to strength and vitality.
It's called Spirit Fist: Red.
For my job, I picked a "spirit fist user" Monk.
I can't equip weapons, but in exchange...
I can give myself buffs and beat shit up with my fists!
Build?
Lots of HP and vitality.
A light fighter, I guess you'd say!
A build that assumes you'll be soaking lots of damage, huh?
"Kill 'em before they kill you."
Makes sense for a fighting gamer like you.
If you're wondering, I'm—
Oh, I've got you pegged already.
A glass cannon with strength and agility focus, right?
Wrong!
I'm a luck fighter, specializing in agility and luck!
But still a glass cannon, right?
He's bursting with vorpal soul!
Vorpal soul?
What's that?
Vorpal soul is vorpal soul, of course!
Let's see...
Looks like the floor ahead starts the passage to the hidden area.
Pass along the left side of the plate with the big hole.
Jump over the fissure.
Jump onto the plate with damaged sides.
Slip into the crack between B2F and B3F.
Now go straight.
Whoever found this is something else!
How do you have to be wired to map out a route like this?
Well, Pencilgon found it, right?
Seems like explanation enough to me.
It truly is a maze!
"Jump into the hole, and you're done," huh?
It's too dark to see the bottom!
You think it's some kind of elaborate prank to kill us?
No way, right?
She'll have some real apologizing to do if it is.
Apologizing?!
My da—er, the boss says a proper apology is very important!
That's right!
We dunno what's down there.
I wouldn't want glass cannon Sunraku to get himself shattered going first.
So, I'll take point!
Thanks.
So kind, so strong, so brave!
What an admirable lady she is!
She's a he, actually.
I mean, the player... Never mind.
Um, point is...
Sometimes a person can look like a woman, but they've got the soul of a man.
L-Life holds so many mysteries!
The world is truly vast.
—ser.
I think he said something.
Get down here, loser!
Hard to hear.
Guess it's not a prank to get us killed, at least.
"Get down here, loser!" he said.
Fine, then!
I'll murder that asshole!
I-I'm not prepared!
There you are.
Surprisingly gentle slope, right?
So this is the hidden area Pencilgon mentioned?
"You can fish up a monster called the Lifestide Lake Serpent in the lake," it says.
Apparently it gives up some sweet XP drops.
Can we fish up a monster with these puny little rods?
Well, might as well try it!
Sure!
Let's compete to see who can catch more!
Got a bite already!
That's fast!
My father used to take me fishing all the time.
I know all the tips and tricks.
I think that's your luck stat, dude.
Got me, huh?
A salmon.
That's not what we're after.
Looks tasty, though.
Hey, I got one, too!
Just another salmon, right?
It looks small, so probably.
Wanna try a different spot?
Sunraku!
What a grand serpent indeed!
Katzo, I think that's our guy!
The Lifestide Lake Serpent!
Guess it's time to unveil my new weapon.
Huh?
I thought you were too low-level to equip those Moonblade things.
Whoever said..
I had only one weapon made?
Behold, the Empire Bee Twinblades!
How very impressive!
What, you had another new weapon?
My big sister, Bee, made them!
Bee?
It's done!
Made from the Empire Bee Queen material you brought...
The Empire Bee Twinblades!
Hey! Wake up, lazybones!
What, it's done already? Um... Bilac?
That's Big Sis Bee for you!
You think you can disrespect me just 'cause Pops ain't here?!
I learned the trade from him, y'know!
Hey, I didn't mean it like that.
I really appreciate it!
I was pretty worried about what I'd do with my main weapon gone.
Am I gonna have to manage affection levels with rabbits other than Emul and Vash?
It's not a dang dating sim!
Actually...
The thought of having to manage affection levels with more rabbits in the future...
What's the matter, Sunraku?
I'm getting trauma flashbacks from that trash game dating sim!
I once had to balance those levels between twelve girls without a moment's slip.
The slightest lapse in attention would trigger a domino effect to the levels...
and I'd land the bad end where all the girls move to Italy to apprentice at a pizzeria!
The heck're you talking about?
Sunraku Picklefish's adolescence, crushed beneath a pizza stone.
But hey, look at these new weapons!
Empire Bee Twinblades, huh?
You're pretty good.
Damn right I am.
It's very impressive indeed!
Glad I came back for the Queen's materials after I beat the Quad Beetle.
Those blades'll serve you well.
The right-hand blade has a special attribute.
The right-hand...
This thing is too damn tough!
We're too under-level to put more than a scratch on it!
Some weapons, skills, spells, and monster attacks...
have the "corrode" attribute, which destroys part of an avatar itself.
By focusing enough damage on a specific area you want to take out,
it'll cause visible damage to the part in question and becomes a weak point.
But that weapon's corrosion works a little differently.
It infects the part you attack and corrodes it over time with corrosive poison.
Just like poison,
the "corrode" attribute builds up and worms its way in little by little.
And do enough repeated strikes...
it breaks through the enemy's debuff resistance and causes the corrode attribute to show itself faster!
I've stripped away its scales, Katzo!
Got it!
I'll bring out the big guns!
Spirit Fist: Black!
Nice!
It's a proper weak point now.
I-I'll aid in the fight!
Emul!
Katzo!
I built myself to tank damage, remember?
That won't be enough to take me out!
Th-Thank you so much!
Repel Counter!
Nice stun! Now, let's press the attack!
Yeah!
Indeed!
I'll cut you into serpent fillets!
I'll make minced eel out of you!
Take this! Magic Edge!
Hell yeah!
We defeated it!
Nice work!
Hey, I leveled up already!
These guys really do offer great XP for the effort.
Boy, that thing was tough.
I got a four-level jump!
Hey, I learned new skills, too!
Wonder if I can link 'em at the Skill Garden...
Linking skills? You thinking of another game again?
No, man!
SLF is all about skills.
Of course you can combine the ones you learn to create combo ones, right?
Combine?
Remember the tutorial in Firstia, the starting town?!
Firstia? Never went.
Skills with proficiency levels can be linked up at a facility called the Skill Garden.
That lets you create new "combo skills"!
P-Proficiency levels?!
That's right...
I was wondering why some skills changed their name like Repel Counter to Flash Counter,
and some just came with level numbers to raise...
So the second kind can be linked up?!
You can also go to the Skill Garden to find out how long until your skills level up or evolve,
and find out conditions for learning new skills.
It's pretty crucial stuff!
They also sell grimoires there, and—
Sunraku! Are you all right?
Don't tell me... you don't even know about sub-jobs and guilds?
How much did I miss by skipping one little town?!
Fine, whatever!
Wallowing in regret will just get me depressed!
Let's get back to the grind!
They say busy hands keep the bad thoughts away!
Let's catch us a big eel, Katzo! Emul!
R-Righty-o!
Going for the mental blackout, huh?
Level 42 and Level 40?
That's a lot of progress in pretty a short time.
You could even afford to slow down a bit...
What got into you?
Actually, turns out Sunraku skipped the tutori—
Fine, fine. I won't tell her.
Still, Emul's got some pretty nice attack power!
I'm truly exhausted!
It just so happens, my dear little Emul is level 56!
And this tent's a handy little thing, huh?
It's not the coziest, but it lets you make a save point, right?
Yeah, but they're the worst.
Stupidly expensive for something with a limited number of uses.
I'd never use one for this if we weren't pressed for time.
Well, enough sitting around. Let's go!
Go?
Go where?
The only time we can meet her is during a full moon, like tonight.
Meet who?
In order to fight Wethermon the Tombguard, there's someone we need to talk to.
The unique NPC, Setsuna of Bygone Days.
Set.