Arthur Pencilgon
The Writing Tool Knight-Queen
Item Shop
Sales Counter
Sunraku
This rock's not even suitable
for throwing.
Pencil Knight
Katzo Tataki
Sunraku
Dystopian Empress
Pencil Knight
Ashura Kai
Giant Killer
Repel Counter
Remy
Branch
Lass
Ketchum
Branch
Remy
Ketchum
Poison   Paralysis      Drain    Exhaustion    Speed
Poison   Paralysis      Drain      Exhaustion      Speed
Debuffs = Status Ailments
Karmic Straw Doll
Consumable item.
Crush it in your hand to send all curses applied
to you back at their caster.
Attempting to expose the "something"
at the straw doll's core will kill you instantly.
Severing
attack,
"Rook-
smasher"
Constant Progress
Frog Swimmer
Battle Circuit
Panty Flash Panic
You've received
a mailbird from
Psyger-100
Secondale  Inn
From: Psyger-100
Dear Psyger-0,
Sorry, but I need you to pause
your private player hunt.
There's a player I really need to talk to.
Can you find him for me?
He was last sighted near Secondale.
He seems to have a talking,
clothed Vorpal Bunny with him.
75: Alinoiyu (Beginner)
I have a question for our esteemed elders. I was picking up equipment
in Secondale when I ran into this player. He had the cutest talking bunny
with him. How can I befriend this monster?
PvP = Battle between players