It's not nice to keep things to yourself.
Everyone should share in the fun...
Revolutionary Knight Sunraku-kun.
You've shown your face, Pencil Knight!
Hey, now.
"Revolutionary Knight Sunraku."
Don't talk to a supreme beauty like me
This title has no meaning in the game of SLF.
like she's some annoying monster.
It's a signifier of a relationship
between Sunraku and a certain other
player in a certain other game.
Besides...
in SLF, I'm not Pencil Knight.
Kindly call me Arthur Pencilgon.
My friend in trash gamerhood,
Pencil Knight...
Or should I say... Arthur Pencilgon.
In order to discuss her,
we first need to talk
about a certain trash game
known as Unite Rounds.
Take anything you want! Just don't kill me!
Let's clean the place out!
If he tries anything, kill him!
Yeah!
Hey, this guy's got quite a stash!
Yeah! What a haul!
Now, let's split.
I'm not gonna spend another
day on my hands and knees!
Nice work getting those items!
It's shakedown time.
The players called it a
"Post-Apocalyptic Looting Simulator."
The game was originally meant to simulate
a kingdom on the verge of collapse,
with players assuming the role of knights
who protect it from attacking monsters—
A co-op MMO VR game.
But because of truly garbage design that
prioritized faithfulness to the concept,
the drop rate was unreasonably low,
and precious few players
tried to play it "the right way."
Even the rocks have a 40% drop rate?!
Even the beginner's quest,
"Gather Medicinal Herbs,"
required twelve hours of combing
through open fields to complete.
Naturally, higher grade items
were even harder to find.
What were the players to do?
The answer was simple:
Steal what they needed.
"Find medicinal herbs?
You expect me to spend hours picking
through the grass for that crap?
I'll just raid an NPC store,
or steal them from a player who did."
That proved to be the winning
move in Unite Rounds.
In an environment where outrage was
rampant and everyone was an enemy,
a lone figure arose,
fueled by violence and cunning,
to take control of the kingdom.
Let's all share the wealth and drop items!
The kingdom is ours!
Comrade Pencil Knight!
Yeah! Pencil Knight!
And thus, the Pencil Kingdom was born.
Hey, Sunraku.
Yeah, Katzo?
Aw, yeah, that's good stuff!
Isn't this game about defending
the kingdom from monsters?
Is it?
I thought it was about defeating
the true big bad, Pencil Knight.
Pencil Knight was nothing like the final
boss built into the game's story.
She would intentionally abuse players
who she didn't allow into her ranks,
then use her agents to create
organized resistance to oppose her.
Thus, she fomented the will to
fight back in her victims,
preventing them from simply
giving up on the game.
Well, shall we get to the assassination?
At this time, the game of Unite Rounds
was completely at the whim of one player,
acting under a name she'd picked up
at some point—the Dystopian Empress.
You used the rebel army as a distraction
to slip a small strike force
into my inner chambers? Nice.
You coulda set some more effective traps.
They were so easy we broke
through 'em on the first try!
Sunraku-kun. Katzo Tataki-kun.
I'll remember that.
Something about that goofy smirk
of yours really gets on my nerves.
It's time for the boss battle.
Can you defeat me and become
the Revolutionary Knight?
In other words...
She and I have one hell of a history.
In Unite Rounds, we fought each other to a draw,
with both of us dying in the end.
And here, we've got a big level gap in play.
I took the penalty and came all
the way from Fifticia to PK you.
You must be so grateful and flattered!
Feel free to cry!
I'll bet those knives have
a poison attribute, right?
They're pretty expensive for
one-use items, you know...
By the way, Sunraku-kun.
What level are you at?
If you just beat Mud Digger,
you've got to be around 30, right?
That's some really impressive dodging, then.
That's the god-tier game factor.
All my moves come nice and smooth.
Pencilgon... is she...
Second in command of that player
killer clan, Ashura Kai...
The Giant Killer?!
Oh, dear! Oh, dear!
"Giant Killer"?
I focused on ambushing higher-level players,
and at some point,
I just picked up the nickname.
But the devs nerfed how that works,
so it's been a lot harder lately.
Now, hang on a minute...
In that dystopia, you were the
giant who got yourself killed!
Giants who live in glass houses
shouldn't throw boulders!
That's a clever turn of phrase
for a birdbrain like you!
You been studying hard lately, huh?
And don't you talk about that here!
I've got a bird head, not a bird brain!
You moron!
Wh-What's with those two?
Matter of fact, I didn't just
come here for personal reasons!
The leader of my clan, Ashura Kai,
asked me to deliver a message!
A message?!
"Publish info on the unique scenario,
or wear a target on your back until you do!"
He's threatening me?!
Sounds like a real dumbass.
Oh, he is.
Still, what do I do here?
There's too big a gap in
our equipment and levels.
Still, seems like you're trying hard
to keep me away from that gate.
I'll bet you timed that first attack to
prevent me from entering the city, too.
Is it that hard for a player killer to do
their thing in a highly populated town?
Well... I'd certainly prefer
to avoid it if I can.
Besides, you're not making
it to the gate, are you?
My tail!
Sunraku-san, I can't hold it any longer!
I'm going to lose my transformed state!
Darn it! I found him first!
But... he's fighting the
infamous Giant Killer...
Oh, wait! I can ask his companion...
Eh? Was she always wearing
those tail and ear accessories?
Hey, can I ask you—
Wh-What the...
Emul!
At the worst possible moment!
P-Please, calm yourself!
That's it!
Getting distracted? I'm not
enough of an opponent for you?
Yeah, right!
You're the one going easy on me!
Figured it out, did you?
Emul! C'mere!
On my way!
W-Wait!
At least let me get a screenshot with her!
If we survive this, I'll think about it!
"Survive"?
You're not fast enough to get away from me.
I don't give a damn about that player...
But if you're gonna put that
sweet little bunny in danger...
I'll slay you where you stand, Giant Killer!
Yes, nice one!
I got her to put herself
in harm's way for me!
Animalia, was it?
I could tell she was
pretty hung up on Emul...
Boy, you make a great mascot, too, Emul!
Now I just need to get into town and have
her make me a teleport gate to Rabituza!
No one should be able to track me there!
I'm the only one serving as messenger...
But I never said I came here alone.
Man, I hate PKing low-level scrubs.
It's hell on your karma points.
Our bosses feel the same way.
That's why they send us
to do their dirty work.
Stop complaining.
You wanna get PKed by Pencilgon-san?
A wild player killer appears, huh?!
You're going this far
against a low-level player?
Well, delegation is my usual MO...
Still, now I get to fight
the keeper of SF-Zoo,
a monster documenter clan with
no interest in other players?
I've really got to thank you, Sunraku-kun!
Damn it!
This god-tier game doesn't
need a trash game arc!
I'm gonna make you cough up that info!
Four PKers.
Bring it on!
I mean, you've only got me beat
in level, equipment, and stats!
Take... this!
Wow!
You work hard on your shaman debuffs to
help you record monster footage, right?
Look at all those status ailments!
You reflected all my curses?
How?!
There was this shaman PK killer who
would just not leave me alone...
So I know how scary curses can be.
That's why I carry this around, just in case.
A Karmic Straw Doll?!
Counters all curses with karmic retribution!
I'd have really been in trouble without it.
Sorry about the rotten luck.
Don't worry. I'll stick around to
watch you die of your own poison.
My best target is that jerk
who thinks I'm a scrub.
With a slow weapon like that longsword,
I don't even need skills
to dodge his attacks.
The real question is, how do
I damage high-level players
decked out in top-tier armor?
Severing attack! Rook-smasher!
Wh-What in the world?!
A one-hit kill?!
Hang on a minute. Is that...
The unparalleled firepower
of the Attack Master?!
"Attack Master"? What the hell is that?
As if I didn't have enough problems here!
A bird head mask.
Character name: Sunraku.
At last...
At last I've found you,
Hizutome-kun!
Hizutome-kun.
Where could he be?
You still haven't found him?
Well, you said he always plays as "Sunraku,"
so I've been looking for
him under that name...
But he seems to have skipped the
first tutorial city entirely...
I'm sure you'll find him soon.
Keep going, Rei-chan!
Okay...
Then tell him how you feel.
I still can't find him anywhere, Mana-san!
The games he likes are so... like...
So unusual and difficult.
They're all too hard for me.
I could never find a game
that I could play with him.
But with SLF...
We've got Hizutome-kun playing it.
I won't let this chance get away!
Mail?
From my sister?
What?!
Dear Psyger-0,
Sorry, but I need you to pause
your private player hunt.
There's a player I really need to talk to.
Can you find him for me?
This seems really bad.
They said taking pictures
is against the rules...
I guess I should probably delete it, right?
He was last sighted near Secondale.
He seems to have a talking,
clothed Vorpal Bunny with him.
He might already be en route to Thirdrema.
I've attached a picture with him in it.
He's equipped with a Staring Bird Mask,
and his legs and torso bear Lycagon's Mark.
His name is...
Sunraku.
A number of clans are already
arranging to make contact with him.
Ashura Kai is among them.
I found you.
There's a very good chance
he's already engaged in PvP.
Be careful.
I won't get a chance like this again!
If I can save him from PKers,
I'll have a natural "in" to talk to him!
Then some day...
I'll be able to talk to him IRL, too!
Severing attack! Rook-smasher!
Things are getting intense over there, too.
Though, those PKers may not
be able to beat Sunraku-kun...
Fighting him in SLF has
made it even more clear...
The skills he's built up playing
terrible games in all genres
are more valuable than unique
items and high-level stats.
And that's a huge asset here
in Shangri-La Frontier.
I hear Katzo-kun's playing SLF, as well.
So with Sunraku-kun...
That project of mine is
looking more possible.
Is that...
Psyger-0?!
First he lured in the Zookeeper,
now the Attack Master?!
I'm so glad I came to see you, Sunraku-kun!
I hit you with five spells.
"Karmic Straw Doll" is extremely powerful,
so each doll tops out at
reflecting five debuffs.
Can you counter my final hand?!