SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
Is the Food Bad in SLF?
Mini!
Oh, how I love carrots!
They are truly the greatest of foods!
The taste, the texture, the shape, the color!
There has never been a food
more perfect than the carrot!
Don't you agree, Sunraku-sa—
S-Sunraku-san?
Are you eating all of those?!
Yeah.
Apparently, there're flavor
limiters in this game.
Flavor limiters?
It might not make sense
to an NPC like you, but...
Let's say there're limiters
on pioneers' tongues,
so anything we eat just tastes
vaguely sweet, spicy, or whatever.
But I heard you can remove flavor
limiters if you eat a ton of food.
I see.
But I do hope you don't gorge yourself...
That's weird.
The flavor's doesn't change,
no matter how much I eat.
I brought this one special
from the Palace of Rabituza!
Boy, I wish I could enjoy food that much...
One level of flavor
limiter has been removed.
Flavor limiters are removed
through consumption of high-quality food items.