It's not nice to keep things to yourself.
Everyone should share in the fun...
Revolutionary Knight Sunraku.
You've shown your face, Pencil Knight!
Hey, now.
"Revolutionary Knight Sunraku."
That's no way to talk to a vixen...
This title has no meaning in the game of SLF.
like she's some kind of annoying monster.
It signifies a relationship
between Sunraku and a certain
other player in a certain other game.
Besides...
I don't go by that username in SLF.
Kindly call me Arthur Pencilgon.
My friend in trash gamerhood, Pencil Knight.
Or should I say... Arthur Pencilgon.
Before we introduce Pencilgon, we need to talk about
a certain trash game known as Unite Rounds.
Take anything you want! Just don't kill me!
Let's clean the place out!
If he tries anything, kill him!
Yeah!
Hey, this guy's got quite a stash!
Yeah! What a haul!
Now, let's split.
I'm not gonna spend another day on my hands and knees!
Nice work getting those items!
It's shakedown time.
The players called it a "post-apocalyptic looting simulator."
The game was originally meant to simulate
a kingdom on the verge of collapse,
with players assuming the role of knights
who protect it from attacking monsters.
It's a co-op MMO VR game.
But because of truly garbage design
that prioritized faithfulness to the concept,
the drop rate was unreasonably low,
and precious few players tried to play it "the right way."
Even the rocks have a 40% drop rate?!
Even the beginner's quest, "Gather Medicinal Herbs,"
required 12 hours of combing through
open fields to complete.
Naturally, higher-grade items were even harder to find.
What were the players to do?
The answer was simple.
Steal what they needed.
"Find medicinal herbs?
You expect me to spend hours
picking through the grass for that crap?
I'll just raid an NPC store,
or steal them from a player who did."
That proved to be the winning move in Unite Rounds.
In an environment where outrage was rampant
and everyone was an enemy,
a lone figure arose, fueled by violence and cunning,
to take control of the kingdom.
Let's all divvy up the wealth and drops!
The kingdom is ours!
Comrade Pencil Knight!
Yeah! Pencil Knight!
And thus, the Pencil Kingdom was born.
Hey, Sunraku.
Yeah, Katzo?
Aw, yeah, that's good stuff!
Isn't this game about
defending the kingdom from monsters?
Is it?
I thought it was about defeating
the true big bad, Pencil Knight.
Pencil Knight was nothing like the final boss
built into the game's story.
She would intentionally abuse players
who she didn't allow into her ranks,
then use her agents to create
organized resistance to oppose her.
Thus, she fomented the will to fight back in her victims,
preventing them from simply giving up on the game.
Well, shall we get to the assassination?
At this time, the game of Unite Rounds
was completely at the whim of one player,
acting under a name she'd picked up
at some point, the Dystopian Empress.
Quite impressive using the rebel army as a distraction
to slip a small strike force into my inner chambers.
You coulda set some more effective traps.
They were so easy, we broke through 'em on the first try!
Sunraku, Katzo Tataki?
I'll remember those.
Something about that goofy smirk
of yours really gets on my nerves.
It's time for the boss battle.
Can you defeat me and become the Revolutionary Knight?
In other words...
she and I have one hell of a history.
In Unite Rounds, we fought each other to a draw,
with both of us dying in the end.
And here, we've got a big level gap in play.
I took the respawn penalty and came
all the way from Fifticia to kill you.
You must be so grateful and flattered! Feel free to cry!
I'll bet those knives have a poison attribute, right?
They're pretty expensive for single-use items, y'know.
By the way, Sunraku. What level are you at?
If you just beat Mud Digger,
you've got to be around 30, right?
That's some really impressive dodging, then.
That's the god-tier game factor.
All my moves come nice and smooth.
Pencilgon... is she...
Second in command of that player killer clan, Ashura Kai...
The Giant Killer?!
Oh, dear! Oh, dear!
"Giant Killer"?
I focused on ambushing higher-level players,
and at some point, I just picked up the nickname.
But the devs nerfed how that works,
so it's been a lot harder lately.
Now, hang on a minute...
In that dystopia, you were the giant who got yourself killed!
Giants who live in glass houses shouldn't throw boulders!
That's a clever turn of phrase for a birdbrain like you!
You been studying hard lately, huh?
And don't you talk about that here!
I've got a bird head, not a bird brain!
You moron!
What... What's with those two?
Matter of fact, I didn't just come here for personal reasons!
The leader of my clan, Ashura Kai,
asked me to deliver a message!
A message?!
"Publish info on the unique scenario,
or wear a target on your back until you do!"
He's threatening me?!
Sounds like a real dumbass.
Oh, he is.
Still, what do I do here?
There's too big a gap in our equipment and levels.
Still, seems like you're trying hard
to keep me away from that gate.
I'll bet you timed that first attack
to stop me from entering the city, too.
Is it that hard for a player killer
to do their thing in a highly populated town?
Well... I'd certainly prefer to avoid it if I can.
Besides, you're not making it to the gate, are you?
No, my tail!
Sunraku, I can't hold it any longer!
I'm transforming back into my normal self!
Darn it!
I was the one who found him first!
But... he's fighting the infamous Giant Killer.
Oh, wait! I can ask his companion...
Eh? Was she always wearing those tail and ear accessories?
Hey, can I ask you—
Wh-What the...
Emul!
Talk about the worst timing!
P-Please, calm yourself!
That's it!
Distracted? Not good enough for you?
Yeah, right!
You're the one going easy on me!
Figured it out, did you?
Emul! C'mere!
On my way!
W-Wait! At least let me get a screenshot with her!
If we survive this, I'll think about it!
"Survive"?
You're not fast enough to get away from me.
I don't give a damn about that player.
But if you're gonna put that sweet little bunny in danger...
I'll slay you where you stand, Giant Killer!
Yes, nice one!
I got her to give us some time!
Animalia, was it?
I could tell she was pretty hung up on Emul.
Boy, you make a great mascot, too, Emul!
Now I just need to get into town
and have her make me a teleport gate to Rabituza!
No one should be able to track me there!
I may be the only one bearing a message...
but I never said I came here alone.
Man, I hate PKing low-level scrubs.
It's hell on your karma points.
Our bosses feel the same way.
That's why they send us to do their dirty work.
Stop complaining.
You wanna get PKed by Pencilgon?
A wild player killer appears, huh?!
You're going this far against a noob like me?
Well, delegation is my usual MO.
Still, now I get to fight the keeper of SF-Zoo,
a monster documenter clan
with no interest in other players?
I've really got to thank you, Sunraku!
Dammit!
This Triple-A game doesn't need this kind of trashy arc!
I'm gonna make you cough up that info!
Four PKers.
Bring it on!
I mean, you've only got me beat
in level, equipment, and stats!
Take... this!
Wow!
You work hard on your shaman debuffs
to help you record monster footage, right?
Look at all those status ailments!
You reflected all my curses?
How?!
There was this shaman PK killer
who would just not leave me alone.
So I know how scary curses can be.
That's why I carry this around, just in case.
You've got a Karmic Straw Doll?!
Counters all curses with karmic retribution!
I'd have really been in trouble without it.
Maybe it's just not your day.
Don't worry. I'll stick around to watch
you die of your own poison.
My best target is that jerk who thinks I'm a scrub.
With a slow weapon like that longsword,
I don't even need skills to dodge his attacks.
The real question is, how do I damage
high-level players decked out in top-tier armor?
Severing attack! Rook-smasher!
Wh-What in the world?!
An instakill?!
Hang on a minute. Is that...
the unparalleled firepower of the Attack Master?!
"Attack Master"? What the hell is that?
As if I didn't have enough problems here!
A bird head mask.
Username's Sunraku.
At last...
At last, I've found you...
Hizutome!
Hizutome...
Where could you be?
So you still haven't found him?
Well, you said he always plays as "Sunraku,"
so I've been looking for him under that username.
But he seems to have skipped the first tutorial city entirely.
I'm sure you'll find him soon.
Don't give up, Rei!
Okay.
Then tell him how you feel.
I still can't find him anywhere, Miss Mana!
The games he likes are so... like...
so unusual and difficult.
They're all too hard for me.
I could never find a game that I could play with him.
But with SLF...
We've got Hizutome playing it.
I won't let this chance get away!
Mail?
From my sister?
What?!
Dear Psyger-0...
Sorry, but I need you to pause your personal player hunt.
There's a player I really need to talk to.
Can you find him for me?
This seems really bad.
They said taking pictures is against the rules.
I should probably delete it, right?
He was last seen near Secondale.
He seems to have a talking, clothed Vorpal Bunny with him.
He might already be en route to Thirdrema.
I've attached a screenshot of him.
He's equipped with a Staring Bird Mask,
and his legs and torso bear Lycagon's Mark.
His username is...
Sunraku.
A number of clans are already arranging
to make contact with him.
Ashura Kai is among them.
I found you.
There's a very good chance he's already engaged in PvP.
Be careful.
I won't get a chance like this again!
If I can save him from PKers, I'll finally be able
to strike up a conversation with him!
Then someday...
I'll be able to talk to him IRL, too!
Severing attack! Rook-smasher!
Things are getting intense over there, too.
Though, those PKers may not be able to beat Sunraku.
Fighting him in SLF has made it even more clear.
The skills he's built up playing terrible games in all genres
are more valuable than unique items and high-level stats.
And that's a huge asset here in Shangri-La Frontier.
I hear Katzo's playing SLF, as well.
So with Sunraku...
My project is looking more possible.
Is that...
Psyger-0?!
First he lured in the Zookeeper, now the Attack Master?!
I'm so glad I came to see you, Sunraku!
I hit you with five curses.
"Karmic Straw Doll" is extremely powerful...
so each doll tops out at reflecting at five debuffs.
But can you counter my final hand?!