The end of eternity
It's danger, danger
The dots and lines connect, they linger
What lies beyond, I want to know
Where does it go?
Let's go
Out of the concrete jungle
Racing through this dungeon, a sea of trees
Let's get ready to rumble, we can go
All right, y'know this isn't your ordinary game
Twists in the plot, turned into a bug
Through pain and grit, we push the limit
Okay, let's get it
It's time to fly
I'm gonna die in my hype
I don't care, I'm aiming high
Light pierces the dark seams
Hysterical, chasing fragile dreams
Still, who are we fighting for?
Scenes flashing past
It's danger, danger
And here you are at last
Frozen in time, we are the game changers
Press ahead
We won't relent
Even if we're left with nothing at the end
It's danger, danger
Those Who Illuminate The World's Darkness
Crystal Talon
Crystal Carapace
Crystal Leg
Crystal Pincer
Crystal Carapace
Crystal Leg
Crystal Pincer
Crystal Carapace
Crystal Leg
Crystal Pincer
Crystal Carapace
Crystal Talon
Crystal Pincer
Crystal Carapace
Crystal Leg
Crystal Pincer
Smith
Jeweler
Swordsmaster
Wild Wind
Cait Sith
Cazzeria
Vice Captain of Musketeers in Boots
Aramiys
Ancient
Craftsman
Werewolf
Lizardman
Eighth City
Eighthold
Professor
Leader of Game Lore Clan, The Library
Vorpal Epic
Begin now?
Bonus Unique Scenario
Vorpal Epic
Begin now?
Yes
No
Bonus Unique Scenario
Vorpal Epic
Begin now?
Yes
No
Bonus Unique Scenario
Vorpal Epic
Begin now?
Yes
No
Bonus Unique Scenario
Vorpal Epic
Begin now?
Yes
No
Sunraku
Professor
has sent you a friend request.
Accept?
Yes
No
If there's regret lingering in my chest
Is it the "goodbye" I couldn't express?
Regret keeps falling, it won't ever cease
Did I run from the end I didn't want to see?
The banyan tree you planted
It grew ever so tall
With its drooping boughs, tears gently fall
I loved you
But the words never came
So simple, so plain
Yet I let them slip away
Oh rain, wash this eternal goodbye
A sweet scent from the rain tree
And my memories start to cascade
Making my heart ache
Heaven in the rain