SLF Theater!
SLF Mini
Gems, Ore,
and Heads of Equal Hardness
Mini!
Bilac, the Vorpal Bunny blacksmith.
Day after day, she works at her anvil,
dreaming of someday reaching,
and surpassing, her father's greatness.
I got you some pretty rare stuff here.
Well... they've got pretty
good specs, sure...
But my blacksmith instinct is
telling me they're not quite right.
Your instinct is pretty selfish.
So, what kind of ore would
your instinct rather have?
More like... well...
Let's see...
I wanna make an alloy.
So you need iron ore, huh?
All right.
Let's go, Emul!
Righty-o!
Sunraku-san! You must run faster!
Okay. We got it.
You got a problem with this, too?!
Well... if I wanna make stronger weapons,
I kinda need gemstones, too...
Fine, fine.
I'll get you some gemstones, then!
Let's go, Emul!
W-We're not going there, are we?!
That should... do it, right?
While you were out, I started thinking.
Maybe it'd be better to use monster
materials or wood or something.
I've got better materials right here.
What?
Ore.
Gems.
And a head as hard as either of them!
Don't totally change directions
right before the job!
You're the one who said you
wanted the ultimate weapon!
W-W-Wait, you two!
Please, no fighting!