Th-This is...
Aroncaleth Hard Lapis, the material
known as the king of coatings?!
And the "bright star plucked from
the heavens," Lapisteria Stellar Crystal?!
Hang on a minute!
You got Lowenanva Amber Crystal, too?!
You don't usually see 'em at this size, either!
Hey, an Amurcidian Quartz!
I have no idea what she's talking about.
There's more where that came from, Bilac!
Crystal Leg?
Crystal Carapace?
Crystal Pincer?!
I got the complete Crystal Scorpion set!
You saying you really went to the land of the crystals?!
All these rare materials are gonna make my head explode!
He failed to retrieve the Crystal Scorpion
Stinger, though, so that isn't—
Here! Good little girls gotta eat their carrots!
So, Bilac, I gotta know...
What kind of weapon can you make
with all these amazing materials?!
I never had any interest in gemstones
outside of their material value.
But when you've got a gem of this quality
right in front of your eyes,
it's hard not to feel pretty delighted.
I think I finally get how the Cait Siths feel!
The heck was that about?!
I was asking what you could make with 'em!
Right. Well...
For sure, I can make weapons outta
the Crystal Scorpion parts and the ore...
Yes, yes.
But gems like these are better off
being made into accessories.
Which means it's less a job for a smith like me
and more a job for a jeweler.
A jeweler?
You know those little items
that produce effects when you slap 'em on?
Jewelers specialize in making the kind
that incorporates gems.
Oh, so they make accessories?
So? Any jewelers here in Rabituza?
Not another of Emul's sisters, I hope?
Sorry, but there aren't any in this place.
Aw, for real?
Wait, it's not a rare job or something, is it?!
What the hell?!
All my great stuff is gonna go to waste, then!
Would you let me finish?
I've got a connection that can make it happen.
Though...
I really hate asking that guy for stuff.
Still, my pride as a blacksmith, as a craftsman,
bristles at letting these wonderful things go to waste.
Quit putting on airs and call him in already!
All right. I guess I gotta.
I'll call him in, then.
Hey, Ignoramus. C'mon in.
Shouldn't you call louder?
The guy's not in the next room, right?
You called, my beauteous raven-haired lady?!
Freaking hell!
Were I tumbling into a bottomless ravine...
You need only call my name, and I will appear at your side!
The hell am I looking at?
I am the Swordsmaster!
The Wild Wind!
The land of Cait Siths, Cazzeria's own...
Vice-captain of the Musketeers in Boots...
Aramiys!
What was that name? "Alarmist"?
And this windbag is the jeweler?
Nah, not him.
And you can just call him Ignoramus.
And I believe you are... my lovely maiden's sister!
Yes, I'm Emul!
And this is Sunraku!
Now, how might this unworthy Aramiys serve you, milady?
At your word, fair creature,
I would challenge Lycagon itself!
Hey, great idea. Go dash yourself on that rock.
At least, that's what I'd like to say,
but I got a favor to ask you today.
A favor? You have need of me, milady?!
I want you to ask your jeweler buddy,
D'Arnyaata, to whip up some accessories.
Oho?
And I'm not talking about any run-of-the-mill stuff.
I'm talking about a masterwork.
My, what a truly spectacular collection of jewels!
Sunraku here collected them!
'Sup?
I first took you for a birdman,
but you have the body of a human...
Though I've never heard of a human
with the head of a bird...
I'm human, okay?
Not just any human, though.
He's been declared worthy by the Night Emperor,
he beat the Eternal Tombguard...
and he's Pops's underling.
This human did all of that?
You'll have to forgive me...
if I harbor doubts.
I see.
I suppose it is true!
Is this guy for real?!
You lousy feline!
Quit screwing around in my sacred forge!
Sunraku! Are you all right?
Ah, fair lady! Your expressions of love do pain me so!
A bit more to the right! Ow, ow, ow!
Now, if I may, birdman of the blue...
Rather, Sunraku...
May I assume you wish me to use all of these gemstones?
Yeah... I guess the only other option is selling 'em, so...
Take good care of 'em, Aramiys.
It shall be done!
This unworthy vice-captain of the Musketeers in Boots,
the Wild Wind, Aramiys,
shall see you the finest of accessories crafted.
Kiss!
The hell you think you're doing?!
I shall see you anon!
He disappeared.
A teleportation spell!
Frickin' Ignoramus.
I really hate the guy.
Um, mind if I ask how you two know each other?
Huh?
I made a weapon for the jerk once. That's it.
He's the vice-captain of the kingdom of Cait Siths, Cazzeria!
He's much stronger than he appears at first glance!
Yeah, I'll bet.
I don't think he put his all into that attack, even.
And he did call himself "Swordsmaster"...
Well, if we're talking pure fighting ability,
he's probably got me beat.
Kingdom of the Cait Siths, Cazzeria, huh?
I'd love to ask more questions about that,
but I'm pretty tired all of a sudden.
I think I'll get some rest.
Oh?
Well... if you're tired, then I suppose you must.
I'll take a quick nap, then come right back.
And after that, we'll seriously start
searching for the magic operations unit.
Gotta make an Ancient Craftsman out of Bilac, after all!
Yes, indeed!
You're a real bundle of energy, too, huh?
So tired...
Guess I'll log in again this evening.
Huh? Got some emails.
Hey, got a question for you!
Where are you right now?
There's a thing I wanna meet up and talk about!
Question for Sunraku!
Where are you right now? Fivelle?
I'd like to meet up with you
and discuss something in person.
You free this evening?
What the heck?
Even a carnivorous plant is more subtle...
The hell are those two plotting now?
Well, either way, I've used too much brainpower.
Gonna sleep now.
Okay!
That little nap was just what I needed!
Let's resume the plan to level up Bilac!
The goal, become an Ancient Craftsman!
I sorta ended up ignoring their emails, but...
Well, whatever.
It was probably just gonna be annoying stuff anyway.
Let's start by rounding up Bilac.
Gotta get that magic operations unit
from the Ruins of Past Glories!
Ah, there's something I must tell you regarding that.
Milady!
Though I am ever pleased by the feel of your foot upon me,
it really does hurt!
I'm trying to put you, and the world,
out of our collective misery!
Ouch! That's my spine!
What's with this married couple comedy routine?
Who the hell are you calling a couple?!
Speaking of, Aramiys. Didn't you go back to Cazzeria?
What'd you do with my jewels?
Rest easy, friend!
I have delivered your jewels to their
best destination, the jeweler, D'Arnyaata!
Then I returned to lend aid to my fair maiden!
She is embarking on a journey
to the wild frontier, is she not?
If so,
then I, Wild Wind Aramiys, am obliged to offer my aid!
Which means... what?
It appears he intends to accompany us.
For real?
Bilac said he was stronger than her.
Wouldn't having another
post-level-90 character make things too easy?
I gotta think about this one.
I'd leave him behind if I could...
but he's gonna tag along, no matter what we say.
Apparently the Cait Siths' king heard about you,
and got a whole head of steam about
not just making accessories,
but putting the whole force of Cazzeria behind you.
Huh?
Why would he do that?
Cazzeria and Rabituza are sworn allies, see?
Being Pops's underling is a bigger deal
than you probably thought.
Plus, you beat one of the Colossi.
I'm guessing you still don't grasp
how much pull that gives you.
My will is the will of Cazzeria itself!
Stand back as I slay all who stand in milady's way!
Cait Siths love their gemstones, see?
Their jewelers are especially skilled as hell,
but they're famous for pocketing the materials you give 'em.
Huh? What the heck?!
I listed your accomplishments to try to head that off...
but it came with a price that's a real pain in the ass.
Now, Sunraku!
We must begin, post-haste!
Let us lead milady to ever-greater heights!
By the way, what else might my "pull" get me?
Well, you got the Night Emperor's
approval tattooed on you,
so you could land yourself a werewolf or lizardman bride.
The ladies are gonna love you.
Hey, can we not?
Well, other than that...
If you're not careful, you could start a war.
C'mon, I'd never do that.
I'm a pure, righteous player here.
Well, either way, you'd better come
to grips with what you've done,
or things could get messy real quick.
I'm just telling you to be careful.
Sure...
Hey, Ignoramus! Time to haul ass!
Are you ready or not?!
But of course, milady!
Say the word and it is done!
This has become quite a grandiose matter!
Yeah.
But meh, I'm sure it's fine.
Even if the whole world turns against me,
I've sorta been through that in other worlds anyway.
I haven't used my human form in so long!
Ah, the family resemblance is clear in your skill!
Brilliant transformation prowess!
Hey, Ignoramus! Watch where
you put your hands, would you?
Milady, my skull! Please, not the skull!
I can see you smiling, asshole!
Ouch! Ouch!
Chill, you guys! You're gonna tear the fabric!
Sheesh.
Even moving through town's a pain in the ass now.
Never thought I'd have to wear this getup again.
Oh, look, they're selling carrots!
Might we buy some?!
You've had plenty already, Emul!
I got mahni to spare, thanks to the Crystal Scorpion battle,
but take it easy on those mana potions, got it?
That hurts!
Knock it off already!
If you run out, you'll have to join us in the robe of hell.
Y-Yes, sir!
Well, it beats walking around in the chimera getup.
At least this thing is official game equipment.
As long as I act confident, no one'll suspect a thing!
People are gonna give you a wide berth either way.
Yeah, I'm pretty used to that by now.
That one's really staring at us, Sunraku!
Stay cool, Emul!
Just act like you belong!
And you guys, hold still!
She's approaching us!
Um... how can I help you, Miss Magical Girl?
Ah! Are you perhaps wondering about this outfit of mine?
Peatz runs a shop in Thirdrema, right?
Er...
See, in Third—
In Thirdrema, there's occasionally
an open-air stall that sells such an item.
The Ritual Medjed Keffiyeh, I believe.
One of the three players involved
in beating Wethermon the Tombguard
is known to wear it, I'm told.
That player typically favors the Staring Bird Mask.
His name, I believe, was Sunraku.
Crud.
Either I blew my cover, or someone leaked info about me.
But more than that, this avatar...
it's got a totally deep old-man voice!
You match the characteristics of a player
I've been searching for, you see.
Could I have a moment of your time?
A magical girl avatar with the voice of an old man?
Is that the gimmick?!
Are you listening to me?
The gap between the appearance
and the voice is supposed to be a gag, right?
Well... not that I can talk, given how I go around.
Oh, apologies.
I've failed to introduce myself.
I am the leader of the game lore clan, The Library.
They call me the Professor.
Game lore clan, The Library...
I believe we're rather well-known here in SLF.
Have you heard of us, perhaps?
We spend our days learning more about
the world and lore of this game.
Oh, right.
I think I heard about them
when I was looking up info online.
Seems like they gather info through ties
to tons of players and clans.
Which means this "Professor"
might have some handy info for me.
But I kinda wanna get where I'm going already.
I've already taken up enough time on detours.
Plus, if info about Emul and the others gets out,
it's gonna open up a whole can of worms.
Have you felt it, by chance?
The distinctiveness of the scenario flags in SLF...
Unlike a normal game, which guides you
purposely through a series of events,
players must find the carefully hidden flags for themselves.
That's true.
It truly is a game for the pioneer spirit.
I've never seen one with so much to discover.
But most intriguing of them all is the part that
fills the core of the world, the Seven Colossi.
They're so difficult to fight
that we researchers have hit a wall.
So when I heard that someone
had slain Wethermon the Tombguard,
my heart danced with joy.
Sunraku.
Will you join us in exploring the truth of this world?
We live in a world filled with countless games...
though the vast majority simply come and go in obscurity.
What's considered the best of the best
is the fully immersive VR game
boasting over 30 million players worldwide.
It's earned the status of "god-tier," Shangri-La Frontier!
Okay, let's do this!
Watch me, Set.
The truth of this world?
If you wish to know of your roots,
of the truth of this world...
Would you like to know the truth of this world, son?
Can the lover of trash games,
Hizutome Rakurou, AKA Sunraku,
unlock the truth of this world?
And there was another thing he didn't realize...
That the night of his rematch
with one of SLF's Seven Colossi,
Lycagon the Nightslayer, was not that far off.