SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
You'll Pay. Oh, You Will Pay...
Mini!
SLF Theater
Unique Scenario,
"Invitation From Rabituza"
Practical Training Opponent 5
"Toxic Eagle"
45th Try
I can't reach it with
attacks from the ground!
In that case...
Gotcha!
You...
Sunraku-san!
Oh, you're gonna pay...
SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
What Kind of Man Is Rakuro Hizutome?
Mini!
SLF Theater
Hey. I'm Rakuro Hizutome.
Yes, that's right.
I'm a trash game hunter.
Why do I love trash games so much?
There's a saying.
"Seek out trials while you're young."
If you struggle while you're young,
the experience will be useful later,
so you should aggressively pursue trials.
From Kojien, 7th Edition
My name, "Rakuro," already means easy,
so why should I seek out
the easy path in life?
Actively seeking out the most difficult paths
and climbing the most
treacherous mountains...
That's where you'll see the most beautiful
views, and the most enjoyable life!
This daydream is fiction. It has no relation to actual
people or trash game hunters.