This world is filled with too many games to count...
though the vast majority simply come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of them all
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide.
It rightly earns the status of "god-tier," Shangri-La Frontier!
One lover of trash games, Hizutome Rakurou,
is trying out this very Triple-A!
What adventures await him there?
Anyway, the game was the buggiest piece of crap,
and you're forced to do only autosaves!
I don't really follow, but it sounds pretty fun!
Nope, not at all.
Tons of bug crashes.
The worst kind of trash!
Then why are you playing it?
'Cause it's fun!
Hey.
He was always smiling.
Hey, Rakurou. Is that the latest issue?
What now?
He seemed to be enjoying himself.
That's why I started thinking about him.
I started looking for him.
'Sup, Rakurou?
Heya.
I tried to talk to him so many times.
But I wasn't brave enough.
I thought, if I could just talk to him...
Even if it was in-game...
Dammit!
This Triple-A game doesn't need this kind of trashy arc!
I'm gonna make you cough up that info!
Severing Attack! Rook-Smasher!
Wh-What in the world?!
Psyger-0?
Doesn't look like the PKing type.
But I'll bet they're after
the unique scenario, same as the others.
I'm never getting out of this.
I need to think up a way out.
But can you counter my final hand?!
It requires the skill "Spell Mastery" and single-digit HP.
A murder-suicide curse to destroy both
my opponent and myself!
I've used up the Karmic Straw Doll.
I can't reflect another curse!
I'll sacrifice my remaining life
and inflict the "Insta-Death" debuff!
Fellow Traveler!
Well, drat.
What the...
Pencilgon?!
Emul, get a gate ready.
Gwuh?!
Sorry.
Hey!
D-Dammit!
You left yourselves wide open, dumbasses!
Don't let him reach the city!
It's swarming with bounty hunters!
I'll remember your name, at least...
Psyger-0.
Dammit! Attack Master!
You think you can just get in our way?!
Don't look down on the Ashura Kai!
Sorry.
He talked to me!
This guy's acting pretty weird, right?
What's going on?
I dunno, but he's wide open.
Now's our chance!
PKing you will have me shooting up the Ashura Kai ranks!
But if not for you people,
I could have talked to him more!
Make a break for it?
Yep.
Sorry, but I'll have to—
I mean, have a taste of my fury!
Yes! I escaped!
Well?
How'd you like that, you basement-dwelling bastards?!
They can't follow me to Rabituza!
That was pretty scary, though!
Didn't expect you'd say you ran out of mana for a gate!
I used it all on my transformation!
We'd have been in real trouble
if we couldn't travel from Thirdrema.
This is truly delicious!
Good thing I bought some magic-restoring potions.
Anyway, objective accomplished.
Pencil Knight... I mean, it's Pencilgon.
That sore loser sent me an email.
FYI, my death was my own fault,
so I don't consider this losing to you.
Can't believe the Attack Master came to bail you out.
Friend of yours?
"Attack Master"?
Is she talking about that Psyger-0 person?
Anyway, I really do want to talk to you,
so call Katzo for a meeting in Unite Rounds.
We'll talk scheduling later.
Talk to me, eh?
The fact that she won't do it inside SLF...
makes me suspicious.
Hey, speak of the devil.
Just got a total "evil mastermind" invite from the pencil.
What'd you do, man?
It's fishy as hell...
but it's equally intriguing, if I'm honest.
Can't say I'm not intrigued,
so I figure we might as well hear her out.
You're not gonna back out, right?
Well, I can't back out after Katzo
starts adding pressure, too.
But I've got bigger things to think about now.
What a lovely treat!
Sorry for the wait, Emul.
Let's get this unique scenario started!
Oh, at last!
Hurrah, hurrah!
So, what's the task?
That Vash guy...
I mean, your bunny boss,
said something about "getting me up to snuff."
Then I shall lead you to the arena
where we do our most serious battle training!
Arena?
The Vorpal Colosseum!
Hey, it's pretty big!
My dadd—ahem, the boss wants you
to fight ten monsters here!
Okay!
So it's a boss rush kind of thing, right?
Ah, but you are strictly limited
to the use of vorpal weapons!
Great!
Okay!
Time to grind levels until I can wipe
that smug smirk off of Pencilgon's face!
All ready.
Let out the first one!
Righty-o!
Here it comes!
I don't expect to go ten in a row on my first try.
I'll use trial and error,
learn their attack patterns, and slowly but surely...
Practical training, first opponent.
Packhound.
Always spawns in groups of five or more.
Average level, 65.
They look tough.
Hang on a minute here!
You're making me fight multiple enemies over level 65?!
Well, of course!
That's how the first opponent works!
A-At least say first fight, not opponent!
I talked to Hizutome!
Sorry.
N-Next time I see him, I'll try to find
the courage to send a friend request.
I wonder if he'd accept it...
A friend request?
Of course I'll accept!
Psyger-0, I can't thank you enough
for saving me back there.
Let's walk to school together everyday!
Oh, you silly!
But I entered Thirdrema
and looked for him after it was over,
and I couldn't find him.
Did he log out, maybe?
I wonder what he's doing now.
These guys... totally...
just think of me as food!
Sunraku! It's your seventh try!
This time, see that you beat them!
Thankfully, there's no penalty for dying in the arena.
But it's not their numbers and level
that make these guys a pain.
It's their completely synchronized team attacks!
Repel Counter!
That coordination is the result
of having a pack leader giving orders!
Slide Move!
I've fought them enough times that I've started to see it.
One monster that keeps howling from
a safe distance and never actually attacks!
You're the pack leader, aren't you?!
Spiral Edge!
Looks like I guessed right!
Your coordination's all out of whack!
And now that I know that, I can ignore these suckers!
I'll focus on the leader before he can bark out orders!
Get over here!
Gotcha!
Impressive as ever, Sunraku!
Monsters left on their own after losing their big bad
are nothing to be afraid of!
Once you know the trick, they're just regular tank mutts.
You're brilliant, Sunraku!
Practical training, first opponent: Packhound, complete.
Excellent work, Sunraku!
The next one's not a group, too, is it?
You'll definitely be facing a single opponent!
It'd better be, man.
Practical training, second opponent: Parasite Tentacle.
It's basically another freaking group!
Like the name implied,
the real monster was the tentacles, not the bear.
I kept up a hit-and-run strategy on the tentacles,
and once the seventh was severed,
the bear stopped moving and I won.
"A really jacked up goblin" is the only way to put it.
Tough or not, though, he's still just a goblin.
He was easier than the wolves or the tentacles.
This boar sucks.
Its ability to blow you up if its nose hits you
while it's charging wasn't that bad.
But it's got crazy stamina.
I timed it, and it ran about 20 seconds on each charge.
If not for my rodeo experience,
it would've taken me way longer to kill.
That's in-game rodeo experience, by the way.
You'll pay. Oh, you will pay.
Sunraku!
This was way easier compared to the birdy bastard
who hovered out of attack range
while dropping poison bombs.
Spend your whole life on the ground, never growing wings.
Fast and strong but not too tough.
Once you learn that its whole strat is to get behind you
and attack from outside your line of sight,
it's easy to take down.
Not great, not terrible.
Just a pretty strong guy.
That's it.
If we call attacks from the right arm A,
and attacks from the left arm B,
when chaining from A to A,
there's almost no gap between its attacks.
But if it goes from A to B or vice-versa,
the chest core lights up for a second.
This allows for some limited anticipation of its attacks.
Given the difference between
my height and the golem's height,
that generates some predictability
in attacks from sides A and B.
I had a theory that the moment I dodged
an attack or the action's attack hit box faded,
I could jump on the arm
to jump up and directly attack the core.
But when I actually tried it,
I ended up repelled by an invisible energy field
which shaved 70% off my HP,
so I was forced to change my strategy,
which turned out to be directly peeling off
its armor to expose a weak point—
Oh, screw it!
I dodged, stripped it down, hit it, and won!
Hell yeah! Just one left!
Practical training, ninth opponent:
Beta Unit Golem S2, complete.
Although...
all that fighting to go up two measly levels?
Thanks so much, Vorpal Soul Collar
which so generously cuts my exp gains in half.
Sunraku! You should probably take a break!
You have a great and terrible look in your eyes!
Whatcha mean?
All this optimization is going great for me!
Now, bring out the last monster already!
Well, well.
You beat the ninth already, did you?
Guess it's perfect timing.
Vash?
Dadd—I mean, Boss!
"Perfect timing," huh?
Beating the ninth monster triggered the event flag, I'll bet.
So, Don.
Would that last monster happen to be...
I thought I'd make your tenth opponent a monster I caught.
I went on a bit of an excursion for it.
A human? Yeah, don't think so...
A sorcerer type?
One of those dummies from long, long, long ago
tried to fuse with a tree to gain longer life.
I doubt you can beat him in the state you're in now,
so I'll give you a different win condition.
What's that?
Survive five minutes.
Unique Scenario: "Invitation From Rabituza."
Practical training, tenth opponent.
Aberrant Woodmage.
Clear condition update: survive for five minutes.
An endurance battle, huh?
Five minutes is really all I need?
So if I just keep moving—
Was there even a warning for that attack?
I'm a fan of your confidence, kid,
but I'd like to see you back it up.
I get it! This might be a long five minutes!
Out of the over 30 million SLF players,
Sunraku is the first one to fight this monster.
But he wouldn't learn this until far into the future.