This world is filled with
too many games to count,
though the vast majority simply
come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of all games
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide—
Shangri-La Frontier, which rightly
earns the title of "god-tier game"!
One lover of trash games, Rakuro Hizutome,
is trying out the god-tier
game, Shangri-La Frontier!
What adventures await him there?
Anyway, the game was the
buggiest piece of crap,
and the only save was autosave!
I don't really follow,
but it sounds pretty fun!
Nope, not fun at all.
Game crash bugs.
The worst kind of trash!
Then why are you playing it?
It's fun!
Hey.
He was always smiling.
Hey, Rakuro. Is that the latest issue?
What now?
More trash game scouting?
He seemed to be enjoying himself.
That's why I started thinking about him.
I started looking for him.
'Sup, Rakuro?
Heya.
I tried to talk to him so many times...
Up all night gaming again?
As a matter of fact...
But I wasn't brave enough.
Listen to this, man!
Talk about a nightmare...
I thought, if I could just
talk to Hizutome-kun...
Trashiest trash game ever...
Even if it was inside a game...
Damn it!
This god-tier game doesn't
need a trash game arc!
I'm gonna make you cough up that info!
Severing attack! Rook-smasher!
Wh-What in the world?!
Psyger-0.
Doesn't look like the PKing type...
But I'll bet they're after the unique
scenario, same as the others.
I'm never getting out of this.
I need to think up a way out.
Can you counter my final hand?!
It requires the skill
"Spell Mastery" and single-digit HP.
A murder-suicide curse to destroy
both my opponent and myself!
I've used up the Karmic Straw Doll.
I can't reflect another curse!
I'll trade out my remaining life,
I'll inflict the "Insta-Death" debuff!
Fellow Traveler!
Well, drat.
What the...
Pencilgon-san?!
Emul. Get a gate ready.
Gwuh?!
Sorry.
Hey!
D-Damn it!
You left yourself wide open, dumbass!
Don't let him reach the city!
It's swarming with bounty hunters!
I'll remember your name, at least...
Psyger-0.
Damn it! Attack Master!
You think you can just get in our way?!
Don't look down on the Ashura Kai!
Sorry.
He talked to me!
That guy's acting pretty weird, right?
What's going on?
I dunno, but he's wide open.
Now's our chance!
PKing you will have me shooting
up the Ashura Kai ranks!
But if not for you people...
I could have talked to him more!
Make a break for it?
Yep.
Sorry, but I'll have to—
I mean, I'm taking my rage out on you!
Yes! I escaped!
Well?
How'd you like that,
you basement-dwelling bastards?!
They can't follow me to Rabituza!
That was pretty scary, though!
Didn't expect that
"Gracious! I have insufficient magic
for a gate!" from you, though.
I used it all on my transformation!
We'd have been in real trouble if
we couldn't travel from Thirdrema.
This is truly delicious!
Good thing I bought some
magic-restoring items.
Anyway, objective accomplished.
Pencil Knight... I mean, Pencilgon
sent me a sore loser email.
FYI, my death was my own fault,
so I don't consider this losing to you.
Can't believe the
Attack Master came to bail you out.
Friend of yours?
"Attack Master"?
That Psyger-0 person?
Anyway, I really do want to talk to you,
so call Katzo-kun for a
meeting in Unite Rounds.
We'll talk scheduling later.
Talk to me, eh?
The fact that she won't talk inside SLF...
Makes me suspicious.
Hey, speak of the devil.
Just got a total "evil mastermind"
invite from the pencil.
What'd you do, man?
It's fishy as hell...
but it's equally intriguing, if I'm honest.
Can't say I'm not intrigued, so I
figure we might as well hear her out.
You're not gonna back out, right?
Well, I can't back out after
Katzo starts adding pressure, too.
But I've got bigger things
to think about now.
What a lovely treat!
Sorry for the wait, Emul.
Let's get to this unique scenario for real!
Oh, at last!
Hurrah, hurrah!
So, what's the task?
That Vash guy...
I mean, your bunny boss, said something
about "getting me up to snuff."
Then I shall lead you to the arena where
we do our most serious battle training!
Arena?
The Vorpal Colosseum!
Hey, that's pretty big!
My dadd—ahem, the boss wants
you to fight ten monsters here!
Okay!
So it's a boss rush kind of thing, right?
Ah, but you are strictly limited
to the use of vorpal weapons!
Great!
Okay!
Time to grind levels until I can wipe
that smug smirk off of Pencilgon's face!
All ready.
Let out the first one!
Righty-o!
Here it comes!
I don't expect to go ten
in a row on my first try.
I'll use trial and error, learn their
attack patterns, and slowly but surely...
Practical training, opponent 1.
Packhound.
Always spawns in groups of five or more.
Average level, 65.
Looks tough.
Hang on a minute here!
You're making me fight
multiple enemies over level 65?!
Well, of course!
That's how the first opponent works!
A-At least say first fight, not opponent!
I talked to Hizutome-kun!
Sorry.
N-Next time I see him,
I'll try to find the courage
to send a friend request.
I wonder if he'd accept it...
A friend request?
Of course I'll accept!
Psyger-0, I can't thank you
enough for saving me back there.
Let's walk to school together every morning!
Oh, you silly!
But I entered Thirdrema and looked
for him after it was over,
and I couldn't find him...
Did he log out, maybe?
I wonder what he's doing now.
These guys... totally...
just think of me as food!
Sunraku-san! It's your seventh try!
This time, see that you beat them!
Thankfully, the penalty for
dying is off here in the arena.
But it's not their numbers and
level that make these guys a pain.
It's their completely
synchronized team attacks!
Repel Counter!
That coordination is the result of
having a commander giving orders!
Slide Move!
I've fought them enough times
that I've started to see it...
One monster that keeps howling
from a safe distance,
and never actually attacks!
You're the commander, aren't you?!
Spiral Edge!
Looks like I guessed right!
Your coordination's all out of whack!
And now that I know that,
I can ignore these suckers!
I'll focus on the commander
before he can bark out orders!
Get back here, you!
Gotcha!
Impressive as ever, Sunraku-san!
Monsters left on their own
after losing their commander
are nothing for me to fear!
Once you know the trick,
they're just durable dogs.
You're brilliant, Sunraku-san!
Practical training, opponent 1:
Packhound, complete.
Excellent work, Sunraku-san!
The next one's not a group, too, is it?
The next one is definitely a single opponent!
It'd better be, man.
Practical training, opponent 2:
Parasite Tentacle.
It's basically another freaking group!
Like the name implied, the real monster
was the tentacles, not the bear.
I kept up a hit-and-run
strategy on the tentacles,
and once the seventh was severed,
the bear stopped moving and I won.
"A really tough goblin"
is the only way to put it.
Tough or not, though,
he's still just a goblin.
He was easier than the
wolves or the tentacles.
This boar sucks.
Its ability to blow you up if its nose
hits you while it's charging wasn't that bad.
But it's got crazy stamina.
I timed it, and it ran about
twenty seconds on each charge.
If not for my rodeo experience,
it would've taken way longer.
That's in-game rodeo experience, by the way.
You'll pay. Oh, you will pay.
Sunraku-san!
You're a simpleton compared
to the birdy bastard
who hovered out of attack range
while dropping poison bombs.
Spend your whole life on the
ground, never growing wings.
Fast and strong but not too tough.
Once you learn that its strategy
is to get around behind you and
attack from outside your sight line,
it's easy to take down.
Not great, not terrible.
Just a pretty strong guy.
That's it.
If we call attacks from the right arm A,
and attacks from the left arm B,
when chaining from A to A,
there's almost no gap between its attacks.
But if it goes from A to B or vice-versa,
the chest core lights up for a second.
This allows for some limited
anticipation of its attacks.
Given the difference between my
height and the golem's height,
that generates some predictability
in attacks from sides A and B.
I had a theory that the
moment I dodged an attack
or the action's attack hit box faded,
I could jump on the arm to jump
up and directly attack the core.
But when I actually tried it, I ended
up repelled by an invisible energy field
which shaved 70% off my HP,
so I was forced to change my strategy,
which turned out to be directly peeling
off its armor to expose a weak point—
Oh, screw it!
I dodged, stripped it down, hit it, and won!
Hell yeah! Just one left!
Practical training, opponent 9:
Beta Unit Golem S2, complete.
Although...
All that fighting to go up two measly levels?
Thanks so much, Vorpal Soul Collar which
so generously cuts my exp gains in half...
Sunraku-san! You should
probably take a break!
You have a great and
terrible look in your eyes!
Whatcha mean?
All this optimization is going great for me!
Now, bring out the last monster already!
Well, well.
You beat the ninth already, did you?
Guess it's perfect timing.
Vash?
Dadd—I mean, Boss!
"Perfect timing," huh?
Beating the ninth monster triggered
the event flag, I'll bet.
So, Aniki.
Would that last monster happen to be...
I thought I'd make your tenth
opponent a monster I caught.
I went on a bit of an excursion for it.
A human? Yeah, don't think so...
A sorcerer type?
One of those dummies from
long, long, long ago
who tried to fuse with a
tree to gain longer life.
I doubt you can beat him
in the state you're in now,
so I'll pick a different win criteria.
What's that?
Survive five minutes.
Unique Scenario.
"Invitation From Rabituza."
Practical training, opponent 10:
Aberrant Woodmage.
Clear condition update:
survive for five minutes.
An endurance battle, huh?
Five minutes is really all I need?
So if I just stay in motion—
Was that attack even telegraphed?
I'm a fan of your confidence, kid,
but I'd like to see you back it up.
I get it! This might be a long five minutes!
Out of the over 30 million SLF players,
Sunraku is the first one
to fight this monster.
But Sunraku wouldn't learn this
until far into the future.