Remnant of the Divinity: The Aberrant Loser
Psyger-0
Poison      Paralysis          Drain          Exhaustion         Speed
See you in Hell,
Fellow Traveler!
Psyger-0
Rabituza Inn
Okay, You Got Me
From: Pencil Knight
To: Sunraku
Nice job escaping those scrubs.
FYI, my death was my own fault,
so I don't consider this losing to you.
Can't believe the Attack Master came
to bail you out. Friend of yours?
Anyway, I really do want to talk to you,
so call Katzo-kun for a meeting in Unite Rounds.
We'll talk scheduling later.
Hey
From: Modor Katzo
To: Sunraku
Just got a total "evil mastermind"
invite from the pencil. What'd you do, man?
Can't say I'm not intrigued, so I figure
we might as well hear her out.
You're not gonna back out, right?
Vorpal Colosseum
Practical Training  Opponent 1
Packhound
Always spawns in groups of 5 or more
Average Level 65
Constant Progress
Spiral Edge
Practical Training  Opponent 1
Packhound
Always spawns in groups of 5 or more
Average Level 65
Complete
Practical Training  Opponent 2
Parasite Tentacle
Defeated on
4th try
Practical Training  Opponent 3
Goblin Berserker
Defeated on
2nd try
Practical Training  Opponent 4
Dinoboar
Defeated on
1st try
Practical Training  Opponent 5
Toxic Eagle
Defeated on
112th try
Practical Training  Opponent 6
Armored Larva
Defeated on
1st try
Practical Training  Opponent 7
Execu-panther
Defeated on
1st try
Practical Training  Opponent 8
Twinhead Tiger
Defeated on
2nd try
Practical Training  Opponent 9
Beta Unit Golem S2
Defeated on
7th try
Practical Training  Opponent 9
Beta Unit Golem S2
Complete
Menacing
Unique Scenario
Invitation From Rabituza
Practical Training  Opponent 10
Aberrant Woodmage
Clear Condition
Survive for five minutes
Practical Training  Opponent 10
Aberrant Woodsman
Average Level 120
Practical Training  Opponent 10
Aberrant Woodsman
Average Level 120