I hate this place. It's swarming with bugs.
A-Are you sure we're ready
to fight the area boss?
What's gotten you so scared all of a sudden?
We've beaten everything
they've thrown at us so far!
But...
We can take this, no pro—
What the heck's this?
I can't get it off! It's too sticky!
Are you okay?
S-Soma.
Is that...
A clown?!
This world is filled with
too many games to count,
though the vast majority simply
come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of all games
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide—
Shangri-La Frontier, which rightly
earns the title of "god-tier game"!
One lover of trash games, Rakuro Hizutome,
is trying out the god-tier
game, Shangri-La Frontier!
What adventures await him there?
The area boss here is a spider, right?
Yes, indeed!
It's called the Clown Spider!
So... we're probably getting close.
Okay!
Huh? I can't go in?
It appears other pioneers
have already engaged it!
Damn it! I gotta climb all
the way back up there?
This boss is such a pain in the ass.
This isn't over! One good hit and I'm—
It flattened that pioneer!
Rest in peace.
Welp, path's open. Let's go!
You didn't mourn him for long!
He's just respawning in Thirdrema. Chill out.
But thanks to Mr. Pancake there,
I got some useful info.
Emul.
You mind hanging out here
and doing color commentary?
I wanna solo the Clown Spider
on my first try, with a no-damage run.
And you really want me
to stay here and watch?
Yeah.
Okay! Let's do this, area boss!
I'm fighting a spider.
The webbing's gonna get
denser the higher I get.
Out of the skills I learned
leveling up in the arena...
I think my best bet here'll be...
Skill...
One-Boat Leap!
Bet you use that to insta-kill first-timers.
Good thing I saw you use it already.
Sunraku-san! You're heading right for...
a sticky web!
It wasn't sticky?!
The radial threads of a
spider's web aren't sticky.
That makes it a little harder
to get stable footing.
But if I judge it just right...
Skill, Accel Lv. 6!
It's not too different from
running around that forest!
I-Incredible!
The time for sitting back and throwing
stuff is over, Clown Spider.
Loop Slash!
Right leg down!
Rush Slash!
A fall from that height should
dish out some juicy damage.
Not a damn chance!
Th-That looked quite painful!
Probably won't be enough to beat it, but...
Well, lookie there!
Aiming's a breeze against a target that big!
I really got you in a tough spot, huh?
Oh, you're brilliant, Sunraku-san!
You can easily make it
through unharmed like this!
There we go.
Well, that's all fun enough, but...
Sunraku-san?
Hup!
If I can't beat an area boss head-to-head...
I'll never make it
to Lycagon's level!
Sunraku-san!
Well, Emul?
I called it. First-time, no-damage run.
Yes indeed!
You're a true man of your word!
Felt almost too easy.
It went right to his head!
Hey, an email from Pencil Knight.
Oh, it's about that.
I thought Sunraku picking this game
up would be a good reason to try it...
But soloing these bosses isn't the
challenge they made it out to be...
I hope what you've got in
store has a little more bite.
Hey, he accepted your friend request?
That's so great!
Y-Yes.
I worked up my nerve, and he accepted it.
I couldn't have done it
without your encouragement.
But Hizutome-kun really is amazing!
Not only did he skip the first town,
he's got a Vorpal Bunny companion!
We all thought you couldn't tame those!
Wow. Well, that's a trash gamer for you.
Welcome!
He hasn't been here for a few days.
Guess he's been in SLF the whole time?
He's a real wild card, though.
He might even be the first
to dispatch a unique monster!
Oh, not even he could do that!
Actually, maybe he could!
Hey, an interview with Katzo.
That guy talks so much shit.
I bet he made the editor's job hell.
SLF's getting a major summer update?
The Severed Sea.
The Frontier Fleet.
The New Land, and a new job...
I guess this is the one Pencilgon
was talking about yesterday.
Hello, hello!
Thank you both for coming today.
When was the last time we were all
together here in Unite Rounds?
Was it when you jackasses stormed my castle,
which had an eighty-player garrison?
Look, that was Sunraku's idea.
"Assassinating the monarch
sounds like a blast!" he said.
You were just as down for it!
Hell yeah, I was.
And it freaking ruled!
Yeah, I wasn't expecting it to end with her
blowing up the castle and
all her retainers with it!
Yeah, the Pencil Dynasty Incident.
They'll be talking about that one 'til
the Unite Rounds servers shut down!
Yeah.
And she acts like it was just part
of her "live in the moment" attitude,
but you can tell she's
still so pissed about it!
She'll start making excuses even
when no one's brought it up—
Now that we're all feeling nice and relaxed,
do you mind if I get to the main topic?
Yes, ma'am!
Good.
I'm betting you called us here to say
more than just "Let's play SLF together."
That's right.
We don't have a lot of time,
so I'll get right to the point.
Want to take out the unique monster,
Wethermon the Tombguard,
with just the three of us?
Huh?! A unique monster?!
A unique monster...
That's the same category of monster as
that Lycagon thing Sunraku fought, right?!
Are you for real?!
I'm dying to fight those unique guys!
That's right.
One of the Seven Colossi
of Shangri-La Frontier...
Wethermon the Tombguard.
Hold on a minute.
I figured she'd be inviting us on
some high-level clan raid, but...
You said "just the three of us"?
Yes.
And you think we stand a chance?
I don't know jack about
this "Wethermon" thing.
Well, it's not like you can beat
him with sheer force of numbers.
We went at him with Ashura Kai's
fifteen best and got wasted.
Is this the kind of monster that gets
more attack and HP the more
people you send at it?
That's part of it, but...
I can't tell you more until
I have your agreement.
We get one chance at this.
We'll carry it out in two weeks.
The night of the new moon,
right after the major summer update.
That's the day we'll do it.
What do you think?
Right after the update?
Why invite a pair of SLF newbies, though?
Wouldn't she want a few max-level elites?
If you're worried about your levels,
that won't be a problem.
What I'm after is pure player skill.
That's why I'm enlisting
Katzo-kun, the pro gamer,
and Sunraku-kun, the trash gamer.
You sure those two things are comparable?
Feel free to back off, trash gamer.
You're stinking up my pro gamer rep.
What was that?!
So, what do you think?
I can always offer additional compensation.
Well... I think I might be down.
But I also think you're
still hiding something.
If you want us to buy in,
you'd better give us the full story.
All right.
Shall we begin our strategy meeting?
Thank you for coming!
E-Excuse me!
H-Hizutome-kun...
H-Hello!
Hey, isn't she...
Pretty sure she was in my class last year...
Um...
Ga... Ga-san...
Her name, her name...
It was something-ga-san!
Just hold on.
Rack your brain, man.
Iga? Koga?
That's it!
You're Saiga-san!
Y-Yes, that's right!
I'm Rei Saiga!
Hell yeah!
I-Isn't it funny that
we ran into each other?!
Yeah, sure is.
W-Were you shopping?
Y-Yeah...
What about you?
I'm on my way to practice...
Practice?
Judo—
Er, I mean... well...
Oh, Mana-san from Rock Roll told me...
You started playing Shangri-La Frontier?
Oh, yeah.
I'm playing.
So... er... I...
I also play... SLF, so...
Oh?
It even gets girls from
rich old families playing?
SLF's really something.
D-Do you think... w-we could play...?
Oh, sorry. Got an email.
Hang on.
R-Right! G-Go ahead!
"Get over here"?
Yeah, figured it'd be Pencilgon.
Can't I even buy groceries in peace?
And she's double emailing! Scary...
Sorry, Saiga-san!
I've got a friend who won't wait.
Gotta go!
See you later!
O-Of course!
I'm so sorry I kept you!
That was so exciting!
We talked so much!
But Hizutome-kun...
He had so many energy drinks.
I suppose he'll be playing SLF for a while...
Maybe I'll get to see him soon!
Oh, I've got to get to practice!
Shoot. I should've asked Saiga-san's handle.
Welcome to Shangri-La Frontier.
Good morning, Sunraku-san!
Emul. Back off.
Righty-o!
Well? What's on the agenda today!
First, I've got a question for you.
What is it?
It looks like, in two weeks,
I'll be picking a fight with
"Wethermon the Tombguard."
It's looking like I'll have to leave
you out of the party while I do...
What's wrong?
Picking a fight with Wethermon?!
D-Da... Bo...
Daboo... Bodadd...
I've got to tell my daddy!
Hey!
What's her problem?
I'm late to see Pencilgon as it is!
Here's a question.
What is it?
You said "just the three of us,"
but I've got an NPC in my party right now.
What about her?
Oh, the infamous bunny.
Bunny?
If you care about her,
you should keep her out of it.
What's with the bunny?
What do you mean?
In SLF...
Oh, dear! Oh, dear!
Once an NPC dies...
It's truly terrible!
They never come back.
Daddy!