Let's Go Tomb Raiding!!
Other players are
fighting this area boss.
Rush Slash
Quick Spin
Loop Slash Lv. 5
Accel Lv. 6
One-Boat Leap
Area Boss
Clown Spider
Loop Slash
Throwing Knife
equipped.
Area Boss
Clown Spider
Dispatch Complete
Let's get up to some mischief!
From: Pencil Knight
To: Modor Katzo
Oikatzo
Major Summer Update!!
The Severed Sea
The Frontier Fleet
The New Land
Kei Uomi
Pro Gamer
Pencil Knight
Sunraku
Katzo Tataki
Pencil Knight
Sunraku
Katzo Tataki
Weekly
VR Full Diver
Comes with
B3 Poster
of the cover page
Judo
From: Pencil Knight
To: Sunraku
Get over here
Are you dying of remorse over keeping me waiting?
Are you okay? Should I call an ambulance?