I hate this place. It's crawling with bugs.
A-Are you sure we're ready to fight the area boss?
What's gotten you so scared all of a sudden?
We've beaten everything they've thrown at us so far!
But...
We can take this, no pro—
What the heck's this?
I can't get it off! It's too sticky!
Are you okay?
S-Soma?
Is that...
a clown?!
This world is filled with countless games...
though the vast majority simply come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of them all
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide.
It rightly earns the status of "god-tier," Shangri-La Frontier!
One lover of trash games, Hizutome Rakurou,
is trying out this very Triple-A!
What adventures await him there?
The area boss here is a spider, right?
Yes, indeed!
It's called the Clown Spider!
So... we're probably getting close.
Found it!
Huh? I can't go in?
It appears other pioneers have already engaged it!
Dammit! I gotta climb all the way back up there?
This boss is such a pain in the ass.
This isn't over! One good hit and I'm—
It flattened that pioneer!
Fs in the chat.
Welp, path's open. Let's go!
You didn't mourn him for long!
He's just respawning in Thirdrema. Chill out.
But thanks to Mr. Pancake there, I got some useful info.
Emul, mind hanging out here and doing color commentary?
I wanna solo the Clown Spider
on my first try, with a no-damage run.
And you really want me to stay here and watch?
Yeah.
Okay! Let's do this, area boss!
I'm fighting a spider.
The webbing's gonna get denser the higher I get.
Out of the skills I learned leveling up in the arena...
I think my best bet here'll be...
Skill...
One-Boat Leap!
Bet you use that to insta-kill first-timers.
Good thing I saw you use it already.
Sunraku! You're heading right for...
a sticky web...
It wasn't sticky?!
The radial threads of a spider's web aren't, actually.
That makes it a little harder to get a stable footing.
But if I judge it just right...
Skill, Accel Lvl. 6!
It's not too different from running around that forest!
I-Incredible!
The time for sitting back
and throwing stuff is over, Clown Spider.
Loop Slash!
Right leg, down!
Rush Slash!
A fall from that height should dish out some juicy damage.
Not a damn chance!
Th-That looked quite painful!
Probably won't be enough to beat it, but...
Well, lookie there!
Aiming's a breeze against a target that big!
I really got you in a tough spot, huh?
Oh, you're brilliant, Sunraku!
You can easily make it through unharmed like this!
There we go.
Well, that's all fun enough, but...
Sunraku?
Hup!
If I can't beat an area boss head-to-head...
I'll never make it to Lycagon's level!
Sunraku!
Well, Emul?
I called it. First-try, no-damage run.
Yes, indeed!
You're a true man of your word!
Felt almost too easy.
And it went straight to his head!
Hey, an email from Pencil Knight.
Oh, it's about that.
I thought Sunraku picking this game up
would be a good reason to try it...
But soloing these bosses was way overhyped.
I hope you've got us something
that packs a little more punch.
Hey, he accepted your friend request?
That's so great!
Y-Yes.
I worked up the nerve, and he accepted it.
I couldn't have done it without your encouragement.
But he really is amazing!
Not only did he skip the first town,
he's got a Vorpal Bunny companion!
We all thought you couldn't tame those!
Wow. Well, that's a trash gamer for you.
Welcome!
He hasn't been here for a few days.
Guess he's been in SLF the whole time?
He's a real wild card, though.
He might even be the first to dispatch a unique monster!
Oh, not even he could do that!
Actually, maybe he could!
Hey, an interview with Katzo.
That guy talks so much shit.
I bet he made the editor's job hell.
SLF's getting a major summer update?
The Severed Sea.
The Frontier Fleet.
The New Land, and a new job...
I guess this is the one Pencilgon
was talking about yesterday.
Hello, hello!
Thank you both for coming today.
When was the last time
we were all together here in Unite Rounds?
Was it when you jackasses stormed my castle,
which had an 80-player garrison?
Look, that was all Sunraku's idea.
"Let's assassinate the king. It'll be fun!" he said.
You were just as down for it!
Hell yeah, I was.
And it freaking ruled!
Yeah, I wasn't expecting it to end with her blowing up
the castle and all her retainers with it!
Yeah, the Pencil Dynasty Incident!
They'll be talking about that one
'til the Unite Rounds servers shut down!
Yeah.
And she acts like it was just
part of her "live in the moment" attitude,
but you can tell she's still so pissed about it!
She'll start making excuses
even when no one's brought it up—
Now that we're all feeling nice and relaxed,
do you mind if I get to the main topic?
Yes, ma'am!
Good.
I'm betting you didn't call us here just to play SLF together.
That's right. We don't have a lot of time...
so I'll get right to the point.
Want to take out the unique monster,
Wethermon the Tombguard, with just the three of us?
Huh?! A unique monster?!
A unique monster?
It's the same category as that Lycagon thing
Sunraku fought, right?!
Are you for real?!
I'm dying to fight those guys!
That's right.
One of the Seven Colossi of Shangri-La Frontier...
Wethermon the Tombguard.
Hold on a minute.
I figured she'd be inviting us
on some high-level clan raid, but...
You said "just the three of us"?
Yes.
And you think we stand a chance?
I don't know jack about this "Wethermon" thing.
Well, it's not like you can beat him
with sheer force of numbers.
We went at him with Ashura Kai's 15 best and got wasted.
Is this the kind of monster that gets more attack
and HP the more people you send at it?
That's part of it, yes.
But I can't tell you more until I have your agreement.
We get one chance at this.
We'll carry it out in two weeks.
The night of the new moon,
right after the major summer update.
That's the day we'll do it.
What do you say?
Right after the update?
Why invite a pair of SLF newbies, though?
Wouldn't she want a few max-level elites?
If you're worried about your levels,
that won't be a problem.
What I'm after is pure player skill.
That's why I'm enlisting...
Katzo, the pro gamer,
and Sunraku, the trash gamer.
You sure those two things are comparable?
Feel free to back off, trash gamer.
You're stinking up my pro gamer rep.
What was that?!
So, what do you think?
I can always offer additional compensation.
Well... I think I might be down.
But I also think you're still hiding something.
If you want us to buy in, you'd better give us the full story.
All right.
Shall we begin our strategy meeting?
Thank you for coming!
E-Excuse me!
H-Hizutome...
H-Hello!
Hey, isn't she...
Pretty sure she was in my class last year...
Um...
Ga... Gary...
Her name, her name...
It was ga-something!
Just hold on.
Rack your brain, man.
Ga... Ga...
Iga? Koga?
That's it!
You're Miss Saiga!
Y-Yes, that's right!
I'm Saiga Rei!
Hell yeah!
I-Isn't it funny that we ran into each other?!
Yeah, sure is.
W-Were you shopping?
Y-Yeah...
What about you?
I'm on my way to practice...
Practice?
Judo—
Er, I mean... well...
Oh, Miss Mana from Rock Roll told me...
You started playing Shangri-La Frontier?
Oh, yeah.
I'm playing.
So... er, I...
I also play... SLF, so...
Oh?
It even gets girls from rich old families playing?
SLF's really something.
D-Do you think... w-we could play...
Oh, sorry. Got an email.
Hang on.
R-Right! G-Go ahead!
"Get over here"?
Yeah, figured it'd be Pencilgon.
Can't I even buy groceries in peace?
And she's spamming me! Scary...
Sorry, Saiga!
I've got a friend who won't wait.
Gotta go!
See you later!
O-Of course!
I'm so sorry I kept you!
That was so exciting!
We talked so much!
But Hizutome...
He had so many energy drinks.
I suppose he'll be playing SLF for a while.
Maybe I'll get to see him soon!
Oh, I've got to get to practice!
Shoot. I should've asked for her handle.
Welcome to Shangri-La Frontier.
Good morning, Sunraku!
Emul. Back off.
Righty-o!
Well? What's on the agenda today!
First, I've got a question for you.
What is it?
It looks like in two weeks,
I'll be picking a fight with "Wethermon the Tombguard."
Seems like I'll have to leave you out of the party while I do...
What's wrong?
Picking a fight with Wethermon?!
D-Da... Bo...
Daboo... Bodadd...
I've got to tell my daddy!
Hey!
What's her problem?
I'm late to see Pencilgon as it is!
Here's a question.
What is it?
You said "just the three of us,"
but I've got an NPC in my party right now.
What about her?
Oh, the infamous bunny.
Bunny?
If you care about her, you should keep her out of it.
What's with the bunny?
What do you mean?
In SLF...
Oh, dear! Oh, dear!
Once an NPC dies...
It's truly terrible!
...they never come back.
Daddy!