SLF Theater!
SLF Mini
Mini!
H-Hello, there!
I'm Psyger-0!
I'd like to show you the prologue text that
rolls at the start of Shangri-La Frontier,
which Hizutome-kun skipped!
Take it away!
The land is vast, and through it is woven the grand tapestry of life...
We, who live in the here and now, use the artifacts of the past
still breathing in history and ruins to trace the footsteps of the Divine.
You are a pioneer, appearing with the wind from the east, and though
brought to your knees time and again, you brave ever onward...
And, like the wind, some of you will simply fade away.
What is the purpose of your life?
Will you trust your life to the swing of your sword?
Will you peer into the depths of the magical arts
and seek to master your craft?
Or will you choose not to fight at all?
All options can be found here.
All options exist within you.
Now, take your first step.
Explore the unknown, your future, and your potential.
This is the mission given unto you,
the children of the Divinity born—fallen—upon this land.
Divine? Divinity?
There's so much intriguing jargon, isn't there?
Well, see you again soon!
Bye-bye!
SLF Theater!
SLF Mini
Mini!
Oh, no! I hit him!
What the hell is your problem?!
What are you even doing in that carriage?!
I told you to wait on the dang bench!
Tee-hee
Curse you, dark lord!
He's the reason all of this is happening!
But this is all your fault!
Tee-hee
Now I'm mad!
I'm not going anywhere with you!
Huh?!
You're the one who causes all the problems,
and I'm the one fighting, not you!
Tee-hee