~The Prayer of the Fairy Princess~
Simulated Environment
Not Trash Games
Semi-Redeemable Trash Games
Never Play Again
Rakuro Hizutome
High School 2nd-Year
What Do You Play Games For?
Soft & Fluffy Melon Pan
Towa Amane
The Celebrity Model on Fashion's Bleeding Edge
Municipal
Mahinoki
High School
Mana Iwamaki
Owner of "Rock Roll"
Rei Saiga
High School 2nd-Year
BLUSH
Tee-hee
Huh?!
Summer Break Promotion!!
Now Adding Servers!
Create New Character
Brawler (Axes)
Brawler (Mauls)
Brawler (Fists)
Knight (Swords)
Knight (Longswords)
Knight (Polearms)
Knight (Mauls)
Monk (Fists)
Monk (Staffs)
Monk (Mauls)
Mercenary (Swords)
Mercenary (Greatswords)
Mercenary (Longswords)
Mercenary (Polearms)
Mercenary (Mauls)
Mercenary (Bows)
Mercenary (Twin Swords)
Bandit (Daggers)
Bandit (Bows)
Bandit (Swords)
Blacksmith (Mauls)
Archaeologist (Swords)
Archaeologist (Bows)
Magician (Staffs)
Magician (Books)
Cleric (Staffs)
Cleric (Mauls)
Swordsman (Swords)
Swordsman (Greatswords)
Swordsman (Longswords)
Swordsman (Twin Swords)
Warrior (Swords)
Warrior (Greatswords)
Warrior (Longswords)
Warrior (Axes)
Warrior (Mauls)
Warrior (Polearms)
Warrior (Twin Swords)
Warrior (Mauls)
Warrior (Polearms)
Warrior (Twin Swords)
Brawler (Sword)
Brawler (Greatsword)
Brawler (Longsword)
Brawler (Axes)
Brawler (Mauls)
Brawler (Fists)
Knight (Swords)
Knight (Longswords)
Knight (Polearms)
Knight (Mauls)
Monk (Fists)
Mercenary
(Twin Swords)
Swordmaster
Wanderer
Optimist
Obvious Talent
Build Type 1-7
Musculature
Face
Skin
Eye Shape
Eye Color
Nose
Mouth
Ears
All
Hair Ornament
Necklace
Bracelet
Ring
Mercenary Twinblade
Staring Bird Mask
None
9000 Mahni
Is this all right?
Try Again          Confirm
Mercenary Twinblade
Leather Cap
Leather Garb
Leather Belt
Leather Shoes
None
3000 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
Leather Garb
Leather Belt
Leather Shoes
None
3000 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
Leather Garb
Leather Belt
Leather Shoes
None
3300 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
Leather Garb
Leather Belt
Leather Shoes
None
3600 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
Leather Garb
Leather Belt
Leather Shoes
None
4000 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
Leather Belt
Leather Shoes
None
4400 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
Leather Belt
Leather Shoes
None
4800 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
Leather Belt
Leather Shoes
None
5000 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
Leather Belt
Leather Shoes
None
5400 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
Leather Shoes
5800 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
Leather Shoes
6000 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
Leather Shoes
6400 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
Leather Shoes
6800 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
7200 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
7500 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
7700 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
8000 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
8400 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
8900 Mahni
Mercenary Twinblade
None
9000 Mahni
Tripled!!
Traveler's Hat
Mercenary's Helm
Clergy's Hat
Knight's Helm
Staring Bird Mask
Please input name
Sunraku
Hizutome Rakuro
Hi (Sun)
Raku
Sunraku
Link established.
Please lie down in a safe place.
Long ago, there was a time known as the Divinity. The great and powerful members of the Divine moved on to the next world and disappeared.
Since then, time has passed.
We, the heirs to the Divine will
Introduction
Pioneers, Feel the Night Wind
The Rampant Forest
Sunraku
Firstia
Mercenary (Twin Blade User) Skill Points Remaining: 0
Cash on Hand  9000 Mahni
HP: 30
Stamina: 20
Strength: 10
Dexterity:15
Vitality: 3
Magic: 10
Agility: 10
Tech: 15
Luck: 30
Mercenary Twinblade
Dropped Item
Goblin Hand Axe
Vorpal Bunny
Condition Achieved
You Learned
Flash Counter
New Skill
Bonus added to counters from parry.
Parry: Deflecting an attack with your weapon
Invisibility Bug
Clipping Bug
Swish
Hitbox Bug
Spin Slash
A spinning slash area attack
Vorpal Bunny
Play Time
Vorpal Chopper
Bonus to critical damage.
Spin Slash
Flash Counter
Tap Step
Screw Pierce
New Skill
Deals a quick strike with a compact weapon
This attack is powerful but cannot be chained
The Rampant Forest
Firstia
Secondale
Sunraku
Ravenous Python
Area Boss
Rec. Level:
Rec. Party Size:
The Rampant Forest