At last...
At last, the dark lord is defeated!
You've done it, Sunraku!
Thank you!
It's been such a long,
hard journey, hasn't it?
Yes.
I've been waiting so long
for this very moment...
Faeria.
Now, you can go with the dark lord
straight to hell!
You're the real dark lord here!
You're the real menace to the world!
Heck yeah!
I finally beat Failia Chronicle!
And I got my revenge
for everything she put me through!
Yeah!
In an age where display-based
games are considered retro,
and fully immersive VR games
have become the norm...
Beneath the small number
of works of significance
lies a massive pile of releases
whose game designs don't live up
to their improved graphics technology.
They are known as "trash games."
Although most people
rightfully despise trash games,
there are those who gleefully seek them out.
We call these people "freaks."
The rumors were true.
What a giant pile of garbage!
This man here, Rakuro Hizutome,
is one of these freaks.
I feel so free!
Is this how a convict finishing up
a prison sentence feels?
Now, what trash game will I try next?
He is known as the "Trash-Game Hunter."
Morning!
Oh, no one's here.
Mom, one of your butterflies got out.
Oh, drat! Thanks for telling me!
Heading out!
Have a good day!
Where're you going for summer break?
Heading to Hawaii in two days!
Awesome!
You?
Makuhari.
Going to the game expo?
Hey, great idea!
E-Excuse me... Hizutome-kun...
Wh-What have you been up to?
Th-That's not what I meant!
I meant to ask... what game are you playing?
Oh, really? The truth is, I also—
Okay!
Hizu—
'Sup, Rakuro?
Heya.
Up all night gaming again?
As a matter of fact...
Listen to this, man!
Talk about a nightmare...
Trashiest trash game ever...
Summer vacation starts tomorrow, then?
That should bring in some business, I'll bet.
Come on in!
Oh, Rei-chan!
Hello, there!
On the way back from practice?
Yes.
Sorry, but he's not here today, either.
O-Oh, I just came to look at the games—
C'mon, I know you too well
for that little act.
Aw, you lucky girl!
Oh, to be young and in love!
M-Mana-san!
He's been trying to crack
an extra-special trash game,
so he hasn't been by in a while.
"Extra-special"?
That one there's his latest.
Failia Chronicle.
It might take him a bit longer yet.
Oh, Faeria Chronicle Online...
My sister told me about that one.
She said it was really hard!
It's a legendary trash game.
Miserable ally AI,
utterly absurd enemy attack patterns,
and more bugs in the code
than you can shake a stick at.
I hear you need serious skills
to even beat the first boss.
It's caused tons of players to
throw their headsets in frustration!
On top of that, I've heard
you gotta fight the final boss
in board shorts and a mask!
Why in the world would you do that?
No idea.
I assume it's an efficiency
thing or something.
So? Are you making progress, Rei-chan?
Yes. I am, but—
Got any decent trash games in?
Hey! Been a while, Hizutome-kun!
Oh?
And... she's gone.
Oh, nothing.
Wait, did you beat Failia already?
You bet!
I took that sucker down!
How was it?
It was a spectacular pile of garbage!
Glad to hear it.
The biggest pile of garbage
was that female lead.
Her name's "Faeria,"
and she ticked me off to no end!
She's the cause of pretty much every
problem you run into on the journey,
and then she makes the situation worse and
gets villagers and party members killed!
Oh, no! I hit him!
What the hell is your problem?!
What are you even doing in that carriage?!
And if you expect her to suffer
consequences for any of it...
Curse you, dark lord!
He's the reason all of this is happening!
She always finds a way to
blame it all on the last boss!
That guy didn't do squat!
You're the real problem here!
The same thing happens anywhere you go,
but if you give her even the tiniest
little shove to vent your annoyance...
Now I'm mad!
I'm not going anywhere with you!
She refuses to move the story along!
The autosave locks you
into that state of affairs,
and it takes three freaking hours
to get back in her good graces!
Then there's this, that,
and the other thing...
Just thinking about it ticks me off again!
I'm impressed you didn't throw in the towel.
Oh, but you see, that's how they get you!
In the three minutes between beating the final
boss and before the credits start rolling,
I guess because it's technically a cutscene,
you can beat the crap out of Faeria
without fear of reprisal!
It's so ironic. The more Faeria annoys you,
the more determined you
become to brave that hell
to experience that three minutes of heaven.
But when that moment finally arrives...
It's as if all that's wiped away!
You feel like you understand
why you were put on this Earth.
Glad to hear you had fun.
But since Failia turned out to be
such a remarkable trash pile,
I can't think of what to follow it up with.
In that case,
why not play something that's
not a trash game for once?
Not a trash game?
Experiencing the lows in life
can help you appreciate the highs.
The reverse is true, as well.
The fully immersive VR game
with over 30 million players...
Shangri-La Frontier?
It can be fun to try things designed
for mass appeal now and then.
Right?
The opposite of a trash game...
A real god-tier game, huh?
Shangri-La Frontier, AKA SLF.
It went on the market last spring
and set a Guinness World Record
for simultaneous player log-ins.
The concept is...
A colony fleet that came from space died out,
but not before leaving a new society behind.
Thousands of years later,
the PCs are living their lives
at roughly medieval tech levels.
A setup that allows for effortless
inclusion of sci-fi elements...
Unlike Failia, which is so bad
the haters find themselves desperately
searching for redeeming features,
this game is so beloved that its few haters
are completely drowned out
by tens of thousands of fans.
Utopia Entertainment Software.
"UES" for short.
Founded by the genius
programmer Tsukuyo Tsukuri,
who developed the fully
immersive VR game system,
it's a leader in the fields
of software development,
hardware, and Internet service provision.
If SLF was produced in-house at UES,
there's no way it can be bad.
How long's it been since I played
something that wasn't a trash game?
I did log in, right?
Looks like I pick my job first.
Wow, look at that!
How many kinds are there?
A twinblade mercenary
sounds pretty flexible.
Next, origin...
"Wanderer" builds defense slowly,
but gets bonuses to luck.
Luck affects your critical chance and item
drop rate in this game, so I'll take that.
Next, to design my character!
Wow, I can even choose race and body type!
I can even start the game with accessories?!
Chill out, man!
You've been so poisoned by those
super-limited trash games,
you're getting blown away
by silly minor stuff!
Okay!
Time to go hardcore on character
design for the first time in forever!
To protect Rakuro's good name,
I'll explain this state of affairs.
He's not into freak fashion
or anything like that.
His playstyle consists of
ignoring armor in favor of getting
the best weapons possible.
These weapons are costly, of course,
but in SLF, amazingly,
you're given the option to sell your starter
equipment during character creation!
And you can make quite a profit!
If I wanna hide my face...
This mask's my only option, huh?
Still, in a big-time game like this,
it'd be pretty awkward to play
half-naked if everyone could see my face.
This was, therefore, the inevitable result.
Player name... Sunraku.
Incidentally, Rakuro is the type of player who
uses the same name in every game he plays.
Link established.
Please lie down in a safe place.
Okay! All ready to go.
Hey, a prologue.
Let's skip that...
Okay, show me the power
of a god-tier game!
A forest?
Awesome!
Moving around feels
pretty much like real life!
I can run!
I can grab!
I can climb!
Failia was so awkward to move around in...
Actually, it feels like
an insult to compare them.
Whoa! It's huge!
So this is the world of SLF...
So... where am I, exactly?
Don't games like these usually start you
off in a tutorial town for beginners?
What Sunraku didn't realize
is that those who choose
"Wanderer" as their origin
will start out at a random
point in the beginners' area.
This starter map looks pretty basic.
Let's see...
This is "The Rampant Forest,"
and to the east is
the starting town, "Firstia."
Guess that's it.
Okay, I'll head roughly in that
direction while I check things out!
I can even land properly!
I know this stuff should go without saying,
but actually getting to
play it feels so good!
Vitality: 3.
Figures I'd have low defense with
the half-naked thing going on...
We'll have to see how far
that high luck stat gets me.
Right as I start playing?!
A Goblin, huh?
In that case...
Let's see what this combat engine's made of!
Wow, a one-hit kill?
But it's just a scrub enemy
in the intro, I guess.
Hey, I leveled up!
Says it can be dual-wielded,
so it's an option...
But its durability is already down to half.
Probably won't last much longer, then.
Monster weaknesses,
patterns, and item drops...
There's a lot to learn here.
Trash game or god-tier game, you
get this feeling everywhere...
The elation of diving
head-first into a new world...
You just can't get that in real life!
Okay, let's not forget to enjoy this!
Well, would you look at that?
One hit from that could put me down.
One critical won't do it for this one, huh?!
Is this all you've got, god-tier game?
If you go for the neck
with every single pass,
I'm gonna figure out what you're doing.
Look at all that EXP!
He was a tough little guy, huh?
No weapon drops, though, huh?
I wanted that knife!
I bet it's powerful as heck!
"Condition Achieved"?
I can learn skills by taking
certain actions, huh?
Hey, yeah, I haven't used any skills yet...
This game's pretty well designed.
Since a player's own skill
supplements your dodges and parries,
I can fight pretty well against
even higher-level enemies.
That makes me wanna try a bunch
of different fighting styles!
Hang on!
Have I been played this whole time
without encountering a single bug?!
What's going on? I can't see anything!
Hey, I found a hidden world!
Darn it! Why can't I hit you?!
Awesome! That's a god-tier game for you!
I honestly wasn't sure if I could enjoy
a bug-free game after all this time,
but I can really have a good time with this!
I guess they don't call it
"god-tier" for nothing!
Okay!
I'm gonna get me a tough
bunny's kitchen knife!
Where are you, bunny?!
That skill's kinda crummy.
The big flashy swing
leaves me open for too long.
Hey, finally leveled again.
I should probably allocate
my stat points already...
I wish that Vorpal Bunny thing
had a higher spawn rate, though...
Guess it was a rare enemy, huh?
It took me forever to get
a matching set of those knives!
Since I beat about fifty of 'em...
I guess that's a drop rate of about 5 percent or so?
This thing's pretty darn rare, huh?
They've got better stats
than the Mercenary Twinblade,
so I'd better take good care of 'em.
And I learned a few new skills...
But Screw Pierce seems
like the only useful one.
The others seem more
"better than nothing" tier.
Still, I'm not gonna gain any more levels
with the scrub-tier monsters around here.
I'd better move on.
I've strayed pretty far away
from the starting town, huh?
At this point, I'm a lot closer
to the next one, Secondale.
To get to Secondale...
I've gotta cross this bridge
over the ravine, huh?
Aha, I see.
I gotta beat you if
I wanna cross. Is that it?
Sounds good to me.
Looks like I've got me
a real challenge at last.
Soloing a boss meant for a party, huh?
With the great ratings SLF gets,
it probably won't be dishing out
any silly bug attacks.
A snake monster's attacks
usually consist of...
Coil, bite, tail swipe, swallow, venom...
That should be all.
With an avatar that actually
moves the way I want it to,
I don't need defenses to beat you!
Give me something to enjoy here,
SLF!