Bird with Rabbits vs. Skeletal Choir
Canyon of Ancient Souls
Crystal Scorpion
Area Boss
Humming Lich
Sunraku
Rabbit Gun: Turret Palm
Buff = Enhancement
Overheat
Can only activate
10 minutes after combat starts.
Adds a bonus to all stats
for five minutes,
but halves all stats after that.
Nitro Gain
Time to use: 1 second
In exchange for taking 20%
of max HP as damage,
increases STR and AGI.
Sunraku
Overheat
Climax Boost
Nitro Gain
Glowing Pierce
Fortress Breaker
Rabbit Pile Bunker
Sunraku
Har-
rumph
Dropped Item
Grudge Bone Fragment
A hideous bone fragment,
soaked to its marrow with hatred.
Has various shamanistic uses.
Its grudge cannot be alleviated,
because the nature of grudges
is to be indiscriminate.
Canyon of Ancient Souls
Eighthold
Eighth City
Register landmark?
No        Yes
Landmark registered.
Wah ha ha ha ha
Eighthold
Canyon of Ancient Souls