Hell yeah!
Let's start the plan to cultivate Bilac!
Yes, indeed!
Y-Yeah!
Okay! Let's head through Fourfolkshire
and on to the Canyon of Ancient Souls!
Get moving, bird-man!
We'll need that magic operations unit to
make you an Ancient Craftsman, right, Bilac?
This area's been a real breeze, huh?
I'm betting the miasma
and the undead and stuff
would normally be a pain in the ass...
But Sunraku-san's mark clears up the
miasma and chases the monsters away,
so it's truly a walk in the park!
On that note, would you guys...
just walk on your own already?!
Walking is far too troublesome!
You've got the Night Emperor's mark, buddy.
Clinging to you lets us conserve Holy Water.
So deal with it.
What am I, your personal air purifier?
Just get walking.
Half-naked with a bird head, walking through
miasma with rabbits on my shoulders...
Not exactly my personal fantasy.
Hey, what's going on overtop of the mist?
Feels like we could climb up if we wanted...
Would that make it even
easier to get to the end?
Might work out if you're feeling suicidal,
but I'll pass, myself.
Atop the cliffs of the
Canyon of Ancient Souls
lurk terrifying monsters known
as the Crystal Scorpions!
Crystal Scorpions?
They're a bunch of tough
nuts not even I could crack.
Crystal Scorpions attack as a swarm,
so if one sees you, you're dead.
What, they're over level 100 or something?
A shortcut for super-veterans, maybe?
Thought I saw a figure moving just now...
Was it just my imagination?
What was it? A Crystal Scorpion?!
I hear that the sight of one means
dozens more are on their way!
Just get walking already!
We're after the area boss, remember?!
Yeah, yeah, I get it!
Crystal Scorpions, huh?
Maybe I'll pick me a fight later on.
Didn't you hear what I just said?!
Don't even joke about such a thing!
What's this black dome thing?
Guess this is our destination.
Looks like an area boss to me, yeah.
There's not someone in there already, right?
We've just gotta fight it in here?
Then let's beat the thing
and move right along!
Yes, let us!
Give it your best shot, bird-man!
Sunraku-san—
Well, well.
Yep.
That's what we're after.
The kind of skelly jerk a
certain type is really into...
Humming Lich.
I'm getting "skeleton that
dishes out curses" vibes.
So before it throws anything
too annoying at us...
Strike first!
Hang on a minute!
That thing's—
Huh? No hitbox?
You moron.
You need a holy-attribute weapon
to deal physical damage!
Huh? But I don't got a holy-attribute weapon!
What fearsome miasma!
That kinda stings!
It's the source of the miasma in the canyon.
You're being hit by all the
hatred and death around us!
It's more potent than ordinary miasma!
Hey... we're okay.
Thanks to Sunraku-san's mark, no doubt!
I did take a bit of damage, but that
debuff resistance is doing its work.
Can't believe it works even
on an area boss's attacks.
But wait, hang on...
If neither of our attacks
works on the other one...
Does that mean we're locked into a stalemate?
What do we do?
I freaking told you to
prepare what you needed!
Honestly...
Guess I gotta do it.
Buy me some time, would ya?
I'm gonna rig us up a solution.
S-Sunraku-san?!
Why did you attach me to your arm?!
You're the only one who can fight
this thing right now, Emul!
Let's go with operation,
Rabbit Gun: Turret Palm!
Not again!
I'll get you some carrots later.
Carrots?!
Don't worry. Our job is just to buy time.
We don't gotta beat the thing.
Still, the best defense is a good offense...
So let's keep those attacks coming! Go, Emul!
Righty-o!
I'll do as I must!
Magic Edge!
Nice! It worked!
Bilac-san!
You maybe got an estimate on
how much longer you need?!
It's not like what I'm doing is easy, y'know?
Just hold on!
You got it!
It's gonna be a rush job,
but I'm gonna turn this rusty
Dullahan General's Decapitator
into a weapon that can hurt the Humming Lich!
You ain't dead yet, buddy.
Arms are coming out of the ground!
Easy mode compared to
Wethermon's attack spam!
Fire!
R-Righty-o!
Magic Edge!
A hit!
Th-There are seven of them now!
And each one's holding a different weapon...
G-Goodness gracious!
Okay, avoiding all of them
at once is pretty annoying!
They're coming!
Take it, bird-man!
Hey, you really cleaned
up that rusty old blade!
I didn't have a forge or an anvil,
so it's not my best work,
but I polished it with holy water.
It'll do the job for
slicing up those reapers.
But it's also gotten way more fragile.
It's got eight swings at
most before it breaks.
Keep that in mind, got it?
Translation: "Beat these things
in eight hits or less."
Sounds like a challenge run to me.
What's that, singing?
It's rather frightening!
A singing skelly septet...
Hence "Humming Lich."
A pretty fitting name.
It's only been eight minutes
since the battle kicked off.
Bilac, grab on!
What's the plan, man?
I gotta find out some things
about the clones first!
Skill... Drift Step!
For a second there...
Yeah, the main body didn't take
the damage, but it still reeled.
Which means it's the type of monster
where the original and the
clones all share an HP pool.
And the fact that it reeled
like that from one hit
suggests its HP is pretty low.
I've got my plan all worked out.
Emul!
Bilac!
Let me give you a quick rundown.
Th-The hell you say?
You want me to do what?
Bilac. A weapon should be
wielded in pursuit of victory.
If you can't win,
it's rude to the weapon, right?
Now, get to it!
It's been ten minutes now.
Let's get buffed up and ready to go!
Ready to go!
Emul! Blast the others outta
the way with your Magic Edge!
Righty-o!
The buff skill's got a limitation—
I can't use it until ten
minutes after combat starts,
so I couldn't use it against
the Dullahan General—
"Overheat."
Combine it with Nitro Gain!
This skill's real value isn't in its buffs,
but in the damage control it allows
with its 20%-of-max-HP cost.
HP management that lets me
use Climax Boost at will...
Magic Edge!
Great, you cleared me a path!
Let's start with that annoying archer!
Six-Boat Leap!
And the special attribute
of the Decapitator...
Attacks to the head deal extra damage!
That, plus all the buffs and a critical hit
can take each clone in one strike!
Let's go, Emul!
Next up, the axe-wielder!
Understood!
Five clones and the main body left.
And I've got seven attacks.
Magic Edge!
I've got one more limitation on me.
After five minutes pass, the effect of
Overheat will drop my stats way down,
and I won't be able to slay
them in one hit anymore.
That's why...
I'll finish this before that happens!
He's got Emul's support and all,
but he can dodge all those
attacks and even counter?
No wonder that guy beat a damn Colossus...
Sounds good to me.
I'm down for your plan!
I've got two attacks left.
And that just leaves...
The main body with the staff!
Get to work, Emul!
Doing what?!
Finishing it off, duh!
Magic Edge!
Nice work, Emul!
Skill...
Glowing Pierce!
Yeah, figures I couldn't finish
the main body off by myself.
You held out well, Decapitator.
Sorry...
But hang in there for one more hit!
Finish it off, Bilac!
Six-Boat Leap!
All right, here I go!
Material Focus...
into...
Fortress Breaker!
Hell yeah!
The Human...
No, the Rabbit Pile Bunker did the job!
After I heard Katzo and Pencilgon
talk about the battle with Kirin...
I always wanted to try that one out!
Ow!
You idiot! You almost killed me!
You're the one who threw
me up there, Sunraku-san!
Quit goofing around, you two!
Looks like I might still
be able to patch you up.
Not right this moment, but...
Hey, you guys! Hurry us up to Eighthold!
C'mon, at least let me
leisurely browse my loot!
Sounds like this item's for Shaman stuff, though.
Can't think of how I'd use it.
Is it just me, or has the fog started lifting?
Naturally, as the source
of the miasma is slain.
Sunraku-san. I feel like you're
thinking something terribly wicked.
Heavens! Perish the thought!
What's the matter with you?
Let's get going already!
Okay, now I can use Emul's gates to come
and go between Rabituza and Eighthold.
So, what's the next move?
I'd like to head back to Rabituza for a bit
and get the Dullahan General's
Decapitator fixed up, myself.
Good idea.
Maybe we'll break up and
take a rest for now, then.
Emul, you should wait in Rabituza, too.
What? But why?!
I just got to a new city.
I wanna have a look around.
And your disguises are kinda haute couture.
They make me stand out even more.
I'm not sure I believe you.
I'll buy you carrots while I'm here.
Carrots?!
Th-Then... If we must!
But you mustn't do anything reckless!
Hey, no worries!
Promise me! You will not be reckless!
Seriously, I'm fine! Just get going!
Don't be reckless, huh?
Human nature says, when someone says
"don't do that," you totally do it!
That's the story of Pandora's Box, too.
I think Zeus gave Pandora that box,
knowing she'd open it.
Even when we know it's gonna unleash
all the world's misfortunes...
We just gotta open it!
That's what it means to be human!
Okay, let's get climbing!
Wait for me, Crystal Scorpions!