Hell yeah!
Let's start the plan to level up Bilac!
Yes, indeed!
Y-Yeah!
Okay! Let's head through Fourfolkshire
and on to the Canyon of Ancient Souls!
Get moving, bird-man!
We'll need that magic operations unit
to make you an Ancient Craftsman, right, Bilac?
This area's been a real breeze, huh?
I'm betting the miasma and the undead
would normally be a pain in the ass.
But Sunraku's mark clears up the air
and chases the monsters away,
so it's truly a walk in the park!
On that note, would you guys...
just walk on your own already?!
It's far too troublesome!
You've got the Night Emperor's mark, buddy.
Clinging to you lets us conserve Holy Water, so deal with it.
What am I, your personal air purifier?
Just keep walking.
Half-naked with a bird head, walking through
miasma with rabbits on my shoulders...
Not exactly what I'd imagine myself doing.
Hey, what's going on overtop the mist?
Feels like we could climb up if we wanted.
Would that make it even easier to get to the end?
Might work out if you're feeling suicidal...
but I'll pass, myself.
Atop the cliffs of the Canyon of Ancient Souls lurk
terrifying monsters known as the Crystal Scorpions!
Crystal Scorpions?
They're a bunch of tough nuts not even I could crack.
Crystal Scorpions attack as a swarm,
so if one sees you, you're dead.
Are they over level 100 or something?
A shortcut for super-veterans, maybe?
Was that my imagination,
or did I see something moving just now?
Was it a Crystal Scorpion?!
I hear that the sight of one
means dozens more are on their way!
Just get walking already!
We're after the area boss, remember?!
Yeah, yeah, I get it!
Crystal Scorpions, huh?
Maybe I'll pick me a fight later on.
Didn't you hear what I just said?!
Don't even joke about such a thing!
What's this black dome thing?
Guess this is our destination.
Looks like an area boss to me, yeah.
There's not someone in there already, right?
We've just gotta fight it in here?
Then let's beat the thing and move right along!
Yes, let us!
Give it your best shot, bird-man!
Sunraku—
Well, well.
Yep.
That's what we're after.
The kind of skelly jerk a certain type is really into...
the Humming Lich.
I'm getting "skeleton that dishes out curses" vibes.
So before it throws anything too annoying at us...
we strike first!
Hang on a minute!
That thing's...
Huh? No hitbox?
You moron!
You need a weapon with
a holy attribute to deal any real damage!
Huh? But I don't have any of those!
What fearsome miasma!
It kinda stings!
It's the source of the dang thing in the canyon.
You're being suffocated by all the hatred
and death, more potent than ordinary miasma!
Hey... we're okay.
Thanks to Sunraku's mark, no doubt!
I did take a bit of damage,
but that debuff resistance is doing its work.
Can't believe it's effective even on an area boss's attacks.
But wait, hang on...
If neither of our attacks works on the other one...
Does that mean we're locked into a stalemate?
What do we do?
That's why I freaking told you to prepare what you needed!
Honestly...
Guess I gotta do it.
Buy me some time, would ya?
I'm gonna rig us up a solution.
S-Sunraku?!
Why did you attach me to your arm?!
You're the only one who can fight
this thing right now, Emul!
Let's go with Operation, Rabbit Gun: Turret Palm!
Not again!
I'll get you some carrots later.
Carrots?!
Don't worry. Our job is just to buy time.
We don't gotta beat the thing.
Still, the best defense is a good offense.
So let's keep those attacks coming! Go, Emul!
Righty-o!
I'll do as I must!
Magic Edge!
Nice! It worked!
Oh, Bilac!
You maybe got an estimate on how much longer you need?!
It's not like what I'm doing is easy, y'know?
Just hold on!
You got it!
It's gonna be a rush job,
but I'm gonna turn this rusty
Dullahan General's Decapitator
into a weapon that can hurt the Humming Lich!
You ain't dead yet, buddy.
Arms are coming out of the ground!
This is easy mode compared to Wethermon's attack spam!
Fire!
R-Righty-o!
Magic Edge!
It's a hit!
Th-There are seven of them now!
And each one's holding a different weapon.
G-Goodness gracious!
Okay, avoiding all of them at once is pretty annoying!
They're coming!
Take this, bird-man!
Hey, you really cleaned up that rusty old blade!
I didn't have a forge or an anvil,
so it's not my best work, but I polished it with holy water.
It'll do the job of slicing up those reapers
But it's also gotten way more fragile.
It's got eight swings at most before it breaks.
Keep that in mind, got it?
Translation, beat these things in eight hits or less.
Sounds like a challenge run to me.
Are they singing?
It's rather frightening!
A singing skelly septet, hence the "Humming Lich."
The name's a perfect fit.
It's only been eight minutes since the battle kicked off.
Bilac, grab on!
What's the plan, man?
I gotta find out some things about the clones first!
Skill, Drift Step!
For a second there...
Yeah, the main body didn't take
the damage, but it still reeled.
Which means it's the type of monster where
the original and the clones all share an HP pool.
And the fact that it reeled like that
from one hit suggests its HP is pretty low.
I've got my plan all worked out.
Emul!
Bilac!
Let me give you a quick rundown.
Th-The hell you say?
You want me to do what?
Bilac. A weapon should be wielded in pursuit of victory.
You'd be disrespecting the weapon if you lose, right?
Now, hop to it!
It's been ten minutes now.
Let's get buffed up and ready to go!
Ready to go!
Emul! Blast the others outta the way with your Magic Edge!
Righty-o!
I can only use this certain buff skill
ten minutes after combat starts...
so I couldn't use it against the Dullahan General.
"Overheat."
Combine it with Nitro Gain!
This skill's real value isn't in its buffs,
but in the damage control it allows with
20% of my max HP to activate.
HP management that lets me use Climax Boost at will...
Magic Edge!
Great, you cleared me a path!
Let's start with that annoying archer!
Six-Boat Leap!
And the special attribute of the Decapitator...
Attacks to the head deal extra damage!
That, plus all the buffs and a crit hit
can take each clone in one strike!
Let's go, Emul!
Next up, the axe-wielder!
Understood!
Five clones and the main body left.
And I've got seven attacks.
Magic Edge!
I've got one more limitation on me.
After five minutes pass, the effect of Overheat
will drop my stats way down...
and I won't be able to slay them in one hit anymore.
That's why...
I'll finish this before that happens!
I know he's got Emul's support and all,
but he can dodge all those attacks and even counter?
No wonder that guy beat a damn Colossus.
Sounds good to me.
I'm down for your plan!
I've got two attacks left.
And that just leaves the main body with the staff!
Get to work, Emul!
Doing what?!
Finish the fight, duh!
Magic Edge!
Nice work, Emul!
Skill...
Glowing Pierce!
Yeah, figures I couldn't finish the main body off by myself.
You held out well, Decapitator.
Sorry, but hang in there for one more hit!
Finish it off, Bilac!
Six-Boat Leap!
All right, here I go!
Material Focus...
into...
Fortress Breaker!
Hell yeah!
The Human...
No, the Rabbit Pile Bunker did the job!
After I heard Katzo and Pencilgon
talk about the battle with Kirin...
I always wanted to try that one out!
Ow!
You idiot! You almost killed me!
You're the one who threw me up there!
Quit goofing around, you two!
Looks like I might still be able to patch you up.
Not right this moment, but...
Hey, you guys! Let's hurry up to Eighthold!
C'mon, at least give the guy some time to browse his loot!
Sounds like this item's for Shaman stuff, though.
Can't think of how I'd use it.
Is it just me, or has the fog started lifting?
Naturally, as the source of the miasma is slain.
Sunraku, I feel like you're thinking
something terribly wicked.
Heavens! Perish the thought!
What's the matter with you?
Let's get going already!
Okay, now I can use Emul's gates to come and go
between Rabituza and Eighthold.
So, what's the next move?
I'd like to head back to Rabituza for a bit and get
the Dullahan General's Decapitator fixed up, myself.
Good idea.
Maybe we'll break up and take a rest for now, then.
Emul, you should wait in Rabituza, too.
What? But why?!
I just got to a new city. I wanna have a look around.
And your disguises are kinda haute couture.
They make me stand out even more.
I'm not sure I believe you.
I'll buy you carrots while I'm here.
Carrots?!
Th-Then... if we must!
But you mustn't do anything reckless!
Hey, no worries!
Promise me! You will not be reckless!
Seriously, I'm fine! Just get going!
Don't be reckless, huh?
It's only human nature when someone says,
"Don't do that," you totally do it!
That's the story of Pandora's Box, too.
I think Zeus gave Pandora that box, knowing she'd open it.
Even when we know it's gonna unleash
all the world's misfortunes...
We just gotta open it!
That's what it means to be human!
Okay, let's get climbing!
Wait for me, Crystal Scorpions!