Want to take out the unique monster,
Wethermon the Tombguard,
with just the three of us?
Huh?! A unique monster?!
Right.
Wethermon is likely a
"special condition" type.
Possibilities that come to mind...
"Pick up or destroy a
particular in-game object."
"Last a certain length of time."
"Survive a particular attack."
You occasionally see "reason with
him in the middle of battle," too.
Any idea on what the condition is?
I've tried a few different things,
and I think it's "Last a
certain length of time."
Wethermon the Tombguard's combat
conditions change as time passes.
First, we need to survive
the ten minutes of Phase 1.
I won't let your memories be sad ones.
Please put Wethermon...
Please put my love to rest.
What's this?
A Rebirth Tearjewel?
It's a resurrection item.
If you use it on a disabled
player within ten seconds,
you can revive them with full HP.
Oh, you can do that?
That's a god-tier item, then!
I went from town to town this morning
and bought all twelve that were for sale.
Use them carefully, now.
They cost four million mahni apiece.
Four million?!
We'll get four Rebirth Tearjewels each.
Then there's this, which lets
you revive at half your max HP—
the Divine Lifesalve—
of which we each get five.
That's the max number of extra
lives you can get in this game.
We'll use these 27 resurrection items
to challenge Wethermon the Tombguard.
Right.
Sunraku-kun will take point on
holding off Wethermon's attacks.
If you get killed, Katzo-kun or I will
revive you and take over for a bit.
And the same goes if one
of us bites it, right?
Yes.
To achieve our goal of surviving long
enough against the Colossus, Wethermon,
this is the only way.
I call it...
Zombie Tactics!
Wind Slash!
Katzo-kun!
Way ahead of you!
Take that!
I'm tagging in until you're ready!
What'd you learn, Sunraku?!
You can't beat him, so focus on dodging!
Well, simple enough!
You lasted two minutes, five seconds.
That's a record for a first encounter.
Very impressive.
So, what do you think after
mixing it up with him?
Without one impressive plan, I can tell...
there's definitely no way
I could keep pace with him.
Wethermon the Tombguard...
He definitely belongs in the
"Seven Colossi" league with Lycagon.
Wind Slash!
Well, I spent a whole lot of money
on this "impressive plan"...
So you'd better make it worthwhile.
Four million mahni for a single respawn, huh?
Their durability is down to half
from just two minutes of fighting?!
I guess you really do need a weapon
with enhanced durability...
Time for the weapon whose durability
I raised to the extreme...
Marsh Daggers V3!
Resurrection items, weapons...
On all fronts, the battle against
Wethermon is one of endurance!
I'm tagging in, Katzo!
Okay! I'll take over again if you die!
Right!
Yeah, figured that wouldn't work...
Thunderclap!
Not that easy!
Skate Foot!
Too close!
Thunderclap calls down a five-second
barrage of insta-kill lightning!
Five damn seconds?!
Okay, I'm getting the hang of this!
Even at close range, if I use Skate Foot
followed by running at max speed,
I can just keep ahead of it!
Nimbus Fist.
Okay, got no clue on that one.
Tagging in!
Wind Slash!
Thunderclap!
Screw all this!
I can't dodge that crap!
It'd be a miracle to stay alive for
even thirty seconds against it!
You've done pretty amazingly, even so.
We still have about half our
resurrection items left.
You've done very well.
Y'know, you've been playing with
those scales for a while...
What's it all about?
Just preparing something.
It might be about time to use them, though.
He stopped?
Ten minutes.
Finally there, huh?
Ten minutes have passed.
Phase 2 begins.
E...
Export. Summon Call.
Tactical Mount...
Kirin!
Katzo-kun!
Right, I got this!
Guess my job as resurrection
backup is over...
Just like the intel said...
When you fight Wethermon for ten minutes,
he summons Kirin, the robot horse!
Okay, so it's a horse...
But it's not exactly what I was picturing.
This is more like...
A dump truck with legs!
Phase 2.
Wethermon summons Kirin, and you
must prevent them from combining
while surviving ten minutes,
just like in Phase 1.
Katzo-kun! You handle Kirin!
If you let him stay in charge,
he'll fire missiles and lasers everywhere!
And if he combines with Wethermon,
the whole plan'll be done for!
There'll be no way to stop
them from trampling us,
and it'll be instant death when they do.
The only way to fight that
is to stay on his back
and trigger his "buck-off animation."
Easier said than done, damn it!
How the hell do you expect me
to play cowboy with this thing?!
Didn't you play a lot of Cavalry Crisis,
that mounted fighting game?
Show me your riding technique!
Cavalry Crisis? What the hell is that?!
I've never heard of a
trash game by that name!
Just focus on your job!
Gotcha!
Cav isn't a trash game!
It's more like a god-tier game!
And that was still just a fighting game...
Okay... how do I do this?
SLF's meticulous with its world-building,
and thinking about that usually
leads you to a solution...
In other words, if Kirin is a machine,
he'll need maintenance!
There it is! A maintenance ladder!
Expectations met!
Yes!
Every horse needs a bridle, right?!
Skill, "Whip Puppet: Snake"!
Never thought my sub-job,
"Archaeologist," would pay off like this!
The rodeo technique of the country's
third-ranked Cavalry Crisis player...
I'll show it to you, you bucking bronco!
Hey!
Sunraku-kun and Katzo-kun are
holding off their targets,
but at this rate, we'll run out of
resurrection items before we hit the time limit.
Now's the time to use it...
The Reward Scales!
The Golden Scales is an
NPC-run trading company.
In its possession is a
particular "unique item"—a category
comprising the rarest items in the game.
It is known as the Reward Scales.
By sacrificing items to the
left-side "offering dish,"
you can receive various perks from
the right-side "blessing dish."
Give me the best you've got, Scales.
I did everything I could and finally persuaded
the Golden Scales to lend you to me.
The Rebirth Tearjewels aren't the only
thing I dipped into my savings for.
High-value items I've won through my
exploits, traded for and bought...
Thirty million mahni's worth in total.
And I'm offering it up!
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope,
nope, nope, nope, nope!
The centrifugal force is gonna throw me off!
Damn it! I don't have
enough stamina for this!
Even if I see the attacks coming,
if my stamina management
is just a little off,
I fail to dodge it, and I die on the spot!
"The scales maintain equilibrium."
"Let its value be measured numerically."
"Bestow upon me the power to fight hundreds."
Albeit temporarily, I can award
additional stat points to others...
The rate is one point per 100,000 mahni.
My entire savings—
Three hundred points in total!
We'll start off with fifty points each!
Take them, you thieves!
Whoa!
My stamina's replenished?
No... my stats have increased!
Pencilgon's behind this, eh?
I was wondering why she was
fiddling with those windows...
She gave me boosts to stamina and luck!
It's clear I can't deal damage,
no matter where I hit you...
But...
Infight!
It's not my first time
fighting someone like that.
There's a combat skill that doesn't
pull from strength, but from luck!
Its name...
Wind—
Hand of Fortune!
—Slash!
A swordsman without a sword
is like curry without roux!
Suck on that! You're just
a plate of white rice now!
Get yourself some pickled
plums and try again later!
Skill...
Skate Foot!
Hell yeah!
I got your sword!
How you like that, sucker?!
And it's... so big and heavy!
Can't stick that in inventory, I guess...
But...
Making sure he can't use that
split-second slash attack
or the lightning strikes is huge!
He's still got that
Nimbus Fist going on, but...
I'm safe from that as long as I'm behind him.
Knowing that will let
me avoid it, no problem.
Nice work!
I appreciate you raising my stats and all,
but that's not gonna let me stop this thing!
Katzo-kun! There's about four
minutes left in Phase 2!
You've got to strap in for that long!
He'll keep to that pattern
as long as you stay on him!
I get it, but—
Strap in...?
I just got a great idea.
A great idea?
Tidal Rush.
Close call!
I dodged in the nick of time...
But he almost had me there!
That's gotta be an insta-kill, for sure.
They even gave him a special move set
for if you steal his sword...
This is a bad field layout!
Pencilgon!
I was so focused on evading,
I ran in the wrong direction!
I turned his aggro on Pencilgon!
Tidal—
Eyes on the prize, Wethermon!
I've still got your sword!
He can grab me from that angle, too?!
Tidal Rush.
Sunraku-kun!
Nimbus Fist.
The safe zone for Nimbus Fist
is behind Wethermon!
Seven, eight...
Let's get back to basics, Wethermon.
Wind Slash!
Sunraku-kun!
One more death could doom our chances!
If that last attack had been
anything other than Nimbus Fist,
he could've taken us all out!
Sorry, okay?!
I guess he's better off with the sword!
At least, I know those animations!
Glad to hear it!
Katzo-kun?!
W-W-Watch this!
H-H-He can't b-b-buck me off like this!
I-I-I can stay on him the whole time!
That... was your great idea?
You want me to go tighter?!
Fine, whatever. If that's what you're into.
What? What's going on?
It's just gonna distract you,
so it's better if you don't look.
Got it!
Th-The shaking is d-d-raining
my HP, I th-th-think!
I'm b-b-built to tank damage, b-b-but
I might not last too long like this!
That's fine.
Huh?
I'm not getting a "you beat me" vibe, here...
Right.
Stay on your guard, both of you.
Even when Ashura Kai was
a halfway decent clan,
we only made it this far one time.
In other words...
Phase 2 is over.
The real challenge starts now.
Phase 3...
The last time I made it here, he wiped
out the Ashura Kai with his first move.
When the cracks formed in
Wethermon the Tombguard's armor...
He let out a howl and unleashed a
shock wave across the entire field.
When it hit us, all our buffs
and armor didn't matter a bit.
We died instantly.
Sounds like a pretty solid death sentence...
But you look like you've got a plan.
We'll see about that.
If this doesn't do the trick,
try to dodge it as best you can.
In SLF, the keys to victory
come from the story.
I'd always assumed Wethermon
was some kind of cyborg,
who'd modified his body with
technology from the Divinity...
But...
He called Wethermon the Tombguard
"a living corpse" who'd "outlived his time"?
That's what gave me the key.
His classification is "undead monster"!
For undead, you use holy water!
And that's not just any holy water...
It's holy water the Saint of Love,
Eristella, put her heart into...
The saint's own holy water!
It's the best potion for fighting
the undead you can get!