SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
The Day Starts Early for a Trash Game Hunter
Mini!
SLF Theater
The day starts early for a trash game hunter.
Why are you up so early?
I'm heading out into the country,
so I needed to catch the first train.
As the trash game hunter
takes the maglev line west
he watches the scenery out the window.
Mr. Sunraku's gaze is focused.
I got a tip that there's a shop
with an unopened copy of the limited
edition Moody Music Adventure.
What is Moody Music Adventure?
You know how modern VR games
are generally soundless?
That is to say, they mostly don't use BGM?
But there are also quite
a few full-dive VR games
that use BGM as seen in the display copies.
Put simply, most people
find it annoying and end up
lowering the volume or turning off the BGM,
but this one's a mix between
rhythm game and action RPG,
and someone had the crazy idea to not
let you turn the BGM volume down.
So it's this trash game where you
have to do rhythm game stuff
with this really annoying BGM.
The limited edition comes packaged
with the main character's headphones.
That nice and all, but who'd
want to wear the headphones you
associate with this BGM
that gives you a headache?
As he speaks on with the
force of a raging bonfire,
there is a bitterness in his tone,
combined with a strange sense of delight.
After getting a brief
breakfast at the station,
he arrives at the shop in question.
But his eyes are harsh.
What are you doing?
Look at this.
It's a folding chair.
It's still warm.
Have they been here since
before the first train?
This is the sign of a
crazy trash game hunter.
With his hand to the lingering
warmth upon the folding chair,
Mr. Sunraku scours the area around him.
There's no way there are two limited
edition unopened copies in there.
Which means...
The moment the shop opens,
we'll have to both run for it.
Trash game—it refers to the
content of the game itself.
Mr. Sunraku undergoes a focused warm-up
routine as his eyes gaze ahead.
At times, he must even fight his own kind...
But there's a smile on his lips.
So, how'd it go?
You get into a brawl?
Nah.
The person was there for
something totally different.
So it wasn't a crazy trash game hunter, huh?
What do you mean, "crazy trash game hunter"?
Please don't ask me that.