Pencil Knight
Sunraku
Katzo Tataki
Putting Feelings Into a Moment, Part 2
Rebirth Tearjewel
Divine Lifesalve
A secret formula sealed within specially treated glass.
When used on a disabled target within ten seconds,
it revives them with half of their max HP.
Life is an ever-repeating cycle,
but what a noble thing it is to fight against the tide!
Accept
Divine Lifesalve
Sunraku
Rebirth Tearjewel
Empire Bee Twinblades
Marsh Daggers [V3]
Moonblade (Waxing)
Empire Bee Twinblades
Category: Twinblade
Durability
Attribute: Corrode
Multiplier: x1.15
Tactical Mount
Kirin
Whip Puppet: Snake
Use Items
Reward Scales
Offer Items
Silverite Amber
The Golden Scales
Reward Scales
Offer Items
Goldblood Ricewine
Crimson Grapewine
Offering Dish
30,002,310 Mahni
Choose Your Perk
More Stat Points
Sunraku LV: 50 Mercenary (Twin Blade User)
Oikatzo LV: 50 Monk
Blessings Dish
Perk: Additional Skill Points 300
Weapon unequipped.
Hand of Fortune
Inventory: A player's item storage
Sunraku
Saint's Holy Water