Want to take out the unique monster,
Wethermon the Tombguard, with just the three of us?
Huh?! A unique monster?!
Right.
Wethermon is likely a "special condition" type.
Possibilities that come to mind...
"Pick up or destroy a particular in-game object."
"Last a certain length of time."
"Survive a particular attack."
You occasionally see
"persuade in the middle of battle," too.
Any idea on what the condition is?
I've tried a few different things...
and I think it's "Last a certain length of time."
Wethermon the Tombguard's
combat conditions change as time passes.
First, we need to survive the ten minutes of the first phase.
I won't let your memories be sad ones.
Please put Wethermon...
Please put my love to rest.
What's this?
A Rebirth Tearjewel?
It's a resurrection item.
If you use it on a disabled player within ten seconds,
you can revive them with full HP.
Oh, you can do that?
It's a god-tier item, then!
I went from town to town this morning
and bought all twelve that were for sale.
Use them carefully, now.
They cost four million mahni apiece.
Four million?!
We'll get four Rebirth Tearjewels each.
Then there's this, which lets you revive at half your max HP.
The Divine Lifesalve, and we each get five.
That's the max number of extra lives
you can get in this game.
We'll use these 27 resurrection items
to challenge Wethermon the Tombguard.
Right.
Sunraku will take point
on holding off Wethermon's attacks.
If you get killed, Katzo or I will revive you
and take over for a bit.
And the same goes if one of us bites it, right?
Yes.
To achieve our goal of surviving long enough
against the Colossus, Wethermon,
this is the only way.
I call it...
Zombie Tactics!
Wind Slash!
Katzo!
Way ahead of you!
Take this!
I'm tagging in until you're ready!
Any tips you got, Sunraku?!
You can't beat him, so focus on dodging!
Well, simple enough!
You lasted two minutes, five seconds.
That's a record for a first encounter.
Very impressive.
So, what do you think after mixing it up with him?
Without one impressive plan, I can tell...
there's definitely no way I could keep up with him.
Wethermon the Tombguard definitely belongs
in the "Seven Colossi" league with Lycagon.
Wind Slash!
Well, I spent a whole lot of money
on this "impressive plan."
So, better make it worthwhile.
Four million mahni for a single respawn, huh?
Their durability is down to half
from just two minutes of fighting?!
I guess you really do need a weapon
with enhanced durability.
I got just the thing with its durability
raised to the max, Marsh Daggers V3!
Resurrection items, weapons...
On all fronts, the battle against Wethermon
is one of endurance!
I'm tagging in, Katzo!
Okay! I'll take over again if you die!
Right!
Yeah, figured that wouldn't work.
Thunderclap!
Not that easy!
Skate Foot!
Too close!
Thunderclap calls down
a five-second barrage of insta-kill lightning!
Five damn seconds?!
Okay, I'm getting the hang of this!
Even at close range, if I run at max speed after using
Skate Foot, I can just keep ahead of it!
Nimbus Fist.
Okay, got no clue on that one.
Tagging in!
Wind Slash!
Thunderclap!
Screw all this!
I can't dodge that crap!
It'd be a miracle to stay alive
for even thirty seconds against it!
You've been pretty amazing, though.
We still have about half our resurrection items left.
You've done very well.
Y'know, you've been playing with those scales for a while.
What's it all about?
Just preparing something.
It might be about time to use them, though.
He stopped?
Ten minutes.
Finally there, huh?
Ten minutes have passed.
It's time for the second phase.
E...
Export. Summon Call.
Tactical Mount,
Kirin!
Katzo!
Right, I got this!
Guess my job as resurrection backup is over.
Just like the intel said,
when you fight Wethermon for ten minutes,
he summons Kirin, the robot horse!
Okay, so it's a horse,
but it's not exactly what I was picturing.
This is more like...
a dump truck with legs!
Phase 2.
Wethermon summons Kirin,
and you must prevent them from merging
while surviving ten minutes, just like in the first phase.
Katzo! You handle Kirin!
If you let him stay in charge,
he'll fire missiles and lasers everywhere!
And if he combines with Wethermon,
the whole plan'll be done for!
There'll be no way to stop them from trampling us,
and it'll be instant death when they do.
The only way to fight that is to stay on his back
and trigger his "buck-off animation."
Easier said than done, dammit!
How the hell do you expect me
to play cowboy with this thing?!
Didn't you play a lot of Cavalry Crisis,
that mounted fighting game?
Show me your rodeo skills!
Cavalry Crisis? What the hell is that?!
I've never heard of a trash game by that name!
Just focus on your job!
Gotcha!
Cav isn't a trash game!
It's more like god-tier!
And that was still just a fighting game...
Okay... how do I do this?
SLF's meticulous with its world-building,
and thinking about that usually leads you to a solution.
In other words, if Kirin is a machine,
he'll need maintenance!
There it is! A maintenance ladder!
Expectations met!
Yes!
Every horse needs a bridle, right?!
Skill, "Whip Puppet: Snake"!
Never thought my sub-job,
"Archaeologist," would pay off like this!
The rodeo technique of the country's
third-ranked Cavalry Crisis player...
Have a taste, you bucking bronco!
Hey!
Sunraku and Katzo are holding off their targets,
but at this rate, we'll run out of
resurrection items before the time limit.
Now's the time to use it.
The Reward Scales!
The Golden Scales is an NPC-run trading company.
In its possession is a particular "unique item",
a category comprising the rarest items in the game.
It is known as the Reward Scales.
By sacrificing items to the "offering dish" on the left side,
you can receive various perks
from the "blessing dish" on the right.
Give me the best you've got, Scales.
I did everything I could and finally persuaded
the Golden Scales to lend you to me.
The Rebirth Tearjewels aren't the only thing
I dipped into my savings for.
High-value items I've won through my exploits,
traded for and bought...
Thirty million mahni's worth in total.
And I'm offering it up!
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope!
The centrifugal force is gonna throw me off!
Dammit! I don't have the stamina for this!
Even if I see the attacks coming,
if my stamina management is just a little off,
I fail to dodge it, and I die on the spot!
"The scales maintain equilibrium."
"Let its value be measured.
Bestow upon me the power to fight hundreds."
Albeit temporarily, I can award
additional stat points to others.
The rate is one point per 100,000 mahni.
I'll use my entire savings! Three hundred points in total!
We'll start off with fifty points each!
Take them, you thieves!
Whoa!
My stamina's replenished?
No... my stats got buffed!
Pencilgon's behind this, eh?
I was wondering why she was fiddling with those windows.
She gave me boosts to stamina and luck!
It's clear I can't deal damage, no matter where I hit you.
But...
Infight!
...it's not my first time fighting someone like that.
There's a combat skill
that doesn't pull from strength, but from luck!
Its name...
Wind...
Hand of Fortune!
...Slash!
A swordsman without a sword is like curry without roux!
Suck on that! You're just a plate of white rice now!
Get yourself some pickled plums and try again later!
Skill...
Skate Foot!
Hell yeah!
I got your sword!
How you like that, sucker?!
And it's... so big and heavy!
Can't stick that in the inventory, I guess.
But...
Making sure he can't use that split-second
slash attack or the lightning strikes is huge!
He's still got that Nimbus Fist going on,
but I'm safe from that as long as I'm behind him.
Knowing that will let me avoid it, no problem.
Nice work!
I appreciate you raising my stats and all,
but that's not gonna let me stop this thing!
Katzo! There's about four minutes left in the second phase!
You've got to strap in for that long!
He'll keep to that pattern if you stay on him!
I get it, but...
Strap in?
I just got a great idea.
A great idea?
Tidal Rush.
Close call!
I dodged in the nick of time,
but he almost had me there!
That's gotta be an insta-kill, for sure.
They even gave him a special move set
if you steal his sword.
This is a bad field layout!
Pencilgon!
I was so focused on dodging, I ran the wrong way!
I turned his aggro on Pencilgon!
Tidal—
Eyes on the prize, Wethermon!
I've still got your sword!
He can grab me from that angle, too?!
Tidal Rush.
Sunraku!
Nimbus Fist.
The safe zone for Nimbus Fist is behind Wethermon!
Seven, eight...
Let's do this from the top, Wethermon.
Wind Slash!
Sunraku!
We can't afford any more deaths!
If that last attack had been anything
other than Nimbus Fist,
he could've taken us all out!
Sorry, okay?!
I guess he's better off with the sword!
At least, I know those animations!
Glad to hear it!
Katzo?!
W-W-Watch this!
H-H-He can't b-b-buck me off like this!
I-I-I can stay on him the whole time!
That... was your great idea?
You want me to go tighter?!
Fine, whatever. If that's what you're into.
What? What's going on?
It's just gonna distract you, so it's better if you don't look.
Got it!
Th-The shaking is d-d-raining my HP, I th-th-think!
I'm b-b-built to tank damage,
b-b-but I might not last too long like this!
That's fine.
Huh?
I'm not getting a "you beat me" vibe, here.
Right.
Stay on your guard, both of you.
Even when Ashura Kai was a halfway decent clan,
we only made it this far one time.
In other words...
The second phase is over.
The real challenge starts now.
Phase 3.
The last time I made it here,
he wiped out the Ashura Kai with his first move.
When the cracks formed
in Wethermon the Tombguard's armor...
he let out a howl and unleashed a shock wave
across the entire field.
When it hit us, all our buffs and armor
didn't matter a bit. We died instantly.
Sounds like a pretty solid death sentence.
But you look like you've got a plan.
We'll see about that.
If this doesn't do the trick, try to dodge him as best you can.
In SLF, the keys to victory come from the story.
I'd always assumed he was some kind of cyborg,
who'd modified his body with technology from the Divinity.
But...
He called Wethermon the Tombguard
"a living corpse" who'd "outlived his time"?
That's what gave me the key.
His classification is "undead monster"!
Holy water is effective against them!
And that's not just any holy water.
Eristella, the Saint of Love, put her heart into it.
So it's blessed by the saint herself!
It's the best potion you can get for fighting the undead!