And...
You're certain that Sunraku was his name?
Y-Yeah... I'm pretty sure that was his character name.
Mia! Don't do that!
That's not a monster, it's a player!
A-Are you sure?
It's really scary-looking, though.
Scary-looking players are still players!
So, this person named "Sunraku,"
do you know where he ha—
Er, where did he go?
R-Right!
I think he'd gotten a face full of poison from the Python.
He ran off into Secondale!
And he was half-naked, with a bird mask?
Yeah, but he could've changed his equipment by now.
The mask had such a creepy expression.
I thought it was a monster!
I almost didn't believe it,
but he really beat the Ravenous Python
without visiting the first town.
Thank you for the information.
As a token of my gratitude...
Take it.
Th-Thanks.
Now...
I'll be off.
So fast!
Who was that?
Not sure, but I remember the emblem on the cape.
I think it's from a clan focused on that
unique monster, Lycagon the Nightslayer.
Unique monster?
Lycagon?
Unique monsters are a special class of monsters
with both an individual name and a title.
When you beat basic mobs or capture them or whatever,
they respawn as a new individual
after a set period of time passes.
But for the unique monsters,
there's only one of each in the game world.
Rumor says there's seven of them in SLF,
but we don't even know
the spawn criteria for most of them.
For each of these unique monsters, called "Colossi,"
lots of top players have formed clans
focused on taking them out.
Wow...
So they're just super rare monsters?
That's about what it boils down to, yeah.
The issue is they're a lot stronger than
you can possibly imagine.
See, it's been a year since the game started,
but even with a playerbase of over 30 million,
not one person has defeated a single unique monster.
Unique monster, Lycagon the Nightslayer,
has been encountered.
Unique... monster?
As damn tough as those Redcaps were...
this one blew 'em away in a second.
A single hit from that and I'm a goner, I'll bet.
You...
You unique monsters
don't have much going for you, do you?!
Th-That was freaking close!
I'm so glad I spent all night grinding levels!
If I hadn't learned Perfect Parry,
I'd be totally dead right now!
One wrong move and I'm done for!
Better go all out!
How'd you like that, huh?!
It disappeared again?
Where'll it come from next?
It's teleporting?!
Dammit, the thing's pelt is tougher than
the Ravenous Python's scales!
I've been whaling on the thing
for over five minutes without taking a hit,
but...
the thing's so tough, I don't think
I'm actually doing any damage!
Pretty sure I've landed a hundred... no, two hundred crits!
My new Vorpal Choppers are already falling apart.
If I don't find a softer spot to land a hit on...
my weapons are gonna crap out before I do!
Actually, I'd say...
taking this thing on, I'm batting way out of my league!
But that's the way I like it!
This is it!
This is what makes Shangri-La a god-tier game!
This spine-tingling intensity
that makes me feel like I'm on fire...
It's impossible to enjoy a game more than this!
Bugs! Garbage balance! Absurd spawn rates!
I'm a gamer who's made it through all those trash games!
And since I know you don't have a bugged-out hitbox...
there's no way in hell I'm gonna throw in the towel!
I'm too far for its attack to hit me.
It's howling?!
I can't move!
What'd it do to me?
What'd it hit me with?
Reality's a harsh mistress, huh?
I'm not gonna suddenly learn an awesome new skill
or get saved by a run-in
from some mysterious high-level player.
None of that cinematic stuff for me.
Actually... I did get one break.
Somehow, after a hit like that, I've got one HP remaining.
It's gotta be a miracle.
You're absurdly strong, you know that?
But that was intentionally coded into you.
You're exactly as strong as the devs wanted you to be.
Which means...
You can be beaten.
I've made up my mind.
I don't give a damn about the final boss or the story.
It might not be now, but someday...
I'm gonna defeat you, for sure.
You better not let anyone beat you before then...
Lycagon the Nightslayer!
Huh?
A curse?
"Lycagon's Mark (Curse)."
"Equipment cannot be equipped to the body part
afflicted with Lycagon's Mark."
Hang on.
Am I... screwed?
Lycagon's Mark?!
What the heck is this crap?!
I can't equip stuff to my torso or legs!
That piece of crap wolf!
It shows up out of nowhere, chomps me,
and marks me with a curse?!
You can't just destroy a guy's equipment like that!
"Equipment cannot be equipped to the body part
afflicted with Lycagon's Mark."
"Monsters of lower level than
the afflicted character will flee."
"Lycagon's Mark will affect conversations with NPCs."
"The afflicted body part gains resistance to magic effects."
"The curse can be removed through the prayers of a Saint
or the defeat of the curse's caster"...
The kind of curse where you gotta destroy
the root to be rid of it, huh?
Nice weather today.
This...
This is...
some trash game bullshit!
Going around half-naked?
So lame!
Couldn't be me.
What a freak!
Is it a reference to something?
Calm down, Sunraku.
Remember the three principles
you learned from trash games.
An open mind.
Unbreakable spirit.
And cool-headed judgment.
Looks like you rack up a lot of experience
from just fighting a unique monster.
Which means I leveled up quite a bit,
buffed up my skills, and got lots of stat points to allocate!
This might be a good time to define my build.
I'd better distribute all of these points carefully.
Vitality, 6.
I made myself a glass cannon that can die in one hit!
But what else could I do?!
I'm locked out of 2 out of 4 of my armor slots!
Spending points on vitality is like pissing in the ocean!
Same with my HP!
I'm just gonna have to cover with speed and stamina!
And my best stat is a 65 in luck.
The reason I got off then with one HP remaining...
That's gotta be my luck at play... right?
It's gotta do something, right?
Yeah, I mean... I've been through enough hell already, right?
It's okay to turn to luck for help, right?!
Ow!
Wh-What now?!
Huh? What's a rabbit doing...
I-Is that...
a Vorpal Bunny?!
It is, right?
Though, it doesn't look quite the same.
Hang on, does this game let monsters spawn in towns?!
Get back here, you!
No, that outfit it's wearing...
That's not just some Vorpal Bunny!
I bet if I catch it, I'll get a rare item!
It's gotta be some kind of special event!
Yes! I got you!
A door?
What the...
"Unique Scenario: Invitation from Rabituza"?
I get it. I saw this on the game guide site.
I think it was...
"SLF has a sweeping main story
about the exploration of the world,
but it's also got a huge number of side quests.
One subset of these is called 'unique scenarios'
which are mystery scenarios whose unlock times,
locations, contents, and flags aren't publicly known."
"So the equipment, skills, and spells
you can acquire in these events
What the heck is this?
are said to all be top-class."
So it's not unusual to see clans searching desperately
to find these unique scenarios, huh?
To encounter one this early in my playthrough...
Is this the result of dumping my stat points into luck?!
I won't let this chance slip away!
What... What is this place?!
Everywhere I look...
It's Vorpal Bunnies?!
Did I end up in a monsters' lair?
My fondest welcomes to you, Sunraku!
I've dearly wanted to meet you!
What?! Hello?!
All of Rabituza is abuzz about you, you know!
Despite your great personal weakness,
you had the courage to attempt
the Nightslayer on your own!
And the skills to continue striking perfect
deadly blows without taking a single hit...
You are the embodiment of the vorpal soul!
V-Vorpal soul?
If only I could be like you!
B-But I barely left a scratch on the thing.
Only because it's so very, very powerful!
The Night Emperor is a Colossus,
capable of gobbling down wyverns like a midday snack!
You being here speaking to me now suggests
you are one of the pioneers under the Divinity's protection!
Boy, this bunny loves to talk.
And those marks upon your body prove that
the Night Emperor regards you
not as mere prey, but as a fellow being!
How amazing!
It's not the first game I've played where the monsters talk.
Is this thing an NPC?
It seems pretty focused on Lycagon.
Actually, that one trait of the Mark...
Is this what it was talking about?
And in light of your great deeds, my Da—
I mean, our boss, would very much
like to speak with you, hence why I was sent to fetch you!
M-Meet me?
I hope this isn't revenge for all
the Vorpal Bunnies I killed, Miss, um...
Oh!
You may call me Emul!
Is this thing really AI?
It can even guess what I was gonna ask.
You may rest easy, I assure you.
Our boss is far above petty matters like revenge.
Look at that craftsmanship!
Quite a number of humans visit Rabituza,
but you'll be the first one to visit the palace!
For real?!
Does that mean...
Is this a unique scenario only I know about?!
When that piece of crap dog
gave me this Mark, I was pretty worried.
But it looks like my luck's finally turned around!
Come, come! Right this way!
Daddy—
I mean, Boss!
I brought the human bearer of the vorpal soul to see you!
What kind of show of gratitude—
Oh?
Took you long enough.
So, you're the one that pup beat up and took a piss on?
Y-Yeah...
Go on!
You people lose your vorpal soul so quickly.
I'd assumed you were all hopeless, but...
Looks like at least one of you's got some promise.
Well?
Mind giving me a bit of your time?
I'm the boss here in Rabituza.
The name's Vysache.