SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
Psyger: Episode-0
Mini!
Time Chaser 2
Bullets of Amber
This game is really hard for me.
But if I can't finish it,
I p-probably won't be able to go on an
adventure with Hizutome-kun... right?
Listen, I think you get good
at games impressively quickly.
but instead of these niche games, you might
want to play one with broader appeal.
B-But...
It's Hizutome's skill levels
that make him such a frea—
er, such a unique individual.
I understand that you don't
want to hold him back,
but maybe you should work
on your fundamentals.
Fundamentals?
The truth is, there's a game that unique
individual will definitely try out!
What is it?!
The polar opposite of the
trash games. The god game!
With over 30 million players
worldwide, it's Shangri-La Frontier?
SLF for short, right?
I've heard of it.
My sister's really into it.
What if you have your
sister teach you the game,
and become strong enough that you
can show Hizutome-kun the ropes?
Show him the ropes?
Th-That's a good idea!
Thanks for coming!
I'm going to become strong enough
to show Hizutome-kun the ropes!
What Mana didn't realize
was that her advice, offered
in a spirit of friendship,
would create a hopeless
addict in SLF's world.