And...
You're certain that Sunraku was his name?
Y-Yeah... I'm pretty sure that
was his character name...
Mia! Don't do that!
That's not a monster, it's a player!
R-Really?
But it's really scary-looking...
Scary-looking players are still players!
So, this player named "Sunraku."
Do you know where he ha—
Er, where did he go?
R-Right!
I think he'd gotten a face full
of poison from the Python.
He ran off into Secondale!
And he was half-naked, with a bird's head?
Yeah, but he could've changed
his equipment by now...
The mask had such a scary expression.
I thought it was a monster!
I almost didn't believe it,
but he really beat the Ravenous Python
without visiting the first town...
Thank you for the information.
As an expression of my gratitude...
Take it.
Th-Thanks.
Now...
I'm in a hurry. Goodbye.
So fast!
Who was that?
Not sure, but the emblem on the cape...
I think it's from a clan focused on that
unique monster, Lycagon the Nightslayer.
Unique monster?
Lycagon?
Unique monsters are a
special class of monsters
with both an individual name and a title.
Most monsters, when you beat them
or capture them or whatever,
respawn as a new individual after
a set period of time passes.
But for the unique monsters, there's
only one of each in the whole world.
Rumor says there's seven of them in SLF,
but we don't even know the spawn
criteria for most of them.
For each of these unique
monsters, called "Colossi,"
lots of top players have formed
clans focused on taking them out.
Wow...
So they're just really rare monsters?
That's about what it boils down to, yeah.
The issue is how abnormally strong they are.
See, it's been a year since the game started,
but even with a playerbase
of over 30 million,
not one person has defeated
a single unique monster.
Unique monster, Lycagon the
Nightslayer, encountered.
Unique... monster?
As damn tough as those Redcaps were...
it blew 'em away in a second.
One hit from that and I'm a goner, I'll bet.
You...
You unique monsters don't have
much going for you, do you?!
Th-That was freaking close!
I'm so glad I spent all night grinding!
If I hadn't learned Perfect Parry,
I'd be totally dead right now!
One second's lapse and I'm done for!
Better go all-out!
How'd you like that, huh?!
It disappeared again?
Where'll it come from next?
It's teleporting?!
Ribbit.
Damn it...
The thing's pelt is tougher than
the Ravenous Python's scales!
I've been whaling on the thing for over
five minutes without taking a hit...
But...
The thing's so tough, I don't think
I'm actually doing any damage!
Pretty sure I've landed a
hundred... no, two hundred crits!
My Vorpal Choppers, which started out close
to mint, are already falling apart...
If I don't find a softer
spot to land a hit on,
my weapons are gonna crap out before I do!
Actually, I'd say...
this thing's way out of the league
of what I can fight right now!
But that's the way I like it!
That's the way!
That's what makes it the god-tier
game, Shangri-La Frontier!
This spine-tingling intensity that
makes me feel like I'm on fire...
It's not possible to enjoy
a game more than this!
Bugs! Garbage balance! Absurd spawn rates!
I'm a gamer who's made it
through all those trash games!
And since I know you don't
have a bugged-out hitbox...
There's no way in hell I'm
gonna throw in the towel!
I'm too far for its attack to hit me.
It's roaring?!
I can't move!
What'd it do to me?
What'd it hit me with?
Reality's a harsh mistress, huh?
I'm not gonna suddenly
learn an awesome new skill
or get saved by a run-in from some
mysterious high-level player...
None of that cinematic stuff for me.
Actually... I did get one break.
Somehow, after a hit like that,
I've got an HP remaining...
It's gotta be a miracle.
You're absurdly strong, you know that?
But that absurdity was
intentionally coded into you.
You're exactly as strong as
your creators wanted you to be.
In other words...
It's a beatable absurdity.
I've made up my mind.
I don't give a damn about
the final boss or the story.
It might not be now, but someday...
I'm gonna beat you, for sure.
You better not let anyone
beat you before then...
Lycagon the Nightslayer!
Huh?
A curse?
"Lycagon's Mark (Curse)."
"Equipment cannot be equipped to the body
part afflicted with Lycagon's Mark."
Hang on.
Am I... screwed?
Lycagon's Mark?!
What the heck is this crap?!
I can't equip stuff to my torso or legs!
That piece of crap wolf!
It shows up out of nowhere,
chomps me, and marks me?!
With a curse?!
You can't just destroy a
guy's equipment like that!
"Equipment cannot be equipped to the body
part afflicted with Lycagon's Mark."
"Monsters of lower level than the
afflicted character will flee."
"Conversations with NPCs will be affected
by the presence of Lycagon's Mark."
"The afflicted body part gains
resistance to magic effects."
"The curse can be removed
through the prayers of a Saint
or the defeat of the curse's caster"...
The kind of curse where you gotta
destroy the root to be rid of it, huh?
Nice weather today.
This...
This is...
This is trash game bullshit!
Going around half-naked?
So lame!
Couldn't be me.
What a freak!
Is it a reference to something?
Calm down, Sunraku.
Remember the three principles
you learned from trash games:
Patient mind.
Unbreakable spirit.
And cool-headed judgment.
Looks like you rack up a lot of experience
from just fighting a unique monster...
Which means I leveled up quite a bit,
buffed up my skills and got lots
of stat points to allocate!
This might be a good time to define my build.
I'd better distribute these
fifty points carefully.
Vitality, 6.
I made myself a glass cannon
who can die in one hit!
But what else could I do?!
I'm locked out of two out
of four of my armor slots!
Spending points on vitality
is like pissing in the ocean!
Same with my HP!
I'm just gonna have to cover
with speed and stamina!
And my best stat is a 65 in luck...
The reason I got off then
with one HP remaining...
That's gotta be my luck at play... right?
It's gotta do something, right?
Yeah, I mean... I've been through
enough hell already, right?
It's okay to turn to luck for help, right?!
Ow!
What now?!
What's a rabbit doing...
I-Is that...
a Vorpal Bunny?!
It is, right?
Though, it doesn't look quite the same...
Hang on, does this game let
monsters spawn in towns?!
Get back here, you!
No, that outfit it's wearing...
That's not just some Vorpal Bunny!
I bet if I catch it, I'll get a rare item!
It's gotta be that kind of thing!
Yes! I got you!
A door?
What the...
"Unique Scenario: Invitation from Rabituza"?
I get it. I saw this on
the game guide site...
I think...
"SLF has a sweeping main story
about the exploration of the world,
but it's also got a huge
number of side quests.
One subset of these is
called 'unique scenarios,'
mystery scenarios whose
unlock times, locations,
contents, and flags aren't publicly known."
"So the equipment, skills, and spells you
can acquire in these unique scenarios...
What the heck is this?
...are said to all be top-class."
So it's not unusual to see clans
searching desperately to find
these unique scenarios, huh?
To encounter one this
early in my playthrough...
Is this the result of dumping
my stat points into luck?!
I won't let this chance slip away!
Wh-What is this place?!
Everywhere I look...
It's Vorpal Bunnies?!
Did I end up in a monsters' lair?
My fondest welcomes to you, Sunraku-san!
I've dearly wanted to meet you!
What?! Hello?!
All of Rabituza is abuzz about you, you know!
Despite your great personal weakness,
you had the courage to attempt
the Nightslayer all on your own!
And the skills to continue striking perfect
deadly blows without taking a single hit...!
You are the embodiment of the vorpal soul!
V-Vorpal soul?
If only I could be like you!
B-But I barely left a scratch on the thing...
Only because it's so very, very powerful!
The Night Emperor is a Colossus,
capable of gobbling down
wyverns like a midday snack!
That you are even here
speaking to me now suggests
you are one of the pioneers
under the Divinity's protection!
Boy, this bunny loves to talk...
And those marks upon your body prove that
the Night Emperor regards
you not as mere prey,
but as a fellow being!
How amazing!
It's not the first game I've
played where the monsters talk...
Is this thing an NPC?
It seems pretty focused on Lycagon...
Actually, that one trait of the Mark...
Is this what it was talking about?
And in light of your great
deeds, my Da— ahem—
our boss would very much
like to speak with you,
hence why I was sent to fetch you!
M-Meet me?
I hope this isn't revenge for all the
Vorpal Bunnies I killed, Miss, um...
Oh!
You may call me Emul!
Is this thing really AI?
It can even guess what I was gonna ask...
You may rest easy, I assure you.
Our boss is far above petty
matters like revenge.
Look at that craftsmanship!
Quite a number of humans visit Rabituza,
but you'll be the first
one to visit the palace!
The first one?!
Does that mean...
Is this a unique scenario only I know about?!
When that piece of crap dog gave me
this Mark, I was pretty worried...
But it looks like my luck's
finally turned around!
Come, come! Right this way!
Daddy—
I mean, Boss!
I brought the human bearer of
the vorpal soul to see you!
What kind of show of gratitude—
Took you long enough.
So, you're the one that pup beat
up and took a piss on?
Y-Yeah...
Go on!
You people lose your vorpal soul so quickly.
I'd assumed you were all hopeless, but...
Looks like at least one
of you's got some promise.
Well?
Mind giving me a bit of your time?
I'm the boss here in Rabituza.
The name's Vysache.