Black Wolf Nightslayer
Gift
Coordinate Teleporter
The Seven Colossi
Unique Monster
Lycagon the Nightslayer
Encountered
Perfect Parry
Able to parry an enemy's physical attack
if executed with exact timing.
Vorpal Choppers
Equipped
Slide Step
Bonus to user's evasion.
Sunraku
Lycagon's Mark (Curse)
Applied
Respawn
Secondale  Inn
Lycagon's Mark (Curse)
Equipment cannot be equipped to the body part afflicted with Lycagon's Mark.
Monsters of lower level than the afflicted character will flee.
Conversations with NPCs will be affected by the presence of Lycagon's Mark.
The afflicted body part gains resistance to magic effects.
The curse can be removed through the prayers of a Saint or the defeat of the curse's caster.
Staring Bird Mask
Lycagon's Mark
Splitblade Belt
None
Sunraku
Mercenary (Twin Blade User)  Skill Points Remaining: 50
Cash on Hand            9000 Mahni
Redo
Vorpal Bunny
Unique Scenario
Invitation from Rabituza
Rec. Level               80
Rec. Level  80
Sunraku LV:28
Rabituza
Conversations with NPCs will be affected by
the presence of Lycagon's Mark
Palace of
Rabituza
Boss of Rabituza
Vysache