Winner
Kei Uomi
Errands, Cultivation, and Game Progress
Pro Gamer
With "Nitro Squad"
Mwahaha
Gwahaha
The Serpent's Apple
Non-Standard Armament: Wire
Keep-Out Wire
Non-Standard Armament: Blade
Harbinger
Non-Standard Ether Reactor
Damaged
Unique Monster
Lycagon the Nightslayer
Encountered
Item ownership has been transferred.
Reward Scales
Pencilgon's Storage
Sold Off
Repayment
Tome of Truth: The Tombguard
Flower Pin of Bygone Prayers
Clear Sky Skillbook
A digital record of sword techniques
left by a Divinity-era swordsmaster.
Ownership
Offering
Smug
Unique Hunters
Outrage
Trash Game Alliance
Wolfgang
Gold Rush
Pike-Mounted Heads
Pencilgon-chan
and Her Errandboys
Unique Hunters
Outrage
Trash Game Alliance
Gold Rush
Pike-Mounted Heads
Pencilgon-chan
and Her Errandboys
Wolfgang
Arthur Pencilgon
Oikatzo
Sunraku
mahni
Ancient Craftsman
Master Craftsman
Divine Craftsman