SLF Mini
SLF Theater!
Making Oikatzo
Mini!
That seems decent for my appearance.
I get the feeling they'll tease me
about the female avatar, though.
Or maybe they'll totally ignore it?
Okay, let's go with it.
Please input name.
Name...
It's gotta have "Katzo" in there.
Modor Katzo. Katzo Bushi.
Modor Katzo
Katzo Bushi
After that should be...
They've been playing SLF for a while.
That means I'll be playing catch-up with 'em.
Pursue. "Oi."
Oikatzo, then.
Please input name.
Oikatzo
Nice to meet you.
Actually, that's not quite right...
"Let's work hard together as Oikatzo," maybe.
I guess I'll pick Monk as my job.
And for origin...
"If you play as a Wanderer,
instead of starting in Firstia,
you'll be dropped off somewhere in
the first area, the Rampant Forest."
What kind of weirdo would
want to start off lost?
Actually, I can imagine.
I might even know someone like that...
Okay, I'm getting a late start,
but I'm gonna catch up in no time!
Let's go, god-tier game, Shangri-La Frontier!