This world is filled with
too many games to count,
though the vast majority simply
come and go in obscurity.
The greatest of all games
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide—
Shangri-La Frontier, which rightly
earns the title of "god-tier game"!
One lover of trash games, Rakuro Hizutome,
is trying out the god-tier
game, Shangri-La Frontier!
What adventures await him there?
Okay, let's move on to fortunes.
Number one star sign is...
Gemini! You have the best luck today.
Your lucky item is roller skates.
Gosh, I wish I could ride
roller skates to school!
But where would I get some?
Gotta say, it's one well made game...
Shangri-La Frontier.
I'd originally meant it to
just kill a little time.
But...
The thought of them enjoying it
without me really ticks me off!
Still, there's just a week
until the big tournament,
so I'd better work out the last of the kinks.
Check out Inventoria Key ASAP, man!
Scratch that.
I really can't bear to
let them get ahead of me!
Okay!
Did you see it?
That awesome sci-fi armor lineup?!
I could take on the entire
SLF playerbase with that!
Yeah, I saw it!
If you could use that stuff, it'd change up
the whole game, for real!
Yeah!
So, what now? What now?!
Well, about that...
Before I came here, I went into the storage
space and checked a few things out.
And?!
My conclusion is...
At the moment, they're not useful
as anything more than art pieces.
Those tactical machines and power armors
seem to require a power source called
a "Non-Standard Ether Reactor,"
an item I've never heard of
and have no idea where to get.
And you can't use the weapons
without the power armor on, so...
No way!
I got so excited, I didn't dig any deeper...
Actually, I've got a
Non-Standard Ether Reactor.
Gross!
Where the hell did you get that?!
Maybe it's 'cause I did most
of the fighting against Kirin,
but I got it in my loot.
I underestimated you, Mr. Bondage Rodeo!
Damn it! Wish I coulda seen that rodeo.
It's my one regret of the Wethermon fight...
It seems like it's damaged, though.
You can't fix it at a shop?
The blacksmiths I went to all
turned me away at the door.
"I can't fix a thing if I've
got no idea what it is."
Yeah, being a Divinity-era relic and all...
We might need a specialized blacksmith.
Or a special item...
Either way, I'm stumped.
I might know a way to get it fixed.
Hey! You did that on purpose!
Hey, are you serious about that?
Well, no guarantees.
And since it involves a unique scenario,
it might be hard to get you there.
I was hoping you'd let me
borrow that item of yours.
Okay.
Or so I'd like to say...
But I've got a condition.
I wanna know the unlock conditions for
that unique scenario you're hiding.
Come on, Katzo.
I mean, it's not like I'm
triggering my own unique stuff!
I gotta piggyback on everyone else's stuff!
You sulk about the most annoying things.
In SLF, information on uniques
is extremely valuable.
Even more so for those with monopolies on it.
The three of us didn't come together
purely out of a sense of camaraderie.
To protect our own profits,
we won't share information easily.
And... the same goes for Katzo-kun.
It's not like it showed me the
conditions when I unlocked it,
so I can only explain my
own situation at the time.
Is that enough?
You mean it?
Don't act so shocked.
You're the one who asked.
I didn't wanna reveal this stuff,
but you want a show of good faith, right?
And like I just said, I don't have any
proof that these are the conditions.
All right, here I go.
What I did was...
Unique monster, Lycagon the
Nightslayer, encountered.
Unique... monster?
At level 20 or less,
I lasted five minutes without taking damage
against the randomly encountered unique
monster, Lycagon the Nightslayer,
then landed around 200 critical
hits with a vorpal weapon.
You expect me to do that?!
You acrobatic asshole!
What are you mad at me for?!
It's like if he asked you how you fly,
and you told him to work out his pecs!
You think there's no harm in telling me
because there's no chance I'll do it, right?!
Hey, this isn't fair!
I gave you a genuine answer!
Fine, whatever!
Just take the stupid thing already.
Hey!
Oh, right. Sunraku-kun...
What now?
Could I get back that thing I left with you?
What thing?
Oh, right. Forgot I hadn't done that.
Hey, Sunraku-kun.
Could you hang onto this for a while?
Um, sure.
That thing you were messing with
in the Wethermon fight, right?
You said you'd borrowed it, right?
From an NPC organization
called the Golden Scales.
I think it's part of one of the highest
classes of items in all Shangri-La Frontier.
Theoretically, if you throw in enough money,
you can get stats even higher
than those of a unique monster.
You'd need the budget of a small
country to do it, of course.
It seems the Inventoria can't
be removed once it's equipped,
so I'd expected it to be sold off...
What? Really?
Right, they did mention it
becoming a part of your body...
Fortunately, it doesn't seem to have been
taken, even as part of the PKK penalty.
But this is the one thing I didn't
want to lose, so I laundered it.
Laundered it?
A little trick to keep your items
from being lost to the penalty.
The penalty for PKing means
that when you're killed,
ownership of your items transfers
to the person who killed you.
And you have to pay a fee in proportion
to your wrongdoing—your karma points.
I think it sets your affection levels from
most NPCs to the lowest level possible,
too, but that's fine.
The fee this time was pretty annoying.
Oh, no!
When you're killed,
even items kept in storage will be
automatically seized and sold off
to help pay off the fee.
Protecting certain items from this
seizure is called "laundering."
So instead of putting them in storage,
you gave them to Sunraku
before Psyger-0 killed you?
You can actually do that?
Seems like a pretty big exploit...
No. Even if you hand over the item,
it'll still search through
your history and sell it off.
Huh?
Then why didn't the Scales go away?
The Scales aren't really mine.
Their ownership fundamentally
lies with The Golden Scales.
What matters here is that
items you don't have ownership of
won't be automatically sold off.
But you can't transfer ownership just
by handing an item to someone else.
So when Psyger-0 killed me,
even if I'd been carrying the Scales,
their ownership by The Golden
Scales wouldn't have changed.
So they wouldn't have been sold off;
they'd probably just be dropped as an object.
I think I get the idea,
but how's that laundering?
Isn't it just the Scales falling
outside the standard penalty purview?
You can exploit that property to
do some very interesting things.
"The scales preserve the balance.
Let the past be my payment,
and return what has been offered."
That's the Tome of Truth and...
What's the flower thing?
My loot from the Wethermon fight.
Looks like the three of us each
got slightly different items.
Let's see... "Clear Sky Skillbook"?
I offered the Flower Pin of Bygone Prayers
and the Tome of Truth to the Scales.
In that instant, ownership of the
Pin transferred to the Scales,
which meant they no longer
had physical existence.
So they couldn't be seized?
Right.
And it actually let you get 'em back?
If you pay the price within one week,
you can retrieve the items.
Of course, I had to give up
40 levels to make it happen...
But if it means I get to keep this pin,
I won't miss them.
On top of that, in order
to rent out these Scales,
I used my main weapon as collateral!
The Scales' power transferred its ownership
to the organization, so it's also safe!
So much for wiping the slate
clean on your crimes...
So, how much was the fee?
A good 500 million mahni.
You won't get it outta me.
I don't need to borrow it.
I can totally afford it.
The most recent fight proved it to me.
Proved what?
Hunting unique monsters is
a profitable enterprise.
As simple as that, huh?
On that point, I have a proposal.
Would you two like...
to form a clan with me?
Rock...
Paper...
Scissors!
Yeah! Pencilgon loses!
That means Pencilgon's our clan leader!
Oh, yeah!
Best out of three!
Nothing doing!
I should've known I couldn't beat
their reaction speed...
Just figuring that out, are you?!
I'm not cut out to be a
leader... but ah, well.
Okay, Leader!
Here's your first job.
What should our clan name be?
Okay.
What about this one, then?
Sounds good to me. Pretty cool.
I'd have been okay with
"Pencilgon-chan and Her Errandboys," myself.
I would not have.
All right, my fellows.
Let's ready our drinks.
We will henceforth become
wolves venturing through the
world of Shangri-La Frontier
in search of unique monsters—
And in celebration of Clan
Wolfgang's founding...
A toast!
So, what'll our emblem be?
I think that one...
should be up to Pencilgon!
Get to it, Leader!
Stop making me do everything!
Didn't know there was a pub back here...
I figure it can just be whatever.
Same here.
C'mon, man.
If we're gonna make a guild,
at least think stuff over!
Wow, there's basically no one here.
Hey, you guys.
I've got a question for you.
I've been searching for the trio
who beat the unique monster
from that recent announcement.
Their names are
Arthur Pencilgon,
Oikatzo,
and Sunraku...
Never heard of 'em!
Hey!
Hey, Leader!
I thought you rented the place out!
I don't recall ever saying that!
I just said barely anyone ever went there!
Well, it's good timing.
Let's call the meeting to a close.
My level dropped,
thanks to the Evil Force and all,
so I'd like to do some leveling, myself.
Yeah, and I should turn in the
Scales and get my main weapon back.
You handle the reactor stuff, Sunraku-kun!
You got it!
And you figure out that emblem!
Later!
They split up!
Hey, player named Sunraku!
Wait! Don't run away!
Terribly sorry!
My name's not Sunraku! It's Samraku!
You liar!
Here we go!
I'm back, Emul!
Open a gate, would you?
You're late, Sunraku-san!
Positively tardy!
Now, now. I'll explain later.
Harrumph!
Right, that creepy sword.
I forgot to hand it back to Pencilgon.
Well, next time.
You chose the wrong escape route, buddy!
You're heading right for a dead end!
I just wanna ask you some questions.
You don't have to run—
Hey, he's gone.
Where'd he go?
Huh? Aniki Vash isn't here?
I haven't seen Dadd—the boss
since the day he spoke to you.
Got it.
So he's not necessarily
always at the Palace, huh?
I was hoping to go see him after I did my
skill fusions and point distributions...
You successfully learned
your new skills, I see.
Hey, bird-man...
Would you like to peruse my skill grimoires?
I'm kinda broke.
Hmph!
Don't "hmph" at me, lady.
You were gonna rope me into a purchase
the minute you saw a chance,
you money-grubbing bunny.
Well, where shall we go next?
Who else besides Aniki could
fix the Ether Reactor?
Probably not Bilac, but I might as well ask.
Yeah, I can't fix that.
Yeah, figured.
Only an Ancient Craftsman can
fix up stuff from the Divinity.
I'm only a Master Craftsman.
Pops is the only guy I know
who could handle this.
So you need the "Ancient Craftsman" job?
Ah, well.
I'll forget the reactor for now,
and work on raising my fused skills.
Raising?
Growth?
What is it?
That's it!
I just need to do some raising!
If there's no Ancient Craftsman around,
I just need to turn Bilac
into an Ancient Craftsman!
Don't underestimate the
Ancient Craftsman title!
It's not as easy as you make it sound!
I'm not telling you to become a
Divine Craftsman like Aniki Vash.
Besides, it's a road you've
got to go down someday, right?
Which means now is the time!
Let's make a try at that
Ancient Craftsman title!
Make a try?
I'm not saying this out of a lack of faith.
I'm saying it with full
confidence in your skills!
And I'll help you, of course!
Big Sis Bee, I know you can do it!
Me, an Ancient Craftsman?
You got it, bird-man.
I'll play along.
I'm gonna become an Ancient Craftsman!
Yay, Big Sis Bee!
Hell yeah!
Let's start the plan to cultivate Bilac!
Yes, indeed!
Y-Yeah!