We live in a world filled with countless games...
though the vast majority simply come and go in obscurity.
What's considered the best of the best
is the fully immersive VR game boasting
over 30 million players worldwide.
It rightly earns the status of "god-tier," Shangri-La Frontier!
One lover of trash games, Hizutome Rakurou,
is trying out this very Triple-A!
What adventures await him there?
Okay, let's move on to fortunes.
Number one star sign is...
Gemini! You have the best luck today.
Your lucky item is roller skates.
Gosh, I wish I could ride those to school!
But where would I buy them?
Gotta say, it's a really thought-out game...
Shangri-La Frontier.
I'd originally meant it to just kill a little time.
But...
The thought of them enjoying it
without me really ticks me off!
Still, there's just a week until the big tournament,
so I'd better work out the last of the kinks.
Check out the Inventoria Key ASAP, man!
Scratch that. I'm not gonna let them have all the fun!
Okay!
Did you see it?
That awesome sci-fi armor lineup?!
I could take on the entire SLF playerbase with those!
Yeah, I saw it!
If you could use that stuff,
it'd change up the whole game, for real!
Yeah!
So, what now? What now?!
Well, about that...
Before I came here...
I went into the storage space and checked a few things out.
And?!
My conclusion is...
At the moment, they're nothing
more than just glorified art pieces.
Those tactical machines and power armors seem to require
a power source called a "Non-Standard Ether Reactor,"
an item I've never heard of and have no idea where to get.
And you can't use the weapons
without the power armor on, so...
No way!
I got so excited, I didn't do my usual digging...
Actually, I've got one of those with me.
Gross!
Where the hell did you get that?!
Maybe it's 'cause I did most of the fighting against Kirin...
but I got it in my loot.
I underestimated you, Mr. Bondage Rodeo!
Dammit! Wish I coulda seen that rodeo.
It's my one regret with the Wethermon fight...
Seems like it's damaged, though.
You can't fix it at a shop?
The blacksmiths I went to all turned me away
as soon as they saw it.
"I can't fix a thing if I've got no idea what it is."
Yeah, being a Divinity-era relic and all...
We might need a specialized blacksmith.
Or a special item...
Either way, I'm stumped.
I might know a way to get it fixed.
Hey! You did that on purpose!
Hey, you serious about that?
Well, no guarantees.
And since it involves a unique scenario,
it might be hard to get you there.
I was hoping you'd let me borrow that item of yours.
Okay.
Or so I'd like to say...
but I've got a condition.
I wanna know the unlock conditions
for that unique scenario you're hiding.
Come on, Katzo.
I mean, it's not like I'm triggering my own unique stuff!
I gotta piggyback on everyone else's!
You sulk about the most annoying things.
In SLF, information on uniques is extremely valuable.
Even more so for those with monopolies on it.
The three of us didn't come together
purely out of a sense of camaraderie.
To protect our own profits,
we won't share information easily.
And...
the same goes for Katzo.
It's not like it showed me
the conditions when I unlocked it...
so I can only explain my own situation at the time.
Is that enough?
You mean it?
Don't act so shocked. You're the one who asked.
I didn't wanna reveal this stuff,
but you want a show of good faith, right?
And like I just said, I don't have any proof
that these are the conditions.
All right, here I go.
What I did was...
Unique monster, Lycagon the Nightslayer,
has been encountered.
Unique... monster?
At level 20 or less,
I lasted five minutes without taking damage
against the randomly encountered
unique monster, Lycagon the Nightslayer.
Then, I landed around 200 crits with a vorpal weapon.
You expect me to do that?!
You flipping show-off!
What are you mad at me for?!
It's like if he asked you how you fly,
and you told him to work out his pecs!
You think there's no harm in telling me
because there's no chance I'll do it, right?!
Hey, this isn't fair!
I gave you a genuine answer!
Fine, whatever!
Just take the stupid thing already.
Hey!
Oh, right. Sunraku...
What now?
Could I get back that thing I left you?
What thing?
Oh, right. Forgot I hadn't done that.
Hey, Sunraku.
Could you hang onto this for a while?
Um, sure.
That thing you were messing with
in the Wethermon fight, right?
Didn't you say you'd borrowed it?
From an NPC organization called the Golden Scales.
I think it's part of one of the highest classes
of items in all of SLF.
Theoretically, if you throw in enough money,
you can get stats even higher than
those of a unique monster.
You'd need the budget of a small country to do it, of course.
It seems the Inventoria can't be removed once it's equipped,
so I'd expected it to be sold off.
What? Really?
Right, they did mention it becoming a part of your body.
Fortunately, it doesn't seem to have been taken,
even as part of the PKK penalty.
But this is the one thing
I didn't want to lose, so I laundered it.
Laundered it?
A little trick to keep your items
from being lost to the penalty.
The penalty for PKing means that when you're killed,
ownership of your items transfers
to the person who killed you.
And you have to pay a fee in proportion to
your wrongdoing, which are your karma points.
I think it sets your affection levels
from most NPCs to the lowest level possible, too,
but that's fine.
The fee this time was pretty annoying.
Oh, no!
When you're killed, even items kept in storage will be
automatically seized and sold off to help pay off the fee.
Protecting certain items
from this seizure is called "laundering."
So instead of putting them in storage,
you gave them to Sunraku before Psyger-0 killed you?
You can actually do that? Seems like a pretty big exploit.
No. Even if you hand over the item,
it'll still search through your history and sell it off.
Huh?
Then why didn't the Scales go away?
Because they aren't really mine.
Their ownership fundamentally lies with The Golden Scales.
What matters here is that
items you don't have ownership
of won't be automatically sold off.
But you can't transfer ownership
just by handing an item to someone else.
So when Psyger-0 killed me,
even if I'd been carrying the Scales...
their ownership by The Golden Scales
wouldn't have changed.
So they wouldn't have been sold off,
they'd probably just be dropped as an object.
I think I get the idea, but how's that laundering?
Isn't it just the Scales falling outside
the standard penalty purview?
You can exploit that property
to do some very interesting things.
"The scales preserve the balance.
Let the past be my payment,
and return what has been offered."
That's the Tome of Truth and... what's that flower thing?
My loot from the Wethermon fight.
Looks like we each got some personalized stuff.
Let's see... "Clear Sky Skillbook"?
I offered the Flower Pin of Bygone Prayers
and the Tome of Truth to the Scales.
In that instant, ownership of the pin
transferred to the Scales,
which meant they no longer had physical existence.
So they couldn't be seized?
Right.
And it actually let you get 'em back?
If you pay the price within a week,
you can retrieve the items.
Of course, I had to give up 40 levels to make it happen.
But if it means I get to keep this pin, I won't miss them.
On top of that, in order to rent out these Scales,
I used my main weapon as collateral!
The Scales' power transferred its ownership
to the organization, so it's also safe!
So much for wiping the slate clean.
So, how much was the fee?
A good 500 million mahni.
You won't get it outta me.
I don't need to borrow it.
I can totally afford it.
And thanks to our last raid, it was crystal clear.
About what?
Hunting unique monsters is a profitable enterprise.
As simple as that, huh?
On that point, I have a proposal.
Would you two like...
to form a clan with me?
Rock...
paper...
scissors!
Yeah! Pencilgon loses!
That means she'll be our clan leader!
Oh, yeah!
Best out of three!
Nothing doing!
I should've known I couldn't beat their reaction speed.
Just figuring that out, are you?!
I'm not cut out to be a leader... but ah, well.
Okay, Leader! Here's your first job.
What should our clan name be?
Okay.
What about this one, then?
Sounds good to me. Pretty cool.
I'd have been okay with "Pencilgon and Her Errandboys,".
I wouldn't have.
All right, my clanmates, let's raise our glasses.
We will henceforth become wolves venturing through
the world of SLF in search of unique monsters.
And in celebration of the Wolfgang Clan's founding...
A toast!
So, what'll our emblem be?
I think that one... should be up to Pencilgon!
Get to it, Leader!
Stop making me do everything!
Didn't know there was a pub back here.
I figure it can just be whatever.
Same here.
C'mon, man.
If we're gonna make a guild, at least think stuff over!
Wow, there's basically no one here.
Hey, you guys.
Could I ask you something?
I've been searching for the trio who beat
the unique monster from that recent announcement.
Their names are...
Arthur Pencilgon,
Oikatzo,
and Sunraku...
Never heard of 'em!
Hey!
Hey, Leader! I thought you rented the place out!
I don't recall ever saying that!
I just said barely anyone ever went there!
Well, it's good timing.
Let's call the meeting there.
My level dropped, thanks to the Evil Force and all,
so I'd like to do some leveling, myself.
Yeah, and I should turn in the Scales
and get my main weapon back.
You handle the reactor stuff, Sunraku!
You got it!
And you figure out that emblem!
Later!
They split up!
Hey, player named Sunraku!
Wait! Don't run away!
Terribly sorry!
My name's not Sunraku! It's Samraku!
You liar!
Here we go!
I'm back, Emul!
Open a gate, would you?
You're late, Sunraku!
Positively tardy!
Now, now. I'll explain later.
Harrumph!
Right, that creepy sword.
I forgot to hand it back to Pencilgon.
Well, next time.
You chose the wrong escape route, buddy!
You're heading right for a dead end!
I just wanna ask you some questions.
You don't have to run...
Wait, he's gone.
Where'd he go?
Huh? Don Vash isn't here?
I haven't seen Dadd—the boss
since the day he spoke to you.
Got it.
So he's not necessarily always at the Palace, huh?
I was hoping to go see him after I did
my skill fusions and point distributions.
You successfully learned your new skills, I see.
Hey, bird-man...
Would you like to peruse my skill grimoires?
I'm kinda broke.
Hmph!
Don't "hmph" at me, lady.
You were gonna rope me into a purchase the minute
you saw a chance, you money-grubbing bunny.
Well, where shall we go next?
Who else besides Vash could fix the Ether Reactor?
Probably not Bilac, but I might as well ask.
Yeah, I can't fix that.
Figured.
Only an Ancient Craftsman
can fix up stuff from the Divinity.
I'm only a Master Craftsman.
Pops is the only guy I know who could handle this.
So you need the "Ancient Craftsman" job?
Ah, well.
I'll forget the reactor for now,
and work on raising my fused skills.
Raising?
Growth?
What is it?
That's it!
I just need to do some "raising"!
If there's no Ancient Craftsman around,
I just need to turn Bilac into one!
Don't underestimate the title!
It's not as easy as you make it sound!
I'm not telling you to become
a Divine Craftsman like Don Vash.
Besides, it's a road you've got to go down someday, right?
Which means now is the time!
Let's make a try at that Ancient Craftsman title!
Could I even?
I'm not saying this out of a lack of faith.
I have full confidence in your skills!
And I'll help you, of course!
Big Sis Bee, I know you can do it!
Me, an Ancient Craftsman?
You got it, bird-man.
I'll play along.
I'm gonna become an Ancient Craftsman!
Yay, that's my big sis!
Hell yeah!
Let's start the plan to boost Bilac!
Yes, indeed!
Y-Yeah!